[
  {
    "question": "Hey, okay",
    "answer": "lets meet tomorrow for a quick meeting",
    "timestamp": "2023-04-05T15:58:52",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "sure",
    "answer": "cool lets target 3:30?",
    "timestamp": "2023-04-05T15:59:21",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "sure that works for me",
    "answer": "3:30 then",
    "timestamp": "2023-04-05T15:59:58",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "üëçüèª",
    "answer": "If you can come slightly earlier",
    "timestamp": "2023-05-05T15:03:20",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "i‚Äôll try my best",
    "answer": "cool",
    "timestamp": "2023-05-05T15:07:25",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "hey, sure [Image] [Image] [Image]",
    "answer": "Thanks [Image]",
    "timestamp": "2023-06-05T17:43:19",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "hey, will we be meeting today?",
    "answer": "Hey yea",
    "timestamp": "2023-12-05T12:54:05",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "is 2:45 possible",
    "answer": "Sure [Image] [Image] [Image] [Image]",
    "timestamp": "2023-12-05T13:54:11",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "hey, is sindh micro finance bank good for an internship?",
    "answer": "Yes send me their website link",
    "timestamp": "2023-12-05T22:52:44",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "internships"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://www.sindhmfb.com/",
    "answer": "Solid",
    "timestamp": "2023-12-05T22:54:58",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "there‚Äôs availability and i‚Äôll register by this week",
    "answer": "yes that works as well, but we have to really do some impactful work",
    "timestamp": "16/05/2023, 2:36:51‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay",
    "answer": "ok greenstar is good",
    "timestamp": "16/05/2023, 2:42:33‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "yes i‚Äôll plan it out in a way where i can do both",
    "answer": "yes also i checked KDSP Website",
    "timestamp": "16/05/2023, 3:18:48‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hello, hope ur had an enjoyable eid. Please advise as to when i come for a meeting.",
    "answer": "Let‚Äôs target Wednesday",
    "timestamp": "2023-03-07T14:01:24",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "i‚Äôm available other than 2-6",
    "answer": "Ok let‚Äôs coordinate a time tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "2023-03-07T14:02:36",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "i‚Äôm in new york for a few days and i was wondering if it would be advisable to have a new york state license to help reduce tuition. Also, would opening up a phone account be beneficial to apply for state fees.",
    "answer": "Hey let me revert on this",
    "timestamp": "2023-10-08T00:47:10",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "somewhere around cornell and stony brook",
    "answer": "results? [Image]",
    "timestamp": "2023-10-08T03:57:26",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "and drop physics",
    "answer": "Yes do that",
    "timestamp": "2023-10-08T10:59:04",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "that‚Äôs what i was thinking",
    "answer": "Ok dropping physics makes sense",
    "timestamp": "2023-10-08T10:59:08",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "will retaking affect my us applications ?",
    "answer": "Well it will, but if results improve it will help",
    "timestamp": "2023-10-08T11:22:44",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "also how long does it take to recheck ?",
    "answer": "youll need to ask kgs",
    "timestamp": "2023-10-08T11:27:38",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sure, we can schedule a call once you send them over",
    "answer": "Sadaf pls add his mom and make me admin too",
    "timestamp": "21/08/2023, 10:36:36‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéYou added Zahid Hameed",
    "answer": "Asa let Sadaf communicate a time and we can have a meeting with everyone soon",
    "timestamp": "22/08/2023, 2:55:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "noted, see you",
    "answer": "Hello",
    "timestamp": "25/10/2023, 2:41:35‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "i‚Äôm finalizing applying to canada with my father, will submit the application by tonight.",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "26/10/2023, 12:18:03‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "yes i have [Image]",
    "answer": "Good stuff",
    "timestamp": "17/11/2023, 5:05:28‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "thank you",
    "answer": "When are we completing the UC form pls",
    "timestamp": "17/11/2023, 5:06:16‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hello, i‚Äôll be coming at 2 to work on my UC application",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "21/11/2023, 12:40:26‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "hello, i‚Äôll be coming at 4 tomorrow to finalize my UC App",
    "answer": "@923353797821 can you have a zoom session for Canada portals",
    "timestamp": "22/11/2023, 11:40:06‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "will do",
    "answer": "thanks",
    "timestamp": "23/11/2023, 4:51:16‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://us05web.zoom.us/j/84927464015?pwd=anAEXbEFfwwUS9ljjaFSNHexyyZZAv.1 u can join this, lets do a quick run through your portals",
    "answer": "Aariz",
    "timestamp": "23/11/2023, 10:34:56‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "sure what time do u want me to come in tomorrow ?",
    "answer": "2:30?",
    "timestamp": "27/11/2023, 6:18:57‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "sure",
    "answer": "Rizwan.javed@dignosco.org",
    "timestamp": "27/11/2023, 6:21:43‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "pls send me login details",
    "timestamp": "21/12/2023, 12:32:29‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "sure",
    "answer": "ok have reviewed",
    "timestamp": "21/12/2023, 12:53:18‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Northeastern Bentley Babson F&M UIUC",
    "answer": "you live close by?",
    "timestamp": "21/12/2023, 1:03:41‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "yes",
    "answer": "so if you can come twice",
    "timestamp": "21/12/2023, 1:04:01‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "i‚Äôm not home right now but i can come in earlier by 2:30 instead of 3",
    "answer": "ok 3 is ok for now",
    "timestamp": "21/12/2023, 1:05:17‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hello @923333575290, when do i need to come in to submit my nyu and university of miami application since the deadline is on the 1st",
    "answer": "If all is ready come",
    "timestamp": "29/12/2023, 11:28:19‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hello @923018379777 can i come in today to show my u miami app and submit it",
    "answer": "1:30",
    "timestamp": "30/12/2023, 11:32:21‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "i‚Äôm out with my father for some work so i‚Äôll be coming a little later, hope that‚Äôs okay",
    "answer": "Hey I have to leave early today",
    "timestamp": "30/12/2023, 12:18:01‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also @923312220925 Miami was reviewed already is there any specific question you have ?",
    "answer": "you can just share a PDF here",
    "timestamp": "30/12/2023, 12:28:49‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "It‚Äôs here I have already reviewed it",
    "answer": "good to go.",
    "timestamp": "30/12/2023, 12:57:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "By tonight iA. Don‚Äôt worry we will submit by tomorrow ‚Äé[01/01/2024, 1:23:46‚ÄØPM] Aariz Zahid: NYU .pdf ‚Ä¢ ‚Äé3 pages ‚Äédocument omitted",
    "answer": "fix the line spacing between the essay",
    "timestamp": "31/12/2023, 2:43:52‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "yes ‚Äé[01/01/2024, 2:15:21‚ÄØPM] Aariz Zahid: NYU.pdf ‚Ä¢ ‚Äé3 pages ‚Äédocument omitted",
    "answer": "looks good",
    "timestamp": "2024-01-01T14:12:38",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "should i submit nyu ?",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "2024-01-01T14:31:52",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923333575290 there‚Äôs an optional place to upload my resume on babson‚Äôs application so do i leave that blank ?",
    "answer": "Yes ‚Äé[01/01/2024, 11:51:39‚ÄØPM] Aariz Zahid: Babson 1.pdf ‚Ä¢ ‚Äé2 pages ‚Äédocument omitted ‚Äé[01/01/2024, 11:51:39‚ÄØPM] Aariz Zahid: Babson 2.pdf ‚Ä¢ ‚Äé2 pages ‚Äédocument omitted",
    "timestamp": "2024-01-01T20:58:37",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923312220925 have sent across the supplement [Image]",
    "answer": "Looks ok",
    "timestamp": "2024-04-01T18:38:36",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "is it possible for me to come in today and show you the entire SRAR once as i have a few questions as well",
    "answer": "come now",
    "timestamp": "2024-09-01T14:49:45",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "i can use the B i got in econ earlier instead right ?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "timestamp": "2024-10-01T11:11:51",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok please do this and share so I can see the short answers [Image] [Image]",
    "answer": "Let‚Äôs think better for dream trip",
    "timestamp": "15/01/2024, 7:22:45‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "is tokyo good for dream vacation",
    "answer": "Some other kid put Tokyo",
    "timestamp": "15/01/2024, 8:32:07‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Honolulu ?",
    "answer": "How about northern lights type?",
    "timestamp": "15/01/2024, 8:34:54‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "yes sure that‚Äôs Tromso, Norway then",
    "answer": "üëç",
    "timestamp": "15/01/2024, 8:36:51‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I think edupreneur would be nice with your profile also ‚Äé[15/01/2024, 10:09:46‚ÄØPM] Aariz Zahid: UNC App.pdf ‚Ä¢ ‚Äé17 pages ‚Äédocument omitted",
    "answer": "ok [Image]",
    "timestamp": "15/01/2024, 9:37:39‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "please approve when i can submit both",
    "answer": "Ok for both",
    "timestamp": "15/01/2024, 10:20:00‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay thank you",
    "answer": "Aariz",
    "timestamp": "15/01/2024, 10:53:57‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923312220925 please take out the questions for Michigan and work on well thought out drafts. Use previously edited content where relavnt and do thorough research on the university where needed. Please share this by Thursday",
    "answer": "yes pls spealk to me today",
    "timestamp": "16/01/2024, 4:38:45‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay noted [Image]",
    "answer": "Yea",
    "timestamp": "16/01/2024, 5:07:54‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "For bocconi do i upload a pdf of my pakistani passport or american ?",
    "answer": "Do American",
    "timestamp": "17/01/2024, 9:36:41‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "can i please come in tomorrow to work on bocconi and to ask a few questions regarding my portals",
    "answer": "Sure",
    "timestamp": "17/01/2024, 9:46:09‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "when‚Äôs the earliest i can come - i won‚Äôt be going to school",
    "answer": "afternoon is best",
    "timestamp": "17/01/2024, 9:46:56‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sure get in touch when free ‚Äé[22/01/2024, 3:49:26‚ÄØPM] Aariz Zahid: U Michigan Drafts .docx ‚Äédocument omitted ‚Äé[23/01/2024, 11:26:54‚ÄØAM] Aariz Zahid: Aariz Resume.pdf ‚Ä¢ ‚Äé2 pages ‚Äédocument omitted",
    "answer": "resume looks good",
    "timestamp": "22/01/2024, 1:55:23‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "am i good to submit bocconi then ?",
    "answer": "yes good to go",
    "timestamp": "23/01/2024, 1:32:15‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay",
    "answer": "Done",
    "timestamp": "23/01/2024, 1:38:02‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Nice! Congratulations",
    "answer": "MA Mubarak",
    "timestamp": "23/01/2024, 8:43:34‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok @923312220925 please make sure app is filled. Once the UK statement is finalised we will use that ‚Äé[25/01/2024, 9:46:00‚ÄØPM] Aariz Zahid: ‚Äéimage omitted [Image]",
    "answer": "@447949508623",
    "timestamp": "25/01/2024, 11:39:36‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923018379777 please check his UCAS choices",
    "answer": "Ok will do shortly",
    "timestamp": "27/01/2024, 11:25:20‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "Let me call you",
    "answer": "also i need UCAS login",
    "timestamp": "27/01/2024, 1:29:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "i‚Äôm in dubai so whatsapp isn‚Äôt working, do you have botim ?",
    "answer": "Aariz what are predicted grades",
    "timestamp": "27/01/2024, 1:33:00‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "A* Math A Psych B Econ",
    "answer": "app is completely ready",
    "timestamp": "27/01/2024, 1:34:29‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes",
    "answer": "we need the PS ‚Äé[27/01/2024, 1:49:31‚ÄØPM] Aariz Zahid: UofT drafts .docx ‚Äédocument omitted",
    "timestamp": "27/01/2024, 1:38:17‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "5th choice ? [Image]",
    "answer": "Yup [Image]",
    "timestamp": "28/01/2024, 5:44:31‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay thank you [Image]",
    "answer": "üëçüëç",
    "timestamp": "30/01/2024, 9:54:12‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay thank you",
    "answer": "what was our fifth choice",
    "timestamp": "31/01/2024, 6:26:52‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "wilfrid laurier",
    "answer": "UK one",
    "timestamp": "31/01/2024, 6:54:11‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "lse kings ucl durham [Image]",
    "answer": "üëç [Image] [Image]",
    "timestamp": "31/01/2024, 6:57:36‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "i didn‚Äôt apply there [Image] [Image] [Image]",
    "answer": "Yup",
    "timestamp": "2024-04-03T14:59:17",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay ‚Äé[11/03/2024, 3:05:11‚ÄØPM] Aariz Zahid: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "answer": "amazing man",
    "timestamp": "2024-09-03T05:57:53",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923018379777 do you know what the process is to apply for an Italian student visa ?",
    "answer": "Will  guide don‚Äôt worry",
    "timestamp": "2024-12-03T16:52:08",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "is it possible for me to come in with my dad to discuss this",
    "answer": "Ok let‚Äôs target for coming week",
    "timestamp": "2024-12-03T17:07:44",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "sure, let me know when convenient [Image] [Image]",
    "answer": "So transferring frm Dearborn to annarbor happens a lot",
    "timestamp": "2024-12-03T19:07:02",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Great üëç [Image]",
    "answer": "Ok join the waitlist [Image]",
    "timestamp": "15/03/2024, 10:44:25‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay [Image] [Image] [Image]",
    "answer": "Wow",
    "timestamp": "16/03/2024, 1:11:22‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Salam @923018379777 @923333575290 need to meet and discuss enrollment  procedure for bocconi as the deadline is the 21st of March. Kindly let me know when you‚Äôre available.",
    "answer": "My suggestion is to do the enrolment regardless",
    "timestamp": "16/03/2024, 8:09:02‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Euro 2000",
    "answer": "So regardless of whatever we choose for the US we should pay this and lock",
    "timestamp": "16/03/2024, 8:10:01‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "hello @923018379777 i‚Äôm filling the bocconi enrollment form - which passport do i upload as i‚Äôll be applying for the study visa on the same one [Image]",
    "answer": "I think best is to email and ask Bocconi [Image]",
    "timestamp": "17/03/2024, 10:43:07‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéThis message was deleted. [Image]",
    "answer": "Have you paid enrolment deposit for Bocnooi",
    "timestamp": "17/03/2024, 11:25:53‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "sure [Image]",
    "answer": "Please accept it",
    "timestamp": "21/03/2024, 9:45:50‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "it‚Äôs asking for additional updates",
    "answer": "We can provide [Image] [Image] [Image] [Image] [Image]",
    "timestamp": "23/03/2024, 1:50:40‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "hello @923018379777 please let me know when i can come in this week - preferably before thursday since bocconis residence form opens that day and i would like some clarity in my decision before i fill it out.",
    "answer": "Come on Tuesday",
    "timestamp": "13/04/2024, 6:03:26‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "sure what time ?",
    "answer": "Come around 3!",
    "timestamp": "13/04/2024, 6:03:54‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "is it possible to come on monday or wednesday post 4:30 so i can bring my parents along as well",
    "answer": "Ok so let‚Äôs do Wednesday 4:45?",
    "timestamp": "13/04/2024, 6:05:25‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "yes okay that works",
    "answer": "Hey Aariz",
    "timestamp": "13/04/2024, 6:06:48‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "a minute away",
    "answer": "ok [Image]",
    "timestamp": "17/04/2024, 4:46:25‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "hello @923018379777 what will be the first step for the italian student visa ? [Image]",
    "answer": "Checklist Plus polio n Covid pass [Image] [Image] [Image]",
    "timestamp": "18/04/2024, 12:55:02‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay noted",
    "answer": "Aaraiz pls share your updated admissions sheet",
    "timestamp": "21/04/2024, 12:47:46‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "i‚Äôm unsure of : CIMEA Certificate Documents attested by MOFA camp office",
    "answer": "Next to FTC. Very convenient and runs like clockwork",
    "timestamp": "22/04/2024, 3:38:55‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "also what documents will i be needing to take it for it",
    "answer": "Actually all documents",
    "timestamp": "22/04/2024, 4:25:50‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "noted",
    "answer": "Update ?",
    "timestamp": "22/04/2024, 5:40:28‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "hello @923018379777, is this the correct form for the italian student visa ? [Image]",
    "answer": "Bro I‚Äôll need to ask someone in the morning",
    "timestamp": "13/05/2024, 11:00:42‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "thank you",
    "answer": "Looks fine [Image] [Image]",
    "timestamp": "13/05/2024, 11:15:47‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Aariz Zahid",
    "student_phone": "+1814886180",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Got in Alhamdulillah",
    "answer": "Congrats",
    "timestamp": "30/03/2018, 3:04:48‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Ali",
    "student_phone": "+5061717673",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thank you Rizwan bhai",
    "answer": "Ab kya Berkeley, Wharton kei baad",
    "timestamp": "30/03/2018, 3:05:03‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Ali",
    "student_phone": "+5061717673",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hahahahahahahaha",
    "answer": "Btw I told Zaidi last night that you‚Äôll get Wharton. Haha",
    "timestamp": "30/03/2018, 3:05:51‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Ali",
    "student_phone": "+5061717673",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéYou're now an admin",
    "answer": "Abdullah",
    "timestamp": "13/11/2020, 6:03:54‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes that's fine with me",
    "answer": "Join Zoom Meeting https://us04web.zoom.us/j/79980096933?pwd=TDFKa25HWGp4ZmFBQitaQ3FmbWlsZz09 Meeting ID: 799 8009 6933 Passcode: 0zKhYk ‚Äé[28/11/2020, 4:12:08‚ÄØPM] Abdullah Bilwani: ‚Äéimage omitted ‚Äé[28/11/2020, 4:12:08‚ÄØPM] Abdullah Bilwani: ‚Äéimage omitted ‚Äé[28/11/2020, 4:12:09‚ÄØPM] Abdullah Bilwani: ‚Äéimage omitted ‚Äé[28/11/2020, 4:12:09‚ÄØPM] Abdullah Bilwani: ‚Äéimage omitted ‚Äé[28/11/2020, 4:12:10‚ÄØPM] Abdullah Bilwani: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "timestamp": "23/11/2020, 2:51:46‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm really sorry but I have a further math extra class till 3:45. Is it possible if we meet at 3:45? Then I'll join tuition a little late",
    "answer": "Yes it‚Äôll be on zoom",
    "timestamp": "25/01/2021, 7:57:31‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I think you got disconnected",
    "answer": "Abdullah pls come in and read some sample essays",
    "timestamp": "26/01/2021, 3:52:19‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do I have to read from UK applications 1 and 2?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "timestamp": "30/01/2021, 3:11:48‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi guys. For the summer internship I need to look for what specific bank department should I look for",
    "answer": "with the economist ideally",
    "timestamp": "2021-07-02T20:45:33",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "internships"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also do you guys think doing an online summer school is worth it",
    "answer": "Depends where and what program",
    "timestamp": "2021-09-02T17:45:40",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "And if so any idea on how that'll affect Oxbridge and ED",
    "answer": "Nothing can be confirmed",
    "timestamp": "27/04/2021, 11:58:30‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "And does the specific bank matter",
    "answer": "Not really as long as the learning takes place",
    "timestamp": "23/05/2021, 2:53:50‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "internships"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do I need to get a certificate after I'm done with the internship",
    "answer": "Preferably",
    "timestamp": "28/05/2021, 9:52:15‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "internships"
  },
  {
    "question": "So do you think I should still go to the bank just for experience and not get a certificate",
    "answer": "Yes that‚Äôs fine",
    "timestamp": "21/06/2021, 4:50:16‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "internships"
  },
  {
    "question": "The bank is syaing they'll still let me come for experience but for HR reasons they won't be able to officially acknowledge that I did an internship there",
    "answer": "Actually certificate is not as important",
    "timestamp": "21/06/2021, 6:31:12‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "internships"
  },
  {
    "question": "Like universities if I say I interned somewhere",
    "answer": "Unis don‚Äôt ask for certificates ever",
    "timestamp": "21/06/2021, 6:45:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "internships"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok perfect I'll continue with the bank then",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "21/06/2021, 6:57:44‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "internships"
  },
  {
    "question": "They've out me in the Islamic Banking corporate division",
    "answer": "cool",
    "timestamp": "22/06/2021, 1:20:09‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "internships"
  },
  {
    "question": "Signing up for August SAT",
    "answer": "Ok cool",
    "timestamp": "28/06/2021, 9:37:04‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "My school got full in the day so I'm doing KITE again",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "28/06/2021, 9:46:45‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do I need to give an ACT",
    "answer": "If you‚Äôre giving SAT then not really",
    "timestamp": "14/07/2021, 8:59:22‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Should I ask for 2 then or is 3 safer",
    "answer": "2 is fine",
    "timestamp": "2021-02-08T11:28:03",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also should I only stick to AS and A2 teachers or are o levels teachers fine",
    "answer": "only AS/A2",
    "timestamp": "2021-02-08T11:28:29",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "And does the subject matter or whoever will give me the best recommendation",
    "answer": "Subjects do make a difference, but obviously the recs have to be top notch, super personalised, and highlighting your academic, non academic skills/strengths, class participation, leadership",
    "timestamp": "2021-02-08T11:29:18",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ya sure",
    "answer": "Hey hoping you guys spoke yesterday",
    "timestamp": "2021-07-08T20:27:22",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© I don't have your email address. If you could send it I'll share the both the essays with you as well",
    "answer": "Rizwan.javed@dignosco.org",
    "timestamp": "14/09/2021, 1:52:58‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok will go through",
    "answer": "Abdullah when is your Oxford  test",
    "timestamp": "19/09/2021, 2:05:46‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "We will review",
    "answer": "Send me login I‚Äôll review tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "2021-01-10T21:53:38",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "UCAS Login Details: https://accounts.ucas.com/Account/Login Email: a.bilwani7061@kgs.edu.pk Password: Abdullah1* UCAS ID: 1612527565",
    "answer": "we still need to add a choice",
    "timestamp": "2021-01-10T21:58:10",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Commonapp Login Details Link to Login: https://apply.commonapp.org/login Email: a.bilwani7061@kgs.edu.pk Password: Abdullah1*",
    "answer": "Hey Adbullah has the UCAS app been submitted",
    "timestamp": "2021-11-10T11:18:41",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "They've sent it now",
    "answer": "Good luck",
    "timestamp": "15/10/2021, 11:23:30‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thanks",
    "answer": "also over the weekend pls complete the canaidan apps",
    "timestamp": "15/10/2021, 11:25:00‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Got an email from kings saying they recieved my application",
    "answer": "Cool",
    "timestamp": "19/10/2021, 2:12:47‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Now she just wants to talk about my extracurriculars and stuff probably for the counselor letter so I'll have a meeting with her about that in the evening",
    "answer": "Bro we need a solid peer rec",
    "timestamp": "20/10/2021, 12:54:16‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "extracurriculars"
  },
  {
    "question": "Like what would you guys want the sibling to write about",
    "answer": "What are your siblings ages etc",
    "timestamp": "20/10/2021, 8:56:44‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sisters 21. brothers 25",
    "answer": "Either can work tbh",
    "timestamp": "20/10/2021, 9:33:00‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Or if there's any general guidelines you guys have I'll just forward them to him",
    "answer": "Has to be personalised focusing on your character, leadership (best through an example or instance), your relationship etc, academic excellence, most importantly why you‚Äôd be such a great fit for Dartmouth",
    "timestamp": "21/10/2021, 12:03:07‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also, I have gone through your OUAC. Program choices and activities are still missing. If you haven't discussed the programs and university list with Rizwan please confirm so we can set up your meeting with him",
    "answer": "pls complete the activites @‚Å®Abdullah Bilwani‚Å©",
    "timestamp": "22/10/2021, 10:25:11‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "Done",
    "answer": "hello whats the status of the common app...are the activity sections complete...id like to review over the wekend [Image]",
    "timestamp": "22/10/2021, 1:26:52‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Put fire safety",
    "answer": "Once everything is added lemme know I‚Äôll review",
    "timestamp": "23/10/2021, 2:03:31‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Should I put this as just I got the training or as the introducing it for more workers thing",
    "answer": "Training plus introduction for workers",
    "timestamp": "23/10/2021, 2:33:59‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "extracurriculars"
  },
  {
    "question": "Everything's been added now",
    "answer": "Ok I will review between today/tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "23/10/2021, 2:56:05‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Did you guys get a chance to go through the Dartmouth supplements",
    "answer": "Not yet will do soon",
    "timestamp": "23/10/2021, 3:14:12‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes will share feedback and have a call with you",
    "answer": "abdullah we need to add more honors",
    "timestamp": "23/10/2021, 3:15:49‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Changed burque and acting descriptions and make honours lowercase",
    "answer": "Do as discussed",
    "timestamp": "24/10/2021, 2:01:09‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Cam I put a 9th grade math award",
    "answer": "Yea",
    "timestamp": "24/10/2021, 2:10:29‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "extracurriculars"
  },
  {
    "question": "Added honours so now 4 total",
    "answer": "Yes we put it in the college courses section",
    "timestamp": "24/10/2021, 2:51:16‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Added draft of first dartmouth supplement ‚Äé[26/10/2021, 12:39:00‚ÄØPM] Abdullah Bilwani: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "answer": "is there an essay for a second interest",
    "timestamp": "26/10/2021, 12:20:15‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "You can submit your resume if you want. Should I do that?",
    "answer": "Only if it has something extra",
    "timestamp": "26/10/2021, 12:44:05‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "internships"
  },
  {
    "question": "Common app also asks for sat score so in that I've written essay score",
    "answer": "What options are popping",
    "timestamp": "26/10/2021, 6:57:45‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "No March is the best wasnt any improvement after [Image]",
    "answer": "Yes so put it and was essay score better now ?",
    "timestamp": "26/10/2021, 7:19:12‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Didn't give essay after march",
    "answer": "Ok the one you‚Äôre ticking is ok",
    "timestamp": "26/10/2021, 7:21:48‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "And when",
    "answer": "As soon as you apply",
    "timestamp": "26/10/2021, 7:22:44‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok thanks",
    "answer": "I‚Äôm gonna do a final review tonight",
    "timestamp": "26/10/2021, 7:23:37‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Common app: a.bilwani7061@kgs.edu.pk Abdullah1*",
    "answer": "Cool",
    "timestamp": "26/10/2021, 7:24:20‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I just press review and submit on the my colleges tab right?",
    "answer": "Yes then it‚Äôll ask you to write down signature and to click on a bunch of terms etc",
    "timestamp": "27/10/2021, 12:02:28‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Congratulations! Yeah it‚Äôs one of their toughest degrees",
    "answer": "Amazing MA",
    "timestamp": "28/10/2021, 5:05:40‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes that works. [Image]",
    "answer": "Why is this coming",
    "timestamp": "29/10/2021, 12:42:35‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Haven't added individual entrepreneurship competitions, should I do that?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "timestamp": "31/10/2021, 2:34:08‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "extracurriculars"
  },
  {
    "question": "What colleges should I put for rottman commerce",
    "answer": "Univeristy college",
    "timestamp": "31/10/2021, 12:54:12‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Once you submit ouac please let us know",
    "answer": "Is it done ?",
    "timestamp": "31/10/2021, 3:16:32‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also what course would be good at Queen's",
    "answer": "only business",
    "timestamp": "2021-01-11T18:42:16",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "pls share the names i will tell u right away",
    "timestamp": "2021-01-11T18:44:36",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "They have a commerce one at the business school",
    "answer": "yes",
    "timestamp": "2021-01-11T18:46:22",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "But that's not business school",
    "answer": "yes business school is the best at Queens",
    "timestamp": "2021-01-11T18:46:58",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "also most competitive",
    "timestamp": "2021-01-11T18:47:21",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "üëçüèº",
    "answer": "cool",
    "timestamp": "2021-01-11T18:47:59",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Would I be able to apply for something else at st George's along side rotman incase it's easier or something",
    "answer": "you can apply to missisuaga",
    "timestamp": "2021-01-11T18:48:55",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok nvm I have to put a previous one",
    "answer": "You‚Äôll have to put sept 2022",
    "timestamp": "2021-01-11T18:54:50",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "It's saying because of citizenship I have to put a past date",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "2021-01-11T18:56:08",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ya it's one for st George",
    "answer": "stick 2 rotman",
    "timestamp": "2021-01-11T18:57:59",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also what could be a good safe option",
    "answer": "You can add the econ at York",
    "timestamp": "2021-01-11T19:03:36",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also I wanted to do either Guelph or Brock as a relatively safe option. Which do you guys think would be better?",
    "answer": "Brick",
    "timestamp": "2021-01-11T20:07:47",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "What program can I do at Waterloo",
    "answer": "Click on Wilfred Laurier uni",
    "timestamp": "2021-02-11T00:09:45",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is that normal",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "timestamp": "2021-03-11T18:01:58",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Suree [Image]",
    "answer": "Pls do it soon",
    "timestamp": "2021-06-11T16:06:40",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Interview is tomorrow at 2. Any tips?",
    "answer": "Who is it with ?",
    "timestamp": "19/11/2021, 7:05:48‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "internships"
  },
  {
    "question": "With someone named Faisal Mir",
    "answer": "ok I think prime focus should be to talk about your overall strengths, you should really go through Dartmouth website in detail",
    "timestamp": "19/11/2021, 7:09:48‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ensure you understand what was discussed in prompt 2 especially",
    "answer": "See what he does: you need to ask him some specific questions as well. Maybe some focused on how Dartmouth as a school for internationals, its strengths with recruitment etc",
    "timestamp": "19/11/2021, 7:14:03‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© what do you think ?",
    "answer": "San Diego snd Davis are both great and in top 40",
    "timestamp": "29/11/2021, 4:08:51‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok so Sam Diego Davis and Santa Barbara",
    "answer": "üëç [Image]",
    "timestamp": "29/11/2021, 4:17:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shoul i put for mathÿå add math and further in the UC app as the subject",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Hamda Khan Dignosco‚Å© pls guide on this question",
    "timestamp": "29/11/2021, 7:54:09‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "For maths Add mathematics 1 For add maths and further maths Select mathematics 2",
    "answer": "Thanks Hamda",
    "timestamp": "29/11/2021, 7:56:43‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will add a couple more activities tomorrow",
    "answer": "Pls complete activities also and I‚Äôll review after",
    "timestamp": "30/11/2021, 1:25:39‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "extracurriculars"
  },
  {
    "question": "I can add house sports for activities",
    "answer": "yes u can",
    "timestamp": "30/11/2021, 4:19:46‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "extracurriculars"
  },
  {
    "question": "You guys can review the app",
    "answer": "F1",
    "timestamp": "30/11/2021, 5:01:13‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok thanks",
    "answer": "Abdullah bro app looking great",
    "timestamp": "30/11/2021, 5:04:54‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Submitted uc app",
    "answer": "cool",
    "timestamp": "30/11/2021, 9:48:39‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "this one",
    "answer": "Pls share pdf of the UC app [Image] ‚Äé[01/12/2021, 3:27:28‚ÄØPM] Abdullah Bilwani: Review & Submit - UC applicationAbdullah.pdf ‚Ä¢ ‚Äé18 pages ‚Äédocument omitted",
    "timestamp": "30/11/2021, 11:44:09‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok sounds good",
    "answer": "Abdullah",
    "timestamp": "19/12/2021, 10:59:23‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ya sure",
    "answer": "Ok I‚Äôll call you today",
    "timestamp": "21/12/2021, 4:53:49‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok we have revised main essay so he should just wait for that",
    "answer": "Since these along with middlbury don‚Äôt have supps pls chat with him if he can put some of his UC essay for add info",
    "timestamp": "24/12/2021, 12:17:12‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes why not",
    "answer": "Abdullah we should be super aggressive imo",
    "timestamp": "24/12/2021, 12:18:31‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sounds good to me",
    "answer": "Have we sorted the add info query",
    "timestamp": "25/12/2021, 12:08:50‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yep",
    "answer": "i need login details",
    "timestamp": "2022-01-01T07:19:06",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Have sent all relevant docs",
    "answer": "Make sure SAT scores are sent through collegeboard",
    "timestamp": "2022-02-01T21:14:18",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Duke submitted",
    "answer": "Can you share screenshot of dashboard [Image] [Image] [Image]",
    "timestamp": "2022-04-01T23:46:48",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "SAT score sent to 10 unis that ive submitted as of now",
    "answer": "Ok and UCs as well yea?",
    "timestamp": "2022-05-01T16:59:34",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "All As",
    "answer": "üëå",
    "timestamp": "2022-10-01T11:45:04",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thank youüëçüèº [Image]",
    "answer": "Totally should",
    "timestamp": "2022-11-01T13:49:03",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok [Image]",
    "answer": "Cool you can reply and say sure if anything is needed you‚Äôll get in touch",
    "timestamp": "14/01/2022, 7:07:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also need to do this for UofT",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "22/01/2022, 7:45:53‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Need to send this to York after which I'll be able to fill in their supplements which are similar in format to UofT. Deadline for supplements is 2nd Feb.",
    "answer": "Ok [Image]",
    "timestamp": "22/01/2022, 7:58:40‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Colby sent this",
    "answer": "Ok we should def send something",
    "timestamp": "25/02/2022, 6:39:07‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "üëç",
    "answer": "Any uk update",
    "timestamp": "2022-02-03T19:29:51",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Does kings require English proficiency before giving an offer?",
    "answer": "It‚Äôs best to provide",
    "timestamp": "2022-09-03T23:25:24",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "So should I send you a English proficiency letter?",
    "answer": "They will only accept ielts",
    "timestamp": "2022-10-03T06:17:38",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Cause I haven't given IELTS",
    "answer": "Can [Image]",
    "timestamp": "2022-11-03T13:22:00",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "If I skip my English general exams does it show in my transcript?",
    "answer": "Yup [Image] [Image]",
    "timestamp": "13/03/2022, 2:10:11‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this like an extra year of foundation or is it regular undergrad",
    "answer": "It‚Äôs not a foundation",
    "timestamp": "17/03/2022, 9:56:56‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "But also your offer says you have been accepted into the business school which is great",
    "answer": "Yup",
    "timestamp": "17/03/2022, 10:01:16‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Great thanks [Image]",
    "answer": "Yup [Image]",
    "timestamp": "17/03/2022, 10:13:45‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thank you [Image]",
    "answer": "Complete the response form",
    "timestamp": "18/03/2022, 1:29:32‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok [Image]",
    "answer": "Ucla? [Image] [Image]",
    "timestamp": "19/03/2022, 6:36:41‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Rejected from Northwestern",
    "answer": "Middlebury",
    "timestamp": "26/03/2022, 6:54:28‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Rejected",
    "answer": "Any UK updates ?",
    "timestamp": "26/03/2022, 5:33:25‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Have LSE UCL and kings been sending offers and stuff",
    "answer": "None yet",
    "timestamp": "26/03/2022, 5:38:23‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "But the conditions aren't showing up [Image] [Image]",
    "answer": "Bro congrats you‚Äôre in",
    "timestamp": "25/04/2022, 2:34:15‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thanks ‚Äé[25/04/2022, 2:51:06‚ÄØPM] Abdullah Bilwani: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "answer": "great stuff",
    "timestamp": "25/04/2022, 2:50:57‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thank you",
    "answer": "You‚Äôll have to firm on ucas",
    "timestamp": "25/04/2022, 4:58:16‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "this is for UofT",
    "answer": "Ok not sure about this",
    "timestamp": "25/04/2022, 4:58:53‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Should I firm LSE and do the other thing for Warwick now?",
    "answer": "Let‚Äôs have a call in the morning",
    "timestamp": "27/04/2022, 3:36:07‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "When would I have to apply for us visa if I enroll",
    "answer": "Yea do it",
    "timestamp": "2022-01-05T18:53:26",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "It's offer is A*AA compared to AAA for lse",
    "answer": "If you are going to the UK, please make sure that you have taken appointment for TB test\". There are already delays so please ensure that this is done immediately\"",
    "timestamp": "2022-03-05T16:11:51",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "You can even call on this number but better to send the email and call both",
    "answer": "did u get the TB test",
    "timestamp": "2022-02-08T14:10:05",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I've emailed them to get one",
    "answer": "And ?",
    "timestamp": "2022-02-08T17:33:27",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hat gotten a response yet",
    "answer": "Pls chase",
    "timestamp": "2022-02-08T17:34:05",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is that a thing??",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "timestamp": "2022-08-08T18:47:20",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© can you confirm",
    "answer": "Already spoken to him",
    "timestamp": "2022-08-08T21:15:32",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Earliest test is august 20th",
    "answer": "Check IDP website they might have an earlier date",
    "timestamp": "2022-08-08T21:29:28",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéYou removed Saadia Gardezi [Image]",
    "answer": "Great",
    "timestamp": "2022-09-08T12:05:28",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Have sent them English grades also",
    "answer": "Ok cool",
    "timestamp": "2022-09-08T13:21:02",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Amazing! Good stuff",
    "answer": "Mubarak",
    "timestamp": "2022-11-08T10:32:48",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will lse update on ucas first?",
    "answer": "Wait for ucas track to be updated",
    "timestamp": "2022-11-08T10:44:29",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok üëç",
    "answer": "For UK visa app please note that you have to mention your last ten year travel history. Please make sure that you put your travel history down on a word document. There is a separate question on travel to UK. Separate question for travel to Europe, America and Australia Separate question for travel to rest of the world. You will need to specify date of entry and exit, country travelled  and number of days in that particular year. Please compile this data from 2012-2022 asap so you donot waste time while completing the visa app.",
    "timestamp": "2022-11-08T14:11:00",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Still waiting for lse to send more info",
    "answer": "solid [Image]",
    "timestamp": "18/08/2022, 12:36:20‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+1456632348",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéMessages and calls are end-to-end encrypted. Only people in this chat can read, listen to, or share them.",
    "answer": "Hey Abdullah we will use this group to communicate",
    "timestamp": "15/01/2025, 1:22:59‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "pirzadaabdulla@gmail.com ‚Äé[15/01/2025, 2:06:08‚ÄØPM] Abdullah Pirzada: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© would like you to meet him tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "15/01/2025, 2:05:48‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay thank u",
    "answer": "https://www.coursera.org/professional-certificates/google-data-analytics",
    "timestamp": "15/01/2025, 11:30:15‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I have tuition at 5 though",
    "answer": "Hey Abdullah",
    "timestamp": "17/01/2025, 8:20:20‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I will be there at 1:30 I need a little break",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "18/01/2025, 1:06:43‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I sent my points to @‚Å®Anicca Usmani‚Å©",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "19/01/2025, 2:22:50‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do u want me to get from Lyceum?",
    "answer": "I would honestly prefer if you can",
    "timestamp": "19/01/2025, 8:13:19‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What time should I come?",
    "answer": "Hey Abdullah for today I‚Äôll give you a call to discuss the recommendation situation and tomorrow you come in so we do the US apps",
    "timestamp": "21/01/2025, 1:33:13‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "So no need to come today right?",
    "answer": "No not today",
    "timestamp": "21/01/2025, 9:39:07‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do we have to call soon or can I call u in the evening as well",
    "answer": "i wanna discuss the recommendation bit",
    "timestamp": "21/01/2025, 1:08:10‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay but do we have to call now or can I call later",
    "answer": "later is ok",
    "timestamp": "21/01/2025, 1:09:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "We can call tomorrow or if ur up now we can call now",
    "answer": "Tomorrow is ok",
    "timestamp": "21/01/2025, 11:31:37‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "But I can only confirm time",
    "timestamp": "21/01/2025, 11:31:59‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What time tomorrow",
    "answer": "In the morning",
    "timestamp": "21/01/2025, 11:32:07‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay ‚Äé<This message was edited>",
    "answer": "Hey Abdullah",
    "timestamp": "21/01/2025, 11:32:20‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "If that‚Äôs fine",
    "answer": "Do 11:45 as I have to step out at 12:30",
    "timestamp": "22/01/2025, 10:49:38‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéYou added sheza adnan Lyceum",
    "answer": "@‚Å®sheza adnan Lyceum‚Å©",
    "timestamp": "22/01/2025, 12:17:40‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes [Image]",
    "answer": "Hi Abdullah",
    "timestamp": "22/01/2025, 12:39:22‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What time u want me to come?",
    "answer": "I‚Äôll confirm in the morning but tentatively 1ish",
    "timestamp": "24/01/2025, 5:48:43‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Not that long right",
    "answer": "Hopefully not",
    "timestamp": "24/01/2025, 7:57:23‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Because I have to reach boat club at 3:30 because of team photos",
    "answer": "Yea I think we won‚Äôt need more than 30 min",
    "timestamp": "24/01/2025, 8:11:18‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "If possible",
    "answer": "That‚Äôs ok",
    "timestamp": "25/01/2025, 12:02:39‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "Hey Abdullah",
    "timestamp": "25/01/2025, 12:13:09‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Let me check",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "27/01/2025, 4:15:17‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "When will we start for Iba?",
    "answer": "@‚Å®sheza adnan Lyceum‚Å©  can you check if app is open",
    "timestamp": "31/01/2025, 8:24:01‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I think 5/6?",
    "answer": "https://onlineadmission.iba.edu.pk/",
    "timestamp": "31/01/2025, 11:06:37‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I think that‚Äôs doable",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "31/01/2025, 11:07:58‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I can‚Äôt right now and it will take me a while to reach",
    "answer": "ok first call me when ur done",
    "timestamp": "31/01/2025, 4:24:47‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I just got free I will call soon [Image]",
    "answer": "Yes no issues",
    "timestamp": "31/01/2025, 5:39:35‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Though I think my cnic",
    "answer": "Take passport",
    "timestamp": "2025-07-02T23:21:09",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I got a 7 in ielts",
    "answer": "Great pls share the official rwsult [Image]",
    "timestamp": "2025-09-02T23:04:02",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "I have question outside of my 5 choices for UK did u make me apply anywhere else?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "timestamp": "2025-12-02T11:50:16",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Like how I got an offer from cardiff Durham etc",
    "answer": "yes those were direct",
    "timestamp": "2025-12-02T11:50:30",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "What about US?",
    "answer": "That too",
    "timestamp": "2025-12-02T11:50:48",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay ‚Äé[12/02/2025, 12:31:57‚ÄØPM] Abdullah Pirzada: ‚Äéimage omitted ‚Äé[12/02/2025, 12:32:05‚ÄØPM] Abdullah Pirzada: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "answer": "nice",
    "timestamp": "2025-12-02T11:54:50",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I haven‚Äôt gotten any offers from US",
    "answer": "May take some time",
    "timestamp": "17/02/2025, 9:25:39‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Does it usually take this much time?",
    "answer": "Yes can be even late March April [Image]",
    "timestamp": "17/02/2025, 9:48:02‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Like it‚Äôs an example",
    "answer": "Yes pls do respond",
    "timestamp": "26/02/2025, 9:47:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I come and we can sort all issue?",
    "answer": "Ok I‚Äôll call you either tomorrow or Saturday and we‚Äôll sort it",
    "timestamp": "26/02/2025, 11:42:10‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "https://admissions.iba.edu.pk/admission-schedule-fall2025.php",
    "timestamp": "27/02/2025, 12:36:34‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚Äé‚Äésheza adnan Lyceum changed their phone number to a new number. ‚ÄéTap to message or add the new number.",
    "answer": "hey",
    "timestamp": "18/06/2025, 2:22:40‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Now what will happen?",
    "answer": "Let‚Äôs wait a day and we will figure next steps iA",
    "timestamp": "2025-12-08T14:43:05",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "@‚Å®sheza adnan 2025‚Å© pls have a meeting with Abdullah for his UCAS",
    "timestamp": "2025-12-08T20:24:58",
    "student_name": "Abdullah Pirzada",
    "student_phone": "+2347470077",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hey folks, I haven't been feeling well for the last two nights. A couple of the symptoms that I'm showing are COVID related. I plan to get tested at noon today. It may not be wise for me to visit your office today. Would it be possible for us to conduct our session over zoom or meet?  I'm happy to come in or do the meeting online. Just let me know. Thank you!",
    "answer": "Hey Ahmed hope you feel better",
    "timestamp": "2022-03-02T11:46:08",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also please share gmat work we discussed once you are done [Image]",
    "answer": "Let‚Äôs discuss this jointly in next meeting also",
    "timestamp": "2022-05-02T17:31:35",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "*About applying to McGill on 15th March for the August ‚Äò22 start* I don‚Äôt think this will work out for me for the following reasons. - My baby will 8 months old at the time we would move to Montreal. It would be tough for my wife to manage alone with the baby given that I‚Äôll be away on campus for a chunk of the day. - We were hoping that I start an MBA program by the time Misha (our daughter) is 12 months old. Though child care in Canada starts for infants as young as 6 months old, we feel more comfortable sending her once she crosses the 1-year mark. Maryam is planning to register for the CHRP exam (HR Certification) this year. It will make her eligible for HR roles in Canada. So she plans to start working in Canada while Misha is at child care and I‚Äôm at school. - It‚Äôs looking like the GTA is going to be the place for me to apply. Maryam has around 5 cousins in the Toronto area. I think she is going to feel a lot better knowing that she has family around. Having said all this, I‚Äôm beginning to feel like the choice is coming down to 4 schools in the following order: Ivey, Schulich, Smith, McGill. While McGill‚Äôs program seems amazing, the late graduation date feels too far off. So this is where I am.",
    "answer": "Ok so schulich you‚Äôre looking for jan 2023?",
    "timestamp": "2022-05-02T18:28:58",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes [Image]",
    "answer": "Ok great",
    "timestamp": "2022-05-02T18:38:16",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi Sadaf when shall we meet?",
    "answer": "Ahmed I‚Äôll meet you since she‚Äôs outta city",
    "timestamp": "17/06/2022, 6:47:03‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "We could also do a phone call",
    "answer": "Cool can target for tomorrow ?",
    "timestamp": "17/06/2022, 7:39:31‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes of coiurse ‚Äé[17/06/2022, 1:17:04‚ÄØPM] Ahmed Tariq  Khan Lecole: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "answer": "yes hitting a 650 is what we should be aiming",
    "timestamp": "17/06/2022, 1:12:05‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I just took an official practice test and scored a 700 Q47 V38. Feeling good! I'm signing up for the 3rd",
    "answer": "Good stuff",
    "timestamp": "2022-01-08T13:25:57",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you want to take it again ?",
    "answer": "dont think theres any need to",
    "timestamp": "2022-03-08T14:14:15",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "I would like to apply to one or two schools in Europe as a backup option in case I don't get a Canadian student visa for any unforeseen reason. Just so I don't have all my eggs in one basket. Can you make some recommendations based on my application profile?",
    "answer": "We can look at Bocconi",
    "timestamp": "2022-04-08T11:30:47",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "HEC, Bocconi, IESE?",
    "answer": "Let‚Äôs look at HEC Bocconi",
    "timestamp": "2022-04-08T11:49:00",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "I think the process with Smith is to email them all the docs. [Image]",
    "answer": "Honestly I wouldn‚Äôt recommend a round 3 for schulich",
    "timestamp": "2022-06-08T12:55:17",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Video of our recent trek",
    "answer": "Very cool :)",
    "timestamp": "23/08/2022, 9:12:52‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "ok",
    "answer": "have reviewed the app",
    "timestamp": "26/08/2022, 12:20:03‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "So",
    "answer": "Should add this in awards",
    "timestamp": "27/08/2022, 12:47:41‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thanks. I had a great talk with her. Here are some notes I took. *Walk me through your MBA admission journey. What was your process, and how did you end up applying to and eventually choosing Cambridge?* She was thinking about MBA during pandemic. Thought about Cambridge because her husband recently did a masters from there. Rushed to make the whole MBA thing happen. Applied in the third round. Took GREs and applied very quickly. They would set you up with potential admits and a professor to break away in groups of four or five to talk and ask any questions you have. During the program she felt the depth of diversity. Many students aren‚Äôt native English speakers. Your study group gets close and students help each other out. *Can you think of any courses relevant for me given my goals? I‚Äôm particularly interested in digital transformation and education technology.* The program has concentrations in various areas. Digital transformation is one of them. The core courses are in finance and business. You only need to complete two electives for the concentration. *I would love to hear any insights about particular programs or student clubs outside of academics.* They have workshops like python and coding. SIG: special interest groups that are student-led. They put together events like speaker sessions. You can be as or less involved as you want. *Were you intimidated at all by other students or some of the professors? Any advice for me based on my application profile?* There is a desire for everyone to grow so you don‚Äôt feel too intimidated. Cambridge could be a really good place for you because it is a start-up environment. It has one of the most well-funded university incubator. You should talk about this in your essays and also mention Silicon Fen, which is a cluster of tech companies than are based in the Cambridge region. They attract a lot of talent and resources",
    "answer": "https://uwaterloo.ca/conrad-school-entrepreneurship-business/graduate-students/master-business-entrepreneurship-and-technology/courses",
    "timestamp": "22/09/2022, 10:32:51‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© just spoke to him and he highly recommends it (see fwd msgs above)",
    "answer": "I think we should consider applying for it",
    "timestamp": "23/09/2022, 12:35:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay!",
    "answer": "Hey Ahmed. should i create your profile for the waterloo program i had shared",
    "timestamp": "2022-01-10T12:21:18",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes please",
    "answer": "ok sure",
    "timestamp": "2022-03-10T15:58:27",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "The interview with Smith went well. They'll get back to me in 7-10 business days. I need better answers to the following questions: 1. Some of your peers would be as young as 22 years old; how would you feel about working in a team with them on an equal footing? 2. Would you consider working in Canada after graduation or are you certain about moving back to Pakistan to continue your business ventures? The career advancement interviewer pressed on the second question. I think they assumed I was planning to move to Canada, which is what they are used to with int'l apps from here.",
    "answer": "Ok what was your response to Q2?",
    "timestamp": "2022-05-10T19:07:37",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "career_guidance"
  },
  {
    "question": "Something along the lines of: _My interest lies in EdTech and if opportunities to enhance my knowledge and experience in these areas arise in Canada then I wouldn't be opposed to continuing on or taking part in  cross-border efforts in education and technology._",
    "answer": "Ok we can sorta work on improving this response a bit",
    "timestamp": "2022-05-10T19:20:26",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "career_guidance"
  },
  {
    "question": "I have an interview with Schulich on Thursday Oct 20",
    "answer": "Ok I think let‚Äôs discuss the interview",
    "timestamp": "14/10/2022, 10:34:25‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Monday at 4pm",
    "answer": "Let sadaf revert",
    "timestamp": "14/10/2022, 10:36:19‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thanks",
    "answer": "Extremely sorry guys but can we stick to 4? I have a school run which has changed to 3:15",
    "timestamp": "17/10/2022, 11:09:52‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hey are we on for 3:30 pm today?",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© can we stick to 4",
    "timestamp": "17/10/2022, 12:26:27‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hey these look good to me. @‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© please have a look as well",
    "answer": "The short term is all about the MBA at schulich, some specific courses within the MBA( right now the first part of the response is too generic) and then you can talk about the ‚Äúmy research into the financial and real estate sectors in Canada..‚Äù Ahmed the Quant skills as a weakness should not be stated. I think the last part where you talk about the data science certification, you can club in with the standardised testing towards the end Being an older grad: change bookish to academic knowledge and strengths. For leadership: you don‚Äôt have to say that leadership skills are a strength. Show it through conversation and examples which you have after the opening line which is fine.",
    "timestamp": "18/10/2022, 7:47:55‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© I need to come up with some good questions for the interviewer",
    "answer": "Ok the response is much much better",
    "timestamp": "19/10/2022, 6:51:39‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "career_guidance"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "How has schulich business school and the career Center been assisting recent graduates with work placements ? How do you see the role of technology in most work places in Canada ? I am very keen to learn more about climate sustainability and role of technology. I wanted to have your views on the same?",
    "timestamp": "19/10/2022, 7:57:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "She also congratulated me GMAT and said that I have a great score",
    "answer": "Amazing bro [Image] [Image]",
    "timestamp": "20/10/2022, 8:03:43‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi Sara, It was a pleasure speaking with you. Thank you for answering my questions about the Schulich MBA and sharing additional information through your follow-up email. The syllabi of the core courses are very insightful and provide the precise details I require. The courses look both exciting and challenging. I am thrilled to learn about the MaRS-Schulich partnership to scale climate innovations! The Coalition Fellowship is something I would love to pursue, given the opportunity and my workload during the MBA program. The most valuable outcome I can see from being a Coalition Fellow is the network I will build with stakeholders across industries who, like me, care deeply about saving our planet. I attended Experience Schulich last week, which was an interactive and informative experience. I plan to attend the MBA Alumni Panel on November 16 to learn more about the program and life after graduating directly from alums. And I have also registered for Professor Rungtusanatham's master class scheduled for next Tuesday (October 25). Thank you again for sharing these details with me. I will be sure to contact you should I have any further questions. Kind Regards, Ahmed",
    "answer": "looking good",
    "timestamp": "21/10/2022, 3:44:23‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "ok",
    "answer": "Any update from schulich ?",
    "timestamp": "25/10/2022, 4:23:43‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Not yet",
    "answer": "Aight",
    "timestamp": "25/10/2022, 9:41:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Right now I'm sitting in on a master class by Professor M. Johnny Rungtusanatham, program lead for the Digital Transformation Specialization",
    "answer": "Ok solid",
    "timestamp": "25/10/2022, 10:09:47‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "Amazing! Congratulations. Please share acceptance [Image]",
    "answer": "Bro",
    "timestamp": "2022-03-11T08:50:53",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "After visa.com üòÇ",
    "answer": ":)",
    "timestamp": "2022-03-11T09:27:38",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi @‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© I think its best to focus on Rotman and McGill for the Jan deadlines. I'm going to go ahead and accept Schulich for now and put down the deposit.",
    "answer": "I don‚Äôt think McGill in terms of business school is remotely as good as schulich",
    "timestamp": "2022-08-11T10:32:10",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "I know man I feel the same way. But the rankings...",
    "answer": "Also in terms of the job market etc",
    "timestamp": "2022-08-11T10:33:14",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes - Toronto would be a better area vs Montreal.",
    "answer": "for sure",
    "timestamp": "2022-08-11T10:35:16",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "No news on Cambridge. Really odd.",
    "answer": "did they specify any date for results [Image]",
    "timestamp": "2022-08-11T10:37:15",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Nice!!! Congratulations",
    "answer": "Solid",
    "timestamp": "2022-08-11T14:54:26",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes! I'm excited but also nervous.",
    "answer": "we have time",
    "timestamp": "2022-08-11T15:05:22",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Feedback from my wife's cousin who got in but ended up at INSEAD. I'm also reaching out to another friend from Syracuse who just graduated from Judge. She helped with the essay brainstorming too.",
    "answer": "Ok cool",
    "timestamp": "2022-09-11T17:37:02",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://www.jbs.cam.ac.uk/insight/2021/an-invitation-to-interview/ [Image] [Image]",
    "answer": "I‚Äôll call ya tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "2022-09-11T17:40:33",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Please keep these confidential. She told me so.",
    "answer": "Yea for sure",
    "timestamp": "2022-10-11T10:20:14",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm going to go ahead and put the $3,000 deposit for Schulich and accept their offer today. SInce it's the only offer in hand, I think it's best to hold on to it for now.",
    "answer": "yes do that for sure",
    "timestamp": "2022-10-11T12:27:26",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm really praying for a Rotman/Cambridge offer.",
    "answer": "Hey",
    "timestamp": "2022-10-11T12:27:42",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "But they need a lot of work",
    "answer": "Will help you",
    "timestamp": "15/11/2022, 10:17:50‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes done [Image]",
    "answer": "Ok will have a look",
    "timestamp": "15/11/2022, 10:31:08‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hey stuck at the dentist will be over as soon as I'm out of here",
    "answer": "ok i gotta be out somwehere at 4:30",
    "timestamp": "17/11/2022, 3:41:23‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "draft of message to Michael Birdsall, an EdTech entrepreneur who graduated from CJBS, consulted with Cambridge on the Cambridge Analytica scandal, tutored and consulting over 1,000 MBA candidates, and recently moved back to Cambridge to start his third company.",
    "answer": "Pls send",
    "timestamp": "18/11/2022, 12:32:59‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "He got back to me. I'm speaking with him on Tuesday at 2:30 PM.",
    "answer": "‚ù§Ô∏è",
    "timestamp": "18/11/2022, 6:44:39‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© I had a wonderful conversation with Michael Birdsall. The best part of it was that he had the SAME interviewer and knew the professor well. So I got some good insight on what to expect. [Image]",
    "answer": "Great I‚Äôm driving will have a look soon [Image]",
    "timestamp": "23/11/2022, 10:43:46‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© I'm travelling on Saturday for four days. Could we meet tomorrow to discuss these responses?",
    "answer": "Ok let‚Äôs do 3:15 tomorrow‚Äô",
    "timestamp": "24/11/2022, 7:22:01‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© I wanted to write a note to Conrad Chua (Executive Director of the MBA) thanking him for mentioning Michael Birdsall, whom I was able to connect with and gain extremely useful insights about the Cambridge MBA, alumni, and Cambridge community as a whole. What do you think?",
    "answer": "Yea sure",
    "timestamp": "30/11/2022, 5:49:18‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also - I'm trying to break all my responses using the 'rule of 3' so that I can remember them and also make them easier and structured for the interviewer.",
    "answer": "Ok that makes sense. Do that and let‚Äôs sit",
    "timestamp": "30/11/2022, 5:52:40‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "I've broken all my responses into sections that I can easily pop up if I want to talk more about them [Image] [Image]",
    "answer": "Threw him off like how?",
    "timestamp": "2022-02-12T19:05:47",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hello Conrad - I just wanted to say thanks for hosting the session with Prof Loch and Mr Stockley. My key takeaways were information about the \"dark triad of personality traits\" Stockley shared with the group and Prof Loch's thoughts on how neoclassical economics legitimises Machiavellianism. Both points are worth considering as we welcome the world's first trillionaires. Also - thank you tremendously for mentioning Michael Birdsall to me. I had an opportunity to connect with Mike, who was gracious enough to speak to me over Zoom last week. He shared his experiences as a Judge MBA student and consultant for Cambridge; and how Cambridge's ecosystem benefited him in becoming a successful entrepreneur. He mentioned that his first investor was from the Cambridge Angels Network, which created credibility for his company, gaining him more investors from London. And he shared how he found his earliest employees through his college and the university community. Hearing first-hand from someone who has been a part of Judge and Cambridge from various perspectives confirms my belief that Cambridge fosters the entrepreneurial spirit within Judge and the larger community.",
    "answer": "I don‚Äôt think you need to elaborate on specifics about the convo with Birdsall.",
    "timestamp": "2022-03-12T14:21:00",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hello Conrad - I just wanted to say thanks for hosting the session with Prof Loch and Mr Stockley. My key takeaways were information about the \"dark triad of personality traits\" Stockley shared with the group and Prof Loch's thoughts on how neoclassical economics legitimises Machiavellianism. Both points are worth considering as we welcome the world's first trillionaires. Also - thank you tremendously for mentioning Michael Birdsall to me. I had an opportunity to connect with Mike, who was gracious enough to speak to me over Zoom last week. Hearing first-hand from someone who has been a part of Judge and Cambridge from various perspectives confirms my belief that Cambridge fosters the entrepreneurial spirit within Judge and the larger community.",
    "answer": "A thank you for the intro is good enough",
    "timestamp": "2022-03-12T14:24:18",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I got a shout out on yesterday's session. Conrad called it \"the million dollar question\"",
    "answer": "Also be prepared to be thrown off :)",
    "timestamp": "2022-03-12T14:25:19",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I know. I think there may be a point where I'll have to go with my instincts and gut during the interview.",
    "answer": "Yea but as long as you cover stuff within the specifics we‚Äôve discussed",
    "timestamp": "2022-03-12T14:25:54",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "career_guidance"
  },
  {
    "question": "He's a Senior Advisor of ESG at HSBC",
    "answer": "I think you can bring in your trekking angle and how you have been exposed to some stuff during the treks, maybe you can talk about some specific sessions you have had with locals and maybe some local ngos who are working on climate issues maybe around north pakistan",
    "timestamp": "2022-03-12T14:29:10",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Things like watching glaciers melting, rivers flowing faster than before, children and pregnant women getting new diseases and crops for the whole year destroyed. [Image]",
    "answer": "Currently driving will have a look in an hour",
    "timestamp": "2022-03-12T14:42:50",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "************Question 1************ Coming from a Pakistan background where we face several catastrophic scenarios. The recent floods, rising inflation, currency depreciation, and political instability have affected us badly. With the floods alone: 1. 8 million more people pushed under the poverty line 2. Loss in productivity by 2% of our GDP (around $7 billion) 3. The World Bank estimates damages of over $15 billion **How can scenario building and reverse stress testing be conducted more effectively on a macro level to deal with some of the catastrophic scenarios we face today?** ************Question 2************ With the recent FTX collapse, cryptocurrencies are under scrutiny; but I firmly believe that digital currencies are here to stay and will prosper in the long-term. We are already seeing traction in accepting the technology in countries like El Salvador and Lebanon. **How do you feel different economies will absorb the decentralisation of currencies through cryptocurrencies like government coins, stablecoins, and algorithmic currencies over the coming decades?**",
    "answer": "Catastrophic natural and economics scenarios",
    "timestamp": "2022-04-12T13:24:14",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "research_opportunities"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://www.cam.ac.uk/research/news/new-industry-collaboration-to-study-cryptocurrencies-and-other-digital-assets",
    "answer": "I‚Äôm gonna read this but sounds really interesting",
    "timestamp": "2022-04-12T16:12:57",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "research_opportunities"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this okay for Sustainability?",
    "answer": "yea sounds good",
    "timestamp": "2022-05-12T13:42:04",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hey the interview was pleasant but I wasn't able to get to MOST of my answers. He barely asked me any standard questions. 1. Where do you see Pakistan and it's role in the future? 2. Tell me about a time when you had to let someone go or fire someone. 3. Why didn't you apply to Harvard? 4. What has been something big that caused you to change your perspective over the past 12 months?",
    "answer": "hmm",
    "timestamp": "2022-05-12T16:36:58",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "career_guidance"
  },
  {
    "question": "On the bright side, when I brought up family: he mentioned that there is some very good support for families here because you will be very busy with the MBA. He recommended Churchill, which is his college, as one of the colleges that welcome and support families. And he said that I should network with alumni and the university to learn more about this.",
    "answer": "what did you respond for Q1",
    "timestamp": "2022-05-12T16:38:21",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Coming from a Pakistan background where we face several catastrophic scenarios. The recent floods, rising inflation, currency depreciation, and political instability have affected us badly. With the floods alone: 1. 8 million more people pushed under the poverty line 2. Loss in productivity by 2% of our GDP (around $7 billion) 3. The World Bank estimates damages of over $15 billion So my question is: **On a macro level, how can scenario building and reverse stress testing be conducted more effectively to deal with some of the catastrophic and economic scenarios we face today?**",
    "answer": "what did he say",
    "timestamp": "2022-05-12T16:38:42",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "research_opportunities"
  },
  {
    "question": "I talked about how we've been hit very badly and that Pakistan may not make up too much ground over the next decade unless there is a drastic shift in policies towards increasing our productivity in manufacturing and agriculture. I also mentioned that the IT sector is growing and that perhaps Pakistan can take away some of the market from India in terms of the low hanging fruits of IT outsourcing while India moves to higher level tech.",
    "answer": "good",
    "timestamp": "2022-05-12T16:40:22",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "He gave a very detailed answer and said that his unit is a smaller shop that does the research but doesn't have the resources to go out and speak to every company. He also mentioned that the main problem is that most governments are temporary so their policies are not long-term. But countries like Saudi Arabia can think long-term because the government doesn't change.",
    "answer": "fair",
    "timestamp": "2022-05-12T16:41:50",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "In the end he had to jump into another interview because we were a minute over. So he said that what'll happen is that he will share his feedback with the admissions committee, who will inform me that the feedback has been received - this should happen in about a week. And he said that I would hear back with a decision a little after that and if I don't then I should reach out",
    "answer": "when do u hear back",
    "timestamp": "2022-05-12T16:44:02",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "I feel like I could have hit some more of the items we had planned. I didn't get a chance to talk about trekking or sustainability which I'm bummed about. But he was just hitting me with unconventional and specific questions. I was only able to redirect 2 of his questions to my responses. But the rest I was on my feet. And to be honest I can't say how I did on those because he actually had me thinking on my feet and not focused on anything else but my own thought process.",
    "answer": "what did u say on the harvard ques",
    "timestamp": "2022-05-12T16:45:42",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "interview_feedback"
  },
  {
    "question": "I want to write a thank you email to the professor. Will share a draft shortly.",
    "answer": "sure",
    "timestamp": "2022-05-12T17:14:00",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "1. Thank you 2. Two more events that changed my perspective this year were the floods where I brought NGOs to Sindh and the trekking where I helped save a life. 3. Thanks for answering my question and all the great work the Center of Risk Studies is doing. 4. I hope to continue further discussions with you at Cambridge.",
    "answer": "i mean you shouldnt be answering a question",
    "timestamp": "2022-05-12T17:16:54",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Dear Professor Ralph, Thank you for our insightful conversations during my interview and for taking the time to answer my question on strategies needed to create awareness around climate action. I wish to continue our discussions on shaping a brighter landscape for education in developing countries - hopefully at Cambridge. Sincerely, Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "answer": "cool",
    "timestamp": "2022-05-12T17:28:51",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "We just have Rotman and McGill left now. I've started to work on their essays",
    "answer": "let‚Äôs hope for the best",
    "timestamp": "2022-06-12T12:28:39",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thanks man. I really appreciate all the help and guidance so far! üôèüôèüôè",
    "answer": "Sure will do soon",
    "timestamp": "2022-06-12T12:31:48",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "career_guidance"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© I just had a though I wanted to run by you. Since I didn't get a chance to talk about trekking and flood relief work, I was wondering if it would be a good idea to post two separate stories on my LinkedIn about my experience and efforts along with some powerful photos. I have noticed through LinkedIn Premium that Conrad and other Cambridge folks view my profile. So it might be worth a shot to post and hope it catches their eye and hopefully makes an impression. Thoughts?",
    "answer": "Yea",
    "timestamp": "2022-07-12T20:13:58",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "extracurriculars"
  },
  {
    "question": "should I post all of these pics with the post or just one or two?",
    "answer": "No harm in putting all [Image] [Image] [Image]",
    "timestamp": "2022-08-12T09:44:37",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "extracurriculars"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hey @‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© @‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© no word yet form Cambridge.",
    "answer": "Did they specify a date",
    "timestamp": "15/12/2022, 12:40:25‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "No but I spoke to one guy who got the admit. He said he got it 10 days after his interview. Today is the 10th day for me.",
    "answer": "Hmm",
    "timestamp": "15/12/2022, 12:41:19‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "ü§ûüèº [Image]",
    "answer": "hmmm",
    "timestamp": "15/12/2022, 12:43:34‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I just need to get the same score I got in my last official practice test and I'm golden",
    "answer": "Yes iA",
    "timestamp": "20/12/2022, 3:33:34‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "do you know any quant tutors who come highly recommended?",
    "answer": "Honestly I don‚Äôt",
    "timestamp": "20/12/2022, 4:05:03‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "career_guidance"
  },
  {
    "question": "I can ask some people i knowwho took the gmat",
    "answer": "yea makes sense. i think best strategty would be to get an online quant tutor",
    "timestamp": "20/12/2022, 4:06:50‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "career_guidance"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this okay?",
    "answer": "Hello Ms Brierley, I am extremely excited at the possibility of attending The Judge Business School this coming fall. This is to confirm that I will be retaking the GMAT test to satisfy the Admission Committee's percentile requirements. I intend to sit for the gmat soon and will keep you updated. I wish the Admissions Team happy holidays and a very happy new year! Warm regards, Ahmed",
    "timestamp": "21/12/2022, 6:13:06‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok sent",
    "answer": "Waiting for that gmat score :)",
    "timestamp": "21/12/2022, 8:24:52‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hey @‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© @‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© we have 3 days till the Rotman deadline and McGill is 2 days after that. Rotman 13th Jan McGill 15th Jan Can we finalize my application so I can submit? I will then inform my references to submit their feedback too.",
    "answer": "ahmed waiting on the essays so we can cut to word limits",
    "timestamp": "2023-10-01T12:42:44",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Let me know if you need access",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Ahmed Tariq  Khan Lecole‚Å© I‚Äôve read the rotman essay. The first two points are good and need minor changes etc which won‚Äôt take much time. Can we use something else versus floods. Firstly I feel the impact from our end is minimal and not sustainable as well. Any other initiatives you may have done , pls highlight and we can see if we can switch with the floods section",
    "timestamp": "2023-10-01T18:33:47",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you still think we should remove the floods piece then maybe we can add some text on establishing and running the Pakistan Education Council. I could dig up a photo of the signing ceremony, it's not as powerful but maybe the story could be told well.",
    "answer": "then we need to make the story better",
    "timestamp": "2023-11-01T11:31:30",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hey can we discuss Rotman tomorrow at any point during the day? I need to submit it tomorrow night.",
    "answer": "Yea we can do rn",
    "timestamp": "2023-12-01T18:41:52",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tomorrow morning is best",
    "answer": "Cool",
    "timestamp": "2023-12-01T18:42:24",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "McGill closed ?",
    "timestamp": "2023-12-01T18:45:08",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© calling you in 15?",
    "answer": "Cool",
    "timestamp": "13/01/2023, 10:25:05‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© I've edited the Rotman essay. Please have a look. https://docs.google.com/document/d/1-WJlD6SflY_sMFW1UicV3Joys66mWiTm24Yd3WhWnA0/edit?usp=sharing",
    "answer": "grant edit access",
    "timestamp": "13/01/2023, 12:46:23‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "done",
    "answer": "made the changes. pls see",
    "timestamp": "13/01/2023, 2:44:45‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay all set I just editted it slightly to bring it to 500 words. I think we're good",
    "answer": "yup",
    "timestamp": "13/01/2023, 2:56:47‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thanks. Both McGill and Rotman are submitted. ü§û",
    "answer": "Great",
    "timestamp": "14/01/2023, 11:41:15‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "But good news is that I took another diagnostic on Saturday and got a 47 in quant. I need 45+ for Cambridge.",
    "answer": ":)",
    "timestamp": "30/01/2023, 7:21:18‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Just sent it to Cambridge through mba.com along with a follow up email to their adcom",
    "answer": "üëå [Image]",
    "timestamp": "22/02/2023, 10:46:21‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Amazing!! Congratulations. Soo happy for you",
    "answer": "üëåüëåüëå",
    "timestamp": "24/02/2023, 6:29:26‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Guys I'm in absolute shock. This journey took us a year of so much work. And these last two months working to improve my score have been exhausting. I still can't believe it. Thank you so much for believing in me and walking me every step of the way. You guys are miracle workers! Thank you!! üôèüôèüôè",
    "answer": "so happy it‚Äôs worked out man :)",
    "timestamp": "24/02/2023, 8:52:10‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Not sure if you have sent already buy if you could change the name to Ahmed khan from Ahmed Tariq that would be great",
    "answer": "Just sent to 2/3 ppl. Will change :)",
    "timestamp": "24/02/2023, 11:47:33‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hey guys my nephew Azzam (15) is visiting from Bahrain where he's currently sitting for GCSEs at St Christopher's. I wanted to bring him and his dad in for an introduction. Does Monday work?",
    "answer": "Yea cool",
    "timestamp": "2023-03-03T17:05:52",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Good news, guys. I had applied to three colleges in order of preference: Pembroke, Queen's, and Darwin. And I'm happy to share that I got into my first choice ü•≥",
    "answer": "Amazing man :)",
    "timestamp": "16/03/2023, 6:59:12‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ahmed Tariq Khan",
    "student_phone": "+8793116355",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Feedback!!",
    "answer": "Hey Alina will revert this week",
    "timestamp": "18/06/2018, 11:35:27‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéYou added Shehryar Sarwat US",
    "answer": "Hey Alina",
    "timestamp": "17/08/2018, 8:55:30‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi Alina. Can you do 11:45 am tomorrow?",
    "answer": "Alina pls confirm",
    "timestamp": "17/08/2018, 9:27:52‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéSahrish Dignosco left",
    "answer": "Hi Alina please discuss the PS related stuff here",
    "timestamp": "18/08/2018, 5:45:41‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéYou added Momina Iftikhar Counselling",
    "answer": "David from Durham university will be doing a session at our office on Monday at 3pm. Please attend",
    "timestamp": "24/08/2018, 3:46:37‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hey, I have testweek this week so I‚Äôll be really busy!",
    "answer": "Ok let‚Äôs meet once you‚Äôre free",
    "timestamp": "2018-08-09T16:15:51",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Early",
    "answer": "Why you‚Äôre giving in Nov right",
    "timestamp": "24/09/2018, 9:52:54‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "But deadline is Nov 1st",
    "answer": "Yeah we can send sat scores the day they come out through a rush report",
    "timestamp": "24/09/2018, 9:53:16‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok for sure?",
    "answer": "So if the sat 2 scores come out on Nov 22",
    "timestamp": "24/09/2018, 9:53:57‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "For subject test",
    "answer": "2",
    "timestamp": "24/09/2018, 9:59:51‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you guys have a meltzer grammar book lying around",
    "answer": "Let me check",
    "timestamp": "28/09/2018, 4:19:44‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "alright, let me know please (:",
    "answer": "You can take it",
    "timestamp": "28/09/2018, 6:39:51‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "thaaank you, I‚Äôm coming by tomorrow",
    "answer": "Cool",
    "timestamp": "28/09/2018, 7:04:13‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://www.britishcouncil.pk/sites/default/files/tsaoxf_form_2018.doc",
    "answer": "You need to do both?",
    "timestamp": "30/09/2018, 1:23:45‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "So",
    "answer": "https://www.ox.ac.uk/admissions/undergraduate/courses-listing/history?wssl=1",
    "timestamp": "30/09/2018, 2:05:25‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Not just history",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "30/09/2018, 2:08:05‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "yeah I can‚Äôt figure out the forms though",
    "answer": "The tsa doesn‚Äôt specify code for history and eco",
    "timestamp": "30/09/2018, 2:09:08‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Then you submit payment challan  along with form at British council I believe [Image]",
    "answer": "It‚Äôs written on the form",
    "timestamp": "30/09/2018, 2:28:07‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "!!",
    "answer": "It‚Äôs probably because most ppl apply for any one of the subjects",
    "timestamp": "2018-01-10T22:01:35",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "oxford doesn‚Äôt offer econ",
    "answer": "Eco and mgt",
    "timestamp": "2018-01-10T22:16:41",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "So I should stick to my chosen course na?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "timestamp": "2018-01-10T22:17:26",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "Like not rewrite my whole ps for ppe or econ mgt or something",
    "answer": "History and eco is great imo",
    "timestamp": "2018-01-10T22:17:45",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "nvm",
    "answer": "Can you also check college wise acceptance for eco and mgt",
    "timestamp": "2018-01-10T22:19:06",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "History",
    "answer": "Also econ and mgt",
    "timestamp": "2018-01-10T22:20:04",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also very boring tbh",
    "answer": "Yea but what about only history",
    "timestamp": "2018-01-10T22:20:53",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôll have to change my ps",
    "answer": "Lots have over 24 percent",
    "timestamp": "2018-01-10T22:21:44",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pages doesn‚Äôt open on my laptop",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Alina Salahuddin‚Å©",
    "timestamp": "2018-08-10T15:28:01",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sure",
    "answer": "Alina pls send doc in a word file",
    "timestamp": "2018-09-10T22:57:44",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Received?",
    "answer": "Yes thx",
    "timestamp": "2018-10-10T00:20:30",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Haven‚Äôt received a confirmation email yet",
    "answer": "That‚Äôs strange",
    "timestamp": "2018-12-10T12:57:24",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Got an offer! [Image]",
    "answer": "Wow",
    "timestamp": "2018-12-10T22:35:18",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "internships"
  },
  {
    "question": "Choice",
    "answer": "I will finalise activities",
    "timestamp": "18/10/2018, 11:36:55‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "can i get a sat2 lit book?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "timestamp": "24/10/2018, 11:30:25‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also I‚Äôm here",
    "answer": "Hey",
    "timestamp": "24/10/2018, 4:53:11‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi, not doing Canada",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "27/10/2018, 4:44:54‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hey guys",
    "answer": "Hello",
    "timestamp": "30/10/2018, 12:04:54‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Got my ucl offer",
    "answer": "Amazing",
    "timestamp": "30/10/2018, 12:05:29‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Loading*",
    "answer": "great stuff [Image]",
    "timestamp": "30/10/2018, 12:06:01‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Congrats!!",
    "answer": "AAA?",
    "timestamp": "30/10/2018, 12:06:45‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "In December",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "2018-12-11T17:45:30",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "(Need to apply now since I need my passport for December sat)",
    "answer": "So apply for the priority visa",
    "timestamp": "13/11/2018, 7:23:10‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ali was saying he already got a letter",
    "answer": "Ali who?",
    "timestamp": "13/11/2018, 7:31:49‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Apna",
    "answer": "What letter ?",
    "timestamp": "13/11/2018, 7:32:06‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "To apply with",
    "answer": "has he gotten an interview call?",
    "timestamp": "13/11/2018, 7:33:22‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Nope",
    "answer": "Then how would they issue a letter",
    "timestamp": "13/11/2018, 7:34:41‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "no it was a different sort of email- I tried that too but my college hasn‚Äôt responded. Can I apply with my confirmation email from the college",
    "answer": "have you been to UK before ?",
    "timestamp": "13/11/2018, 7:36:06‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yeah but my visa expired just a few months ago",
    "answer": "So just reapply for visit visa",
    "timestamp": "13/11/2018, 7:38:37‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Like",
    "answer": "Yea why won‚Äôt it work",
    "timestamp": "13/11/2018, 7:39:05‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Chances of getting rejected ..?",
    "answer": "Apply for priority visa",
    "timestamp": "13/11/2018, 7:39:16‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "ok I‚Äôll tell my dad then",
    "answer": "Because if you just apply with a confirmation they might refuse and ask to bring invitation",
    "timestamp": "13/11/2018, 7:39:46‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sure",
    "answer": "Any update from oxford",
    "timestamp": "13/11/2018, 7:55:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Have they sent any emails yet?",
    "answer": "Yea Nameera got it",
    "timestamp": "20/11/2018, 10:05:50‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "This week I think",
    "answer": "You can actually call the college and find out when they‚Äôll be sending an update regarding interview",
    "timestamp": "20/11/2018, 10:07:17‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Has Lse‚Äôs first round started?",
    "answer": "Hmm haven‚Äôt heard ppl get emails yet",
    "timestamp": "20/11/2018, 10:08:25‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Oh alright",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "20/11/2018, 10:09:09‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hahahaha",
    "answer": "Also did you give sat 2",
    "timestamp": "20/11/2018, 10:09:24‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "No prep",
    "answer": "Hmmm",
    "timestamp": "20/11/2018, 10:09:26‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Not thinking about the us",
    "answer": "and....",
    "timestamp": "20/11/2018, 10:09:41‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "And 720 lit",
    "answer": "Oh",
    "timestamp": "20/11/2018, 10:10:04‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "it was 2 days after my ox tests so I spent like a day trying to study",
    "answer": "you‚Äôre really not thinking of The Usüò¨",
    "timestamp": "20/11/2018, 10:10:23‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "My passports at the visa office",
    "answer": "Please give",
    "timestamp": "20/11/2018, 10:10:54‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yeah I have no issues in going to sit for it",
    "answer": "So we can target some top schools atleast",
    "timestamp": "20/11/2018, 10:11:10‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Unis don‚Äôt look at gpr",
    "answer": "Call me later today",
    "timestamp": "20/11/2018, 11:01:10‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "When is it?",
    "answer": "Awesome",
    "timestamp": "23/11/2018, 1:32:00‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "That kind of thing",
    "answer": "Can we put her through to someone studying history at oxford? @‚Å®Ata Rehman‚Å©",
    "timestamp": "27/11/2018, 5:11:16‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What time would be good",
    "answer": "Come at 4",
    "timestamp": "21/12/2018, 12:03:16‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Guys",
    "answer": ". [Image]",
    "timestamp": "21/12/2018, 8:49:07‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéYou added Mahnoor farooq",
    "answer": "Alina please ask Mahnoor",
    "timestamp": "21/12/2018, 8:50:38‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I can‚Äôt find a section for extra curriculars [Image]",
    "answer": "I think you can‚Äôt put activities in this app",
    "timestamp": "21/12/2018, 8:51:31‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "extracurriculars"
  },
  {
    "question": "thanks (:",
    "answer": "Amazing",
    "timestamp": "15/03/2019, 10:20:26‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alina Salahuddin",
    "student_phone": "+9323761832",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéYou created group ‚ÄúAlizeh Grad apps‚Äù",
    "answer": "Alizeh we will use this group to communicate",
    "timestamp": "25/09/2024, 12:04:15‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/12iPnJcU62yhEYdWMcLO0bj9UM7zVpSvO4jbnEqATVgs/edit?gid=0#gid=0 [Image]",
    "answer": "Alizeh also share the google sheet",
    "timestamp": "25/09/2024, 7:23:42‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Shared it",
    "answer": "Thanks",
    "timestamp": "26/09/2024, 9:53:35‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://www.kcl.ac.uk/study/postgraduate-taught/courses/economics-and-policy-msc",
    "answer": "Nopes we‚Äôre good with that",
    "timestamp": "26/09/2024, 6:28:32‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Alizeh Kazmi Grad Lead‚Å© I have added rehab from our team to this group and she will be helping you with your personal statement. We will be starting with the LSE one first",
    "answer": "Alizeh",
    "timestamp": "28/09/2024, 1:03:27‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yeah about that just one confirmation needed from your end, can I expect the person to know python?",
    "answer": "i mean these kids are high schoolers",
    "timestamp": "29/09/2024, 10:02:42‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "internships"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okie the let‚Äôs stick to research oriented work",
    "answer": "maybe we can suggest and look at options with/without coding",
    "timestamp": "29/09/2024, 10:03:46‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "research_opportunities"
  },
  {
    "question": "And if the person knows python then we can do a descriptive analysis of the first digital census data released by PBS",
    "answer": "Ok I‚Äôll finalise which way we‚Äôre going later today",
    "timestamp": "30/09/2024, 10:47:50‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "research_opportunities"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôll create drafts about the kind of work I have in my mind for the three ideas for more clarity and send them by second half",
    "answer": "Solid [Image]",
    "timestamp": "30/09/2024, 10:52:07‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "research_opportunities"
  },
  {
    "question": "We discussed there would be a certain way you would be informing me on how to approach them",
    "answer": "Hey Alizeh",
    "timestamp": "2024-01-10T21:03:44",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I can come to you tomorrow for discussion too",
    "answer": "Yes well finalise this in a day or so",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-10T21:51:56",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "This works too, could do it around 5:30 pm",
    "answer": "Let‚Äôs do morning pls ?",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-10T21:53:30",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Around what time?",
    "answer": "I‚Äôll message and coordinate a time with you in the morning, but I‚Äôll do something which works for you",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-10T21:54:03",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôll download that no issue",
    "answer": "Also we have already highlighted a student who you‚Äôll supervise for this",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-10T21:55:43",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "and its 832 words üò¨",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Rehab UK‚Å©",
    "timestamp": "2024-05-10T00:05:50",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Else there quota will get full",
    "answer": "Hey",
    "timestamp": "2024-07-10T10:22:31",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Wanted to discuss UCL too",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "2024-07-10T10:27:21",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "5:30 works tomorrow?",
    "answer": "üëç",
    "timestamp": "2024-07-10T10:28:05",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I want to apply to this program too",
    "answer": "Let‚Äôs take it step by step and first work on the LSE wala",
    "timestamp": "2024-07-10T19:55:18",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "And in Qualifications should I add Alevel and Olevels too? [Image]",
    "answer": "Yes add",
    "timestamp": "13/10/2024, 10:01:32‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Level of degree - like what does my undergrad degree qualify as",
    "answer": "Should do both academic",
    "timestamp": "13/10/2024, 10:27:36‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "career_guidance"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay ‚Äé[13/10/2024, 12:15:37‚ÄØPM] Alizeh Kazmi Grad Lead: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "answer": "we can do this bit later [Image]",
    "timestamp": "13/10/2024, 10:30:33‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "For imperial need this too [Image]",
    "answer": "It depends . Some unis take same",
    "timestamp": "14/10/2024, 8:29:59‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hello, should I add my recommenders to respected applications?",
    "answer": "Yes pls do",
    "timestamp": "21/10/2024, 8:54:45‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "thats okay lmk when done [Image]",
    "answer": "So talk about how the professor was selected because the subject was important to you etc, and was willing to take out time to write rec",
    "timestamp": "23/10/2024, 5:14:41‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay [Image] [Image]",
    "answer": "add the work then",
    "timestamp": "26/10/2024, 8:09:36‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "for now added GRE",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "27/10/2024, 11:06:54‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Its not specified anywhere",
    "answer": "You can",
    "timestamp": "27/10/2024, 11:14:15‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "One is the LSE graduate one Other is for John Hopkins SIAS whose also a consultant at world bank",
    "answer": "both will have LUMS ids?",
    "timestamp": "28/10/2024, 1:51:02‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "28/10/2024, 1:52:32‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "The program really seems to focus on experience",
    "answer": "share link of program",
    "timestamp": "28/10/2024, 1:53:07‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "internships"
  },
  {
    "question": "Currently all my programs need GRE",
    "answer": "Ok what do you have in mind",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-11T12:59:37",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Like Econ and computation related",
    "answer": "did u look into Durham",
    "timestamp": "2024-04-11T13:46:09",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "no, will look at this one today",
    "answer": "Yea I think Durham won‚Äôt have one",
    "timestamp": "2024-04-11T13:46:54",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Should I use that option?",
    "answer": "We could yes",
    "timestamp": "20/11/2024, 8:58:46‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "If V is around 153-155 and Q: 164 or above should we go ahead with it?",
    "answer": "Yea",
    "timestamp": "20/11/2024, 9:05:28‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Let‚Äôs do it around 1 pm pak time? ‚Äé[21/11/2024, 9:03:58‚ÄØAM] Alizeh Kazmi Grad Lead: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "answer": "there are times they give a waiver.",
    "timestamp": "21/11/2024, 6:24:22‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where do I stand with this",
    "answer": "Verbal is on the lower side",
    "timestamp": "22/11/2024, 12:34:04‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "And I‚Äôve used all resources out there",
    "answer": "When is the earliest you can give",
    "timestamp": "22/11/2024, 12:59:19‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I think because we did 21 days gap",
    "answer": "Yea so the Cambridge program accepts the gre post submission",
    "timestamp": "22/11/2024, 1:09:52‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I checked it says no",
    "answer": "That‚Äôs fine",
    "timestamp": "22/11/2024, 1:13:30‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What the max date before which I can give another attempt - if I do give one",
    "answer": "I believe give it right after 21 days",
    "timestamp": "22/11/2024, 1:32:22‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "But if you want me to give it again for quant for LSE than I can perhaps work with that but then what more resources would I use",
    "answer": "We can meet on Tuesday",
    "timestamp": "22/11/2024, 1:45:50‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "What time?",
    "answer": "We can do 11",
    "timestamp": "22/11/2024, 1:55:38‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Understandable let me sleep over it",
    "answer": "yes and let‚Äôs really go all out with the app and the recommendations",
    "timestamp": "22/11/2024, 2:01:09‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okie thanks",
    "answer": "I‚Äôll revert on this tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "24/11/2024, 8:00:23‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© @‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© can you please clarify this",
    "answer": "The O and ALevel certificate",
    "timestamp": "25/11/2024, 11:11:05‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Just the degree and transcript right?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "timestamp": "25/11/2024, 11:13:27‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "At camb",
    "answer": "My suggestion is to submit LSE post second attempt with GRE",
    "timestamp": "27/11/2024, 1:18:19‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rehab UK‚Å© also when will you be sending my edited resume",
    "answer": "Yup",
    "timestamp": "2024-01-12T23:37:17",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "internships"
  },
  {
    "question": "what about this?",
    "answer": "Send me a voice note on this",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-12T11:54:41",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Both statements are written",
    "answer": "Resume is looking good",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-12T18:50:51",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I bake a lot and had a venture in Covid too",
    "answer": "so totally should add",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-12T18:54:27",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "extracurriculars"
  },
  {
    "question": "And there is nothing now that i can cut so should i add it or not?",
    "answer": "No we don‚Äôt wanna add a line",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-12T18:57:31",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "If this all is good lemme know I‚Äôll upload this resume and then can submit",
    "answer": "Looks good",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-12T19:20:08",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "internships"
  },
  {
    "question": "And this good to go too?",
    "answer": "Yes that‚Äôs ok",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-12T19:24:44",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "internships"
  },
  {
    "question": "So do I keep them or remove them?",
    "answer": "Removing is also ok",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-12T19:26:03",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "internships"
  },
  {
    "question": "What would you recommend I keep them or remove them?",
    "answer": "Put A",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-12T19:44:03",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "internships"
  },
  {
    "question": "Done and I‚Äôll put grade as A",
    "answer": "Just submit app and then do the professional right after",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-12T19:45:05",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "internships"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is that okay?",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Rehab UK‚Å© @‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å©  should we proceed ?",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-12T19:53:53",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "internships"
  },
  {
    "question": "165 quant 152 verbal",
    "answer": "what was last score",
    "timestamp": "17/12/2024, 12:30:31‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "164 and 151",
    "answer": "ok send it to cambridge",
    "timestamp": "17/12/2024, 12:31:16‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Send to LSE and imperial",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "17/12/2024, 12:31:38‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å©",
    "answer": "Yea pls do and request them to add to your file",
    "timestamp": "18/12/2024, 6:50:46‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "This is LSE application",
    "answer": "Are we applying for two programs @‚Å®Rehab UK‚Å© ?",
    "timestamp": "20/12/2024, 8:57:44‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Everything remains the same course names etc get changed",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "20/12/2024, 10:21:53‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "When can we target LSE",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Rehab UK‚Å©",
    "timestamp": "27/12/2024, 9:55:56‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "I have flight on Saturday",
    "answer": "When you back then",
    "timestamp": "27/12/2024, 11:03:34‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "It‚Äôs next Saturday",
    "answer": "Ok @‚Å®Rehab UK‚Å© let‚Äôs close before she leaves",
    "timestamp": "27/12/2024, 11:04:01‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "4th so I wanna be done before that",
    "answer": "I wanna review whole app",
    "timestamp": "27/12/2024, 11:04:15‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "And when I‚Äôm back let‚Äôs complete imperial",
    "answer": "Ok I think we can do that",
    "timestamp": "27/12/2024, 11:04:27‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "and then there is personal statement lemme check word count for that ‚Äé[27/12/2024, 4:08:02‚ÄØPM] Alizeh Kazmi Grad Lead: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "answer": "can ‚Äé[27/12/2024, 5:18:36‚ÄØPM] Alizeh Kazmi Grad Lead: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "timestamp": "27/12/2024, 3:53:10‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "what is GRE registration number? ‚Äé[27/12/2024, 5:19:41‚ÄØPM] Alizeh Kazmi Grad Lead: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "answer": "yea put that",
    "timestamp": "27/12/2024, 5:19:02‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also there are no details as to what should be In personal statement",
    "answer": "What is this for",
    "timestamp": "27/12/2024, 5:34:20‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Imperial MSC Economics and Strategy for Bussiness",
    "answer": "Just upload your score pdf",
    "timestamp": "27/12/2024, 5:34:50‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rehab UK‚Å© @‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å©",
    "answer": "Alizeh please give us a day to revert",
    "timestamp": "28/12/2024, 10:18:50‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "hey Alizeh appreciate you sending this through but since you‚Äôve just sent it please wait for some time till we understand the extent of edits and changes, as I go through will let you know if i need anything ‚Äé<This message was edited>",
    "answer": "Alizeh we will do whatever best we can, but honestly with such thin timelines we have to see how a doc turns out",
    "timestamp": "30/12/2024, 12:20:12‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I do understand that and I acknowledge the efforts that are being put in place to complete it in time, having said this my circumstances are such that time is really sensitive thing for me and given my circumstances I want to put forth the best thing",
    "answer": "Hi",
    "timestamp": "30/12/2024, 7:38:16‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What‚Äôs the status",
    "answer": "Alizeh let me call you in an hour",
    "timestamp": "2025-03-01T13:22:35",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "We will be submitting LSE tomorrow right?",
    "answer": "I believe we should be ok for that",
    "timestamp": "2025-06-01T10:21:00",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "And imperial? ‚Äé<This message was edited>",
    "answer": "‚ÄéYou deleted this message.",
    "timestamp": "2025-06-01T10:37:24",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Have emailed you edited versions. Please review",
    "answer": "Alizeh once you have plugged in everything pls share the link and login and ill review",
    "timestamp": "2025-06-01T17:01:47",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Filled in imperial app",
    "answer": "Share link of app",
    "timestamp": "2025-06-01T20:10:13",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Should I submit the app?",
    "answer": "Call me",
    "timestamp": "2025-07-01T09:12:01",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôll call you in 30 mins is that okay",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "2025-07-01T09:16:39",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéThis message was deleted.",
    "answer": "callme",
    "timestamp": "21/01/2025, 1:58:19‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What time suits you",
    "answer": "call abhi ‚Äé[21/01/2025, 2:21:15‚ÄØPM] Alizeh Kazmi Grad Lead: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "timestamp": "21/01/2025, 2:05:01‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "of program ‚Äé[21/01/2025, 2:23:23‚ÄØPM] Alizeh Kazmi Grad Lead: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "answer": "ask ur dad",
    "timestamp": "21/01/2025, 2:22:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Right after this is how many people are dependent on this income, I have 4 including musled",
    "answer": "yea whatever is full amount ‚Äé[21/01/2025, 2:29:31‚ÄØPM] Alizeh Kazmi Grad Lead: ‚Äéimage omitted ‚Äé[21/01/2025, 2:30:05‚ÄØPM] Alizeh Kazmi Grad Lead: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "timestamp": "21/01/2025, 2:23:56‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does this imply good or bad?",
    "answer": "It‚Äôs not a rejection so clearly ok for. Ow",
    "timestamp": "25/01/2025, 11:05:45‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Bc it says they want a wider pool to consider too",
    "answer": "wat is pending",
    "timestamp": "25/01/2025, 4:06:59‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "UCL application",
    "answer": "pls close it [Image]",
    "timestamp": "28/01/2025, 1:13:28‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Or second",
    "answer": "should go for it",
    "timestamp": "28/01/2025, 4:58:12‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ya agree",
    "answer": "but yea valid Q by Rehab",
    "timestamp": "28/01/2025, 4:58:37‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "It‚Äôs a very competitive program",
    "answer": "should do it",
    "timestamp": "28/01/2025, 4:58:48‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "They‚Äôve said further to their info",
    "answer": "if they are saying",
    "timestamp": "28/01/2025, 4:58:54‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ya then we should go for",
    "answer": "but theyre recommending it for her",
    "timestamp": "28/01/2025, 4:59:07‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "And submit pdf with the response u send",
    "answer": "i mean we already have alot of cintent",
    "timestamp": "28/01/2025, 4:59:54‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Please guide how to prepare",
    "answer": "Share [Image] ‚Äé[30/01/2025, 9:57:00‚ÄØPM] Alizeh Kazmi Grad Lead: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "timestamp": "30/01/2025, 9:56:39‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also for this make sure to keep the answers very succinct",
    "answer": "let Sadaf revert",
    "timestamp": "2025-01-02T13:53:40",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Not long at alll",
    "answer": "also Rehab can you pls have a call with her on the Imperial interview",
    "timestamp": "2025-01-02T13:53:55",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "I can‚Äôt find any email addresss and I recieved email from do not reply to this address ‚Äé[03/02/2025, 12:36:12‚ÄØPM] Alizeh Kazmi Grad Lead: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Rehab UK‚Å© is there a graduate email address whjere she can forward the no reply mail",
    "timestamp": "2025-03-02T12:35:38",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also have you checked on your portal if there is any option to edit or add another program [Image] [Image] [Image] [Image] [Image]",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Rehab UK‚Å© can you please login and check",
    "timestamp": "2025-07-02T14:04:52",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "congrats that‚Äôs amazing Masha Allah ü•≥",
    "answer": "Wooow",
    "timestamp": "27/02/2025, 10:49:34‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Got into LSE",
    "answer": "Woooh",
    "timestamp": "18/03/2025, 12:54:57‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "MSc Management and Strategy",
    "answer": "MA",
    "timestamp": "18/03/2025, 12:55:22‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôm currently working with my dad in his bussiness on a new venture and I plan on continuing that and launching our venture after masters and I do plan on become associated with LUMS or any other university depending on where I end up in teaching capacity. So eventually I will pursue a PhD too in distant future in strategic management type field, given this career plan which university seems more well suited - if you guys have insight on this I‚Äôd be very helpful",
    "answer": "They‚Äôre both equally great",
    "timestamp": "19/03/2025, 7:39:43‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "career_guidance"
  },
  {
    "question": "I personally think imperial the school is great and has a much higher outreach in my opinion",
    "answer": "I think it really comes down to that",
    "timestamp": "19/03/2025, 7:40:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Aw amazing!! I am sure you‚Äôll enjoy it ü•∞",
    "answer": "good luck Alizeh",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-04T12:28:14",
    "student_name": "Alizeh Kazmi",
    "student_phone": "+2557451124",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéYou created group ‚ÄúAmaan Mufti Apps‚Äù",
    "answer": "Hey Amaan we will use this group to communicate [Image]",
    "timestamp": "21/02/2024, 8:13:17‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéThis message was deleted. ‚Äé[22/02/2024, 4:39:59‚ÄØPM] Amaan Mufti: Resume Template - Grad MBA Executive (2) (1).docx ‚Äédocument omitted",
    "answer": "sure will review tom",
    "timestamp": "22/02/2024, 4:36:57‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "About what opportunities her line of work could give me",
    "answer": "Ok I‚Äôll speak to her",
    "timestamp": "22/02/2024, 6:17:37‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "career_guidance"
  },
  {
    "question": "When do the registrations for the August sat open",
    "answer": "Typically post March",
    "timestamp": "25/02/2024, 12:27:58‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes",
    "answer": "Cool",
    "timestamp": "27/02/2024, 7:50:39‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hey so could I get a list of books I should read and online courses I should start doing",
    "answer": "I‚Äôll share online courses by tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "2024-01-03T18:05:56",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thanks",
    "answer": "https://www.coursera.org/learn/fundamental-skills-in-engineering-design",
    "timestamp": "2024-01-03T18:10:01",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do precited grades work? Is there a threshold set by the school for mocks and midterms. And who gives the predicted grades the school or the CIE board",
    "answer": "every school has their own way of calculating",
    "timestamp": "2024-04-03T14:04:31",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "And for subjects like coding which don't have a predicted grade how important are their school exams/tests",
    "answer": "Well they‚Äôre important",
    "timestamp": "2024-04-03T16:48:10",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "And I'll start this one after my mocks",
    "answer": "We are confirmed for 2pm from this Saturday",
    "timestamp": "2024-04-03T18:11:04",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hey so I have physics tuition at 330 and my exams on Monday so is it fine if I leave the workshop at around 320?",
    "answer": "No Amaan",
    "timestamp": "2024-09-03T13:55:22",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "extracurriculars"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yeah okay",
    "answer": "Thanks",
    "timestamp": "2024-09-03T13:56:08",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I'll just watch the recording of the tuition",
    "answer": "Great",
    "timestamp": "2024-09-03T13:56:16",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can we meet on Friday ?",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "2024-11-03T10:59:17",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hey so is it possible to reschedule the meeting to Saturday or Sunday?",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "15/03/2024, 9:57:52‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "We didn't set a time last weekend",
    "answer": "ok will coordinte soon for coming week",
    "timestamp": "20/03/2024, 9:59:38‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What time are we meeting today?",
    "answer": "Can you come at 2",
    "timestamp": "27/03/2024, 10:41:04‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "27/03/2024, 10:48:10‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Asa i can't attend tomorrows class i have a tuition mock is it possible to reschedule class to another day? ‚Äé<This message was edited>",
    "answer": "Classes can‚Äôt be rescheduled",
    "timestamp": "2024-05-04T22:44:25",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "3-5",
    "answer": "So class is 1-4",
    "timestamp": "2024-05-04T22:46:17",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes please come at 5 sharp",
    "answer": "Hi Amaan",
    "timestamp": "17/04/2024, 11:44:10‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Just got done with 2 papers today I have another two papers on Thursday after which I have a large gap between my papers",
    "answer": "Ok so which day is good to meet",
    "timestamp": "30/04/2024, 1:49:33‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is Saturday fine?",
    "answer": "If I‚Äôm in office on sat then yes",
    "timestamp": "16/05/2024, 4:45:31‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes come tomorrow at 4:30",
    "answer": "Hey what‚Äôs been happening",
    "timestamp": "19/05/2024, 3:56:03‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is it possible to meet soon I wanted to discuss my internships this summer",
    "answer": "Yup",
    "timestamp": "2024-07-06T19:24:18",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "internships"
  },
  {
    "question": "Any update on the internship? [Image]",
    "answer": "@923181138668 call them with Ishaqs reference",
    "timestamp": "21/06/2024, 3:21:22‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "internships"
  },
  {
    "question": "You can go try out edge",
    "answer": "Edge , I‚Äôll pas you their number",
    "timestamp": "24/06/2024, 5:46:12‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôm apart of their product team so sensually they‚Äôre launching a product mid July and I‚Äôm part of that team launching that service",
    "answer": "Amazing",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-07T12:18:45",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "And the last thing I read were the Lord of the rings books like 2 weeks ago",
    "answer": "Let‚Äôs add a book now",
    "timestamp": "25/07/2024, 12:35:08‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "sadaf.khan@dignosco.org [Image]",
    "answer": "So LSE doesn‚Äôt make sense",
    "timestamp": "31/07/2024, 3:17:47‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yeah",
    "answer": "Amaan",
    "timestamp": "2024-01-08T16:44:35",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923702250422 were you able to look at the uk courses [Image]",
    "answer": "üëåüëå",
    "timestamp": "2024-12-08T11:40:33",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "Think I‚Äôll be able to do much better in October",
    "answer": "good job",
    "timestamp": "2024-06-09T15:58:10",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "discussion with Amaans dad. will do 4-5 US unis with aid. europe and maybe UK.",
    "timestamp": "26/09/2024, 11:53:59‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hello Amaan. Come at 3:30 tomorrow",
    "answer": "Hey, please be at the office on October 5, 2024. The head of International office from University of Edinburgh will be visiting our office from 1:45 PM till 3:15 PM. We will discuss program choices, location and any specific questions you may have pertaining to the university.",
    "timestamp": "30/09/2024, 3:12:54‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also a lot of university applications have opened like HKU and Bacconi and Studielink for the Netherlands so when r we gonna start working on those applications",
    "answer": "We can meet today",
    "timestamp": "2024-08-10T08:12:14",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "I have tuition 230-330 is it possible to have the meeting at 345",
    "answer": "Also did you discuss ucas with dad",
    "timestamp": "2024-09-10T08:53:30",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes he said he wants to talk with u on call",
    "answer": "I called him",
    "timestamp": "2024-09-10T08:56:46",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "üëç",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "15/10/2024, 3:16:35‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "And individual applications like HKU bacconi etc",
    "answer": "Will start asap",
    "timestamp": "22/10/2024, 10:15:25‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôve made my HKU account",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "23/10/2024, 12:18:02‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is tomorrow at 4 possible?",
    "answer": "üëç",
    "timestamp": "23/10/2024, 12:18:12‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Instead of today",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "25/10/2024, 12:23:42‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923018379777 can you please have a quick chat with him so we have rough idea of exact program in atleast 3 of the UK schools. We are working on the statement so need it",
    "answer": "Mechanical engineering",
    "timestamp": "13/11/2024, 10:37:15‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Since they have the same requirements",
    "answer": "Amaan",
    "timestamp": "13/11/2024, 10:48:57‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes but I thought it was possible to transition into electrical considering they‚Äôre very similar",
    "answer": "you can do that later",
    "timestamp": "13/11/2024, 10:50:08‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://warwick.ac.uk/study/undergraduate/courses/beng-mechanical-engineering/",
    "answer": "@923702250422 have you also checked if any of these have any testing requirements",
    "timestamp": "13/11/2024, 11:59:28‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok will review",
    "answer": "@923702250422 have you seen if boconni is live ?",
    "timestamp": "16/11/2024, 8:52:04‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also what‚Äôs the update on my UCAS and Commonapp applications?",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "30/11/2024, 12:39:59‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok so is it fine if I come tomorrow by 4?",
    "answer": "Yes.",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-12T17:12:55",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hey so there‚Äôs been an issue with the car is it fine if I come tomorrow at the same time",
    "answer": "im not in tomorrow afternoon",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-12T16:07:05",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "My school said I‚Äôll get the necessary documents on Monday so should I still come today?",
    "answer": "Wait then",
    "timestamp": "2024-06-12T13:07:52",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I can come on friday because I have exams everyday until Thursday",
    "answer": "I thought he was coming today",
    "timestamp": "2024-09-12T17:48:47",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923018379777 my dad said he wants to meet with you at 3 is that doable?",
    "answer": "today is tough to meet, we can meet on Monday in person",
    "timestamp": "13/12/2024, 11:42:04‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hey so due to a family emergency me and my dad won‚Äôt be able to come in today is it possible to meet tomorrow?",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "16/12/2024, 2:01:28‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923018379777 can you meet with my father on Tuesday",
    "answer": "Yup",
    "timestamp": "21/12/2024, 1:03:18‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": ".",
    "answer": "This isn‚Äôt carl benz",
    "timestamp": "2025-03-01T16:08:16",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is it fine if I come today by 340?",
    "answer": "Yup",
    "timestamp": "2025-06-01T07:43:24",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": ".",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "2025-12-01T13:13:14",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Since we‚Äôve decided on the majority of universities being outside London",
    "answer": "Monday is tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "2025-12-01T14:25:58",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I come by 4-430?",
    "answer": "4",
    "timestamp": "13/01/2025, 11:35:11‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I come a bit earlier at 345?",
    "answer": "yea come",
    "timestamp": "13/01/2025, 2:28:44‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "For all students who have applied to US universities with the SAT option, please make sure SAT scores are sent from Collegeboard website. If this doesn't apply to you please ignore the message. ‚Äé[13/01/2025, 4:17:24‚ÄØPM] Amaan Mufti: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "answer": "@923328234782 pls update sheet",
    "timestamp": "13/01/2025, 3:53:03‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay",
    "answer": "Aman send me passport copy",
    "timestamp": "13/01/2025, 5:13:34‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôm at school I‚Äôll do it once I get home",
    "answer": "UCAS ID number",
    "timestamp": "14/01/2025, 11:29:54‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "So would that be fine or would it result in an issue",
    "answer": "It comes out as math lessons not A level math specifically so no issues",
    "timestamp": "14/01/2025, 12:12:51‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I mean from Georgia tech",
    "answer": "@923333575290 ?",
    "timestamp": "14/01/2025, 1:35:51‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok cool then we are good",
    "answer": "Amaan Boconni yes or no ?",
    "timestamp": "14/01/2025, 5:44:01‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923702250422 have reviewed Carl Benz it good. Just change the courses in first answer like we did for the UCAS",
    "answer": "Aman",
    "timestamp": "17/01/2025, 7:08:57‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Carl Benz essay?",
    "answer": "Pdf of the app ‚Äé[18/01/2025, 12:35:55‚ÄØPM] Amaan Mufti: Motivational letter Carl Benz.pdf ‚Ä¢ ‚Äé2 pages ‚Äédocument omitted",
    "timestamp": "18/01/2025, 12:34:29‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923018379777",
    "answer": "Within this week",
    "timestamp": "18/01/2025, 5:58:20‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "So what‚Äôs the process gonna be like do I submit it or will you handle all of it",
    "answer": "I‚Äôll coordinate with you",
    "timestamp": "18/01/2025, 6:14:33‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "And applying to Sussex",
    "answer": "we can finalise this week",
    "timestamp": "21/01/2025, 3:03:31‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923018379777",
    "answer": "Let‚Äôs target Friday",
    "timestamp": "21/01/2025, 7:53:32‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôm getting all these emails about application portals for specific uk unis shud I pay them any attention",
    "answer": "Yea",
    "timestamp": "30/01/2025, 12:40:23‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "UCL was A star double A Nottingham was a C in math",
    "answer": "Amazing Yaar",
    "timestamp": "2025-11-03T20:25:48",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "I got an offer from Bath double A star A",
    "answer": "Amazing",
    "timestamp": "2025-12-03T15:13:56",
    "student_name": "Amaan Mufti",
    "student_phone": "+4086225489",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923018379777 please start review of common app.",
    "answer": "yes will do tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "20/10/2021, 1:40:31‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ammar Haidermota",
    "student_phone": "+7154575603",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I call now",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "timestamp": "20/10/2021, 4:08:16‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ammar Haidermota",
    "student_phone": "+7154575603",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ammar when are you free to chat ?",
    "answer": "Have you added the honours",
    "timestamp": "20/10/2021, 6:18:22‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ammar Haidermota",
    "student_phone": "+7154575603",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do I write courses in the common app?  Under the education section. I‚Äôm not sure what level to give",
    "answer": "Which courses are these [Image]",
    "timestamp": "22/10/2021, 9:37:21‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ammar Haidermota",
    "student_phone": "+7154575603",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thank you",
    "answer": "Ammar the section on how you got to know about Penn where you have added your sisters is fine. if you can add their Penn ids here that would be great as welll",
    "timestamp": "22/10/2021, 10:10:50‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ammar Haidermota",
    "student_phone": "+7154575603",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay thank you",
    "answer": "also for hakimi school 20 weeks in a year sound a lot",
    "timestamp": "23/10/2021, 9:06:34‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Ammar Haidermota",
    "student_phone": "+7154575603",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "For sports is 7 hrs a week/20 weeks a year fine?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "timestamp": "23/10/2021, 11:11:30‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Ammar Haidermota",
    "student_phone": "+7154575603",
    "category": "extracurriculars"
  },
  {
    "question": "Please complete it by week end so Rizwan can review your app",
    "answer": "Ok can we have a quick call on this so I can guide",
    "timestamp": "2021-11-11T13:52:41",
    "student_name": "Ammar Haidermota",
    "student_phone": "+7154575603",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Should I call now",
    "answer": "Call me in like 5 min pls",
    "timestamp": "2021-11-11T14:32:35",
    "student_name": "Ammar Haidermota",
    "student_phone": "+7154575603",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tried calling",
    "answer": "Lemme know when I can review the UC app",
    "timestamp": "2021-11-11T14:41:55",
    "student_name": "Ammar Haidermota",
    "student_phone": "+7154575603",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Please share login details",
    "answer": "?",
    "timestamp": "22/11/2021, 3:48:16‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ammar Haidermota",
    "student_phone": "+7154575603",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thank you!!",
    "answer": "Happy birthday :)",
    "timestamp": "29/11/2021, 6:37:55‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Ammar Haidermota",
    "student_phone": "+7154575603",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "You can submit tonight. Rizwan will do a final review in a little while",
    "answer": "Ammar activities are great. for the last one pls add the link of the research paper done through The Nation",
    "timestamp": "29/11/2021, 9:34:22‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ammar Haidermota",
    "student_phone": "+7154575603",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will do so",
    "answer": "Pls share pdf of submitted app",
    "timestamp": "29/11/2021, 10:45:42‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Ammar Haidermota",
    "student_phone": "+7154575603",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéMessages and calls are end-to-end encrypted. Only people in this chat can read, listen to, or share them.",
    "answer": "Hey Areeb",
    "timestamp": "15/08/2023, 10:42:32‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "Also for any tasks etc you‚Äôre confused pls always put here",
    "timestamp": "15/08/2023, 10:43:00‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Current APs: Ap Statistics Ap Calculus Ab Ap Physics 2 Ap Psychology",
    "answer": "Also what are school timings",
    "timestamp": "15/08/2023, 10:53:42‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "My calendar and timings",
    "answer": "Thank you",
    "timestamp": "16/08/2023, 12:14:36‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "How about 10:45 pm my time today",
    "answer": "Hey we can do 10:45pm your time on Saturday.",
    "timestamp": "17/08/2023, 11:20:20‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "That works",
    "answer": "Cool",
    "timestamp": "18/08/2023, 4:29:48‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "SAT official guide coming tomorrow and rest by this Friday",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "23/08/2023, 7:53:34‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "Hey Areeb you good to speak rn ?",
    "timestamp": "31/08/2023, 7:30:47‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yeah",
    "answer": "Ok gimme 5 min",
    "timestamp": "2023-02-09T08:35:26",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "My phone ran out of charge",
    "answer": "hey Areeb",
    "timestamp": "2023-02-09T09:18:40",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Activity form",
    "answer": "thanks",
    "timestamp": "2023-06-09T11:45:09",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "extracurriculars"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can we meet tomorrow night",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "2023-09-09T10:11:15",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéYou added Sadaf Khan",
    "answer": "Hey Sadaf, Areeb is in junior year at heritage high school in cali",
    "timestamp": "2023-08-10T09:04:52",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://us04web.zoom.us/j/78535933084?pwd=ajQtHtwTdnzzdH89cAdctF9nQR5vqp.1",
    "answer": "Hey Areeb let‚Äôs speak tomorrow night your time !",
    "timestamp": "2023-11-10T21:02:49",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sure",
    "answer": "Cool will speak around this time tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "21/10/2023, 8:37:10‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yeah",
    "answer": "Join Zoom Meeting https://us04web.zoom.us/j/72680477920?pwd=RhZrqsTgRRxTPkDUkW1j9J2ORzKEJ6.1 Meeting ID:  726 8047 7920 Passcode: tfK60B",
    "timestamp": "21/10/2023, 8:41:23‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sure",
    "answer": "Join Zoom Meeting https://us04web.zoom.us/j/77943088443?pwd=me3RzdUyo9uEYKH6Gwkso9aNFokdhf.1 Meeting ID:  779 4308 8443 Passcode: WL8aqA",
    "timestamp": "28/10/2023, 8:37:32‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "When can we meet soon",
    "answer": "Hey Areeb I‚Äôll reschedule and coordinate with you",
    "timestamp": "29/10/2023, 9:51:41‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "https://datasciencedojo.com/blog/ai-and-ml-podcasts/#",
    "timestamp": "29/10/2023, 10:07:10‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "Hey Areeb",
    "timestamp": "29/10/2023, 10:09:29‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yeah",
    "answer": "Ok gimme ten min",
    "timestamp": "2023-05-11T08:38:58",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I was able to subscribe",
    "answer": "Let‚Äôs speak as soon as sat score is out",
    "timestamp": "15/11/2023, 1:43:49‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yeah",
    "answer": "Ok gimme ten min",
    "timestamp": "19/11/2023, 9:46:13‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I am right now",
    "answer": "Ok gimme ten min",
    "timestamp": "2023-10-12T09:00:34",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yeah",
    "answer": "yea diff is straight 12 hours",
    "timestamp": "16/02/2024, 9:18:17‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi areeb! Let‚Äôs coordinate a time for this week please. Maybe tomorrow or day after.",
    "answer": "Hi Areeb please confirm, we wanna start some essay brain storming",
    "timestamp": "26/02/2024, 3:46:24‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "How about Saturday 9 am my time",
    "answer": "Let Sadaf confirm",
    "timestamp": "27/02/2024, 7:34:46‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok üëç that works. Speak to you then.",
    "answer": "I think you‚Äôll have to do Sunday 9pm maybe his time then",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-03T16:02:34",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Aoa",
    "answer": "WAS",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-03T19:23:57",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "The meeting will be at zoom or WhatsApp",
    "answer": "Can be either",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-03T19:24:54",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Time exchange commitment is getting lost in messages",
    "answer": "yes don‚Äôt worry will be done.",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-03T19:27:12",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can we do 9am Sunday? It will be your 10pm Saturday night.",
    "answer": "Let me confirm this by tomorrow pls",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-03T19:33:58",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi @‚Å®Areeb Masood USA‚Å© as per our last meeting let‚Äôs update this now please.",
    "answer": "areeb.syed0307@gmail.com",
    "timestamp": "13/03/2024, 3:12:03‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "His spring break is starting by end of this week",
    "answer": "Yes can do for sure",
    "timestamp": "13/03/2024, 5:54:49‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What about summer camp, skiing and hiking",
    "answer": "Yes all of that should be included",
    "timestamp": "20/03/2024, 1:11:44‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "How about Sunday night",
    "answer": "ok ill call you",
    "timestamp": "20/04/2024, 8:45:54‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://royaneh.ggacbsa.org/",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© can u send him sample common app essays",
    "timestamp": "22/04/2024, 10:55:20‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi @‚Å®Areeb Masood USA‚Å© I would like to have a meeting this weekend. Please let me know what day you prefer",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Areeb Masood USA‚Å© pls lets do this and continue on the essay discsuions we wanna do for Cali and common app",
    "timestamp": "26/04/2024, 4:15:24‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Let‚Äôs talk Saturday night",
    "answer": "WAS",
    "timestamp": "2024-01-05T21:09:19",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Did this meeting happen?",
    "answer": "Yup",
    "timestamp": "20/05/2024, 10:55:13‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi @‚Å®Areeb Masood USA‚Å© were you able to work on the next prompt ?",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Areeb Masood USA‚Å© ?",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-07T17:35:43",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "When can we meet",
    "answer": "Can speak in 15 min",
    "timestamp": "28/07/2024, 10:25:30‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://www.inspiritai.com/",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Areeb Masood USA‚Å© as discussed please have a look at a new SAT Center even if you can‚Äôt get one near your area, I would recommend to find an alternative. @‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© he is struggling with content for the leadership essay. If you can schedule a call with him within this week to discuss content. My suggestion is we take the scouts route for this if we can talk about something different versus what we‚Äôre doing for community service. My suggestion for the academic essay is to speak about CS, and here you can talk about all that you have learnt through projects, any languages you excel at. Why the subject excites you, etc We can discuss the fourth essay once we are done with these 3. Please note that the common app account needs to be created for Claremont universities and the main common app essay needs to be brainstormed and should ideally be around your scouts work. We need to communicate more on WhatsApp so you can highlight wherever you get stuck so firstly we‚Äôre in the loop and secondly we can guide you towards a solution. Let‚Äôs please be super interactive for next 5/6 months so we can have a very solid app going in.",
    "timestamp": "28/07/2024, 11:30:19‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéYou removed Masood Syed Cali",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Areeb Masood USA‚Å© when can you speak with Sadaf to discuss the leadership and academic essat",
    "timestamp": "30/07/2024, 4:57:18‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "WhatsApp somehow never showed the call on my side ‚Äé<This message was edited>",
    "answer": "Ok pls coordinate with sadaf for tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "2024-01-08T17:59:26",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi @‚Å®Areeb Masood USA‚Å© how‚Äôs it going? Were you able to work on the drafts further ?",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Areeb Masood USA‚Å© ?",
    "timestamp": "2024-12-08T19:46:15",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I have edited the community prompt",
    "answer": "Hey Areeb i belive we need to improve our communication response times",
    "timestamp": "15/08/2024, 9:55:19‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I feel like it can be brought under the word limit if I remove the first paragraph",
    "answer": "pls",
    "timestamp": "15/08/2024, 9:56:24‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I will try to finish the leadership prompt by the weekend",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "15/08/2024, 9:57:03‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "The academic subject and leadership prompts",
    "answer": "we need a total of 4",
    "timestamp": "15/08/2024, 9:59:48‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "We could do the beyond what has shared prompt",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "15/08/2024, 10:00:48‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I will make it soon",
    "answer": "can you make it today",
    "timestamp": "15/08/2024, 10:02:17‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will finish by teausday ‚Äé<This message was edited>",
    "answer": "Ok but let‚Äôs speed this",
    "timestamp": "20/08/2024, 5:30:23‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© for recommendation letters, what date do you want them to be finished",
    "answer": "first you need to create the common app account, then you need to invite 2 teachers and they need to write full proper recs (atleast a page long) highlighting your strengths and your work over last 2-3 years and then they submit it",
    "timestamp": "26/08/2024, 12:11:47‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Areeb Masood USA‚Å© what‚Äôs the update on our drafts",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Areeb Masood USA‚Å© please respond",
    "timestamp": "29/08/2024, 4:33:18‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I have finished the first draft of the leadership essay in the same uc prompts google doc",
    "answer": "Areeb",
    "timestamp": "2024-04-09T10:50:59",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Please set a timeline with me for when I can see both remaining drafts . Ideally by this weekend Sunday we should have drafts",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Areeb Masood USA‚Å© pls can you respond",
    "timestamp": "23/09/2024, 5:08:43‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "It should be completed by the end of the week",
    "answer": "Ok and the main common app essay discussion which you had with sadaf ?",
    "timestamp": "25/09/2024, 7:46:16‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "Asa",
    "timestamp": "25/09/2024, 8:17:29‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi @‚Å®Areeb Masood USA‚Å© are your drafts done ?",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Areeb Masood USA‚Å© ??",
    "timestamp": "2024-01-10T11:22:15",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôm having trouble with the draft, let‚Äôs meet tomorrow night and l‚Äôll try to finish the other one by then",
    "answer": "pls share a voice note on the issue you are facing",
    "timestamp": "2024-05-10T23:59:23",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôm having trouble relating swimming to a specific idea, and trying to write about how you start isn‚Äôt making sense",
    "answer": "ok let sadaf revert on it",
    "timestamp": "2024-06-10T00:02:10",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "and the academic sections",
    "timestamp": "2024-06-10T00:03:00",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I finished the academic section",
    "answer": "ok pls do the activties today",
    "timestamp": "2024-06-10T00:03:20",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "I believe sadaf will call you morning our time",
    "timestamp": "2024-06-10T00:08:19",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "??",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Areeb Masood USA‚Å© pls respond",
    "timestamp": "2024-11-10T15:37:53",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I completed them and they are in the doc",
    "answer": "What about the UC form",
    "timestamp": "2024-11-10T19:26:21",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "And is there any colleges that are missing from the commen app account",
    "answer": "I‚Äôll review your common app this week and have a call on that",
    "timestamp": "15/10/2024, 11:58:41‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "ok",
    "answer": "Ok that‚Äôs fine",
    "timestamp": "15/10/2024, 11:59:20‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "You can maybe speak about technical understanding analytical skills or exploring the topics in depth outside of tn classroom. For weakness what are you thinking ?",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Areeb Masood USA‚Å©",
    "timestamp": "15/10/2024, 12:21:48‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can we meet tonight or tomorrow night",
    "answer": "Let sadaf confirm",
    "timestamp": "16/10/2024, 6:54:44‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I think I have already given my login for the commen app and I have filled out most of it",
    "answer": "Ok will review",
    "timestamp": "16/10/2024, 11:12:50‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hello",
    "answer": "Hey",
    "timestamp": "17/10/2024, 9:28:06‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "can we call today about the recommendation letter",
    "answer": "Yea let‚Äôs do now",
    "timestamp": "17/10/2024, 9:28:21‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "ok",
    "answer": "Calling",
    "timestamp": "17/10/2024, 9:28:39‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Crystalline123@ [Image] [Image] [Image]",
    "answer": "Hey Areeb",
    "timestamp": "17/10/2024, 9:30:35‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéYou pinned a message",
    "answer": "for cali also you havent added any activities",
    "timestamp": "23/10/2024, 10:22:46‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Let me call you at 10 as right now I‚Äôm busy",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "2024-07-11T07:25:02",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@Sadaf can we meet my sunday night to discuss the commen app essay ‚Äé[07/11/2024, 10:17:06‚ÄØAM] Areeb Masood USA: ‚Äéimage omitted ‚Äé[07/11/2024, 10:21:31‚ÄØAM] Areeb Masood USA: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Areeb Masood USA‚Å©",
    "timestamp": "2024-07-11T10:06:08",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1FU5jfquJyAPNKVYkOnCWb8UYz7obwbFv0IOry0bco7M/edit?usp=sharing",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Areeb Masood USA‚Å© have you flled the UC",
    "timestamp": "2024-12-11T13:30:30",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Does Boy Scouts count as a volunteer or extracurricular activity",
    "answer": "can be either depending on the description",
    "timestamp": "13/11/2024, 1:01:48‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also @‚Å®Areeb Masood USA‚Å© Thursday you need to send the main essay draft",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Areeb Masood USA‚Å©",
    "timestamp": "13/11/2024, 1:54:35‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok please keep me posted and show me draft this weekend",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "14/11/2024, 2:39:39‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you please launch a doc with the questions and then we can discuss",
    "answer": "Should we not just trim the UC ones for UT",
    "timestamp": "18/11/2024, 2:26:53‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "But will need to work on them separately",
    "answer": "üëç",
    "timestamp": "18/11/2024, 2:27:37‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Have you put the prompts on the common app doc?",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Areeb Masood USA‚Å©  pls respond",
    "timestamp": "19/11/2024, 10:34:53‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok keep me posted on this.",
    "answer": "Areeb i have reviewed your UC and fixed alot of grammar errors. there were tons of spell issues and punctuation issues. pls note any good uni wouldnt really tolerate this",
    "timestamp": "20/11/2024, 1:04:59‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I get an update on the editing of my UC essays",
    "answer": "Pls do that so I can review tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "23/11/2024, 1:13:53‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "When can I get the edited essays by",
    "answer": "Let‚Äôs give it another 2 days",
    "timestamp": "24/11/2024, 2:47:06‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi @‚Å®Areeb Masood USA‚Å© have just emailed you the UC essays. Please review and then discuss with me before we prepare for submission",
    "answer": "Areeb since you‚Äôre off from school please go through whole UC app and your essays",
    "timestamp": "26/11/2024, 6:12:57‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© Can we call soon",
    "answer": "hey yes she will call soon",
    "timestamp": "27/11/2024, 10:42:14‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "have reviewed everything @‚Å®Areeb Masood USA‚Å© @‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å©",
    "answer": "Ok I‚Äôll do a check in 30 min",
    "timestamp": "28/11/2024, 1:12:03‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok üëç",
    "answer": "in the additional info should we mention that \" I am giving 4 AP exams in Senior Year. I have predicted grades of 5 in all of them\"",
    "timestamp": "28/11/2024, 1:13:41‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes I think we can. It‚Äôs not mentioned anywhere else is it ?",
    "answer": "i dont see it anywhere",
    "timestamp": "28/11/2024, 1:19:52‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å©",
    "answer": "call me",
    "timestamp": "28/11/2024, 1:32:44‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© when can I review the commen app essay?",
    "answer": "Areeb you‚Äôve added the tenth activity yea?",
    "timestamp": "30/11/2024, 10:23:33‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yea",
    "answer": "Essay is ready",
    "timestamp": "30/11/2024, 10:24:32‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "UT Austin app is submitted",
    "answer": "Areeb make sure you send sat score to UT",
    "timestamp": "30/11/2024, 9:34:17‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do I also have to send my Ap scores",
    "answer": "Yup",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-12T09:58:33",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "And Claremont McKenna?",
    "answer": "also pls do purdue",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-12T12:51:24",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you please share one by one so we can start working. Georgia tech was almost done right ?",
    "answer": "Areeb pls",
    "timestamp": "2024-07-12T12:06:28",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok we can get back to you on Claremont. But please yes Purdue and rice also [Image]",
    "answer": "We should do Claremont",
    "timestamp": "2024-11-12T12:37:35",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will review the other Purdue in the meantime",
    "answer": "Areeb call me",
    "timestamp": "2024-12-12T13:50:39",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "I will review the Ut supplements tomorrow as well as start working on Harvey mudd",
    "answer": "UT?",
    "timestamp": "14/12/2024, 2:55:17‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "research_opportunities"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes was going to say do Harvey mudd next",
    "answer": "Hey Areeb",
    "timestamp": "14/12/2024, 3:10:25‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "And please Harvey mudd by tomorrow latest",
    "answer": "Pls call me",
    "timestamp": "17/12/2024, 1:52:23‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "I finished the 500 word harvey mudd supplement",
    "answer": "call me",
    "timestamp": "18/12/2024, 1:57:48‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pomona I am sending you edited version now but still waiting on one prompt from you please send that so we can finalise",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Areeb Masood USA‚Å© then target submissions for today include : Purdue Case Western Middlebury Georgia Tech",
    "timestamp": "19/12/2024, 8:09:06‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "I thought UIUC had no required supplements",
    "answer": "UIUC has two small 150 words",
    "timestamp": "21/12/2024, 2:40:04‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "I will try to get you those supplements in the coming days",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "22/12/2024, 1:27:33‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "When I get the chance I will submit the Pomona application",
    "answer": "pls can you do asap",
    "timestamp": "24/12/2024, 12:52:56‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å©",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "26/12/2024, 12:46:35‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "UIUC Jan 5 Harvey Mudd Jan 5 USC Jan 15 Stanford Jan 5th Michigan feb 1st",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Areeb Masood USA‚Å© i checked you haven't submitted Pomona or Purdue",
    "timestamp": "26/12/2024, 12:17:55‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "I haven‚Äôt received the edited Purdue supplements yet",
    "answer": "What is the question ?",
    "timestamp": "26/12/2024, 5:53:37‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Purdue I will resend to you",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© can we use the add info essay for this one ? Will we need any tweaking to address last part of the question ?",
    "timestamp": "26/12/2024, 6:18:08‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Submit Purdue and let us know",
    "answer": "Areeb",
    "timestamp": "29/12/2024, 9:58:12‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Uiuc has been shared also",
    "answer": "Have you submitted",
    "timestamp": "30/12/2024, 5:47:05‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "I have submitted Pomona and uiuc at the moment and plan to submit rice and Purdue in the morning",
    "answer": "Pls follow above instructions",
    "timestamp": "2025-02-01T02:08:14",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Purdue, rice, Harvey mudd is submitted",
    "answer": "Will send in some hours from how",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-01T10:51:02",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "When can I receive the Stanford prompts",
    "answer": "Will send soon",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-01T22:59:01",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Muhammad Areeb",
    "answer": "you had not submitted the writing supplement of Rice as that was separae",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-01T23:08:28",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I didn‚Äôt see that",
    "answer": "yup",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-01T23:10:38",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Stanford is submitted",
    "answer": "submit Case Western too",
    "timestamp": "2025-06-01T00:58:09",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "do I also have to send ap scores",
    "answer": "Yup",
    "timestamp": "2025-06-01T21:53:36",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© @‚Å®Areeb Masood USA‚Å© I have shared USC as well. Please note we will not use add info for this app",
    "answer": "Areeb ?",
    "timestamp": "15/01/2025, 6:22:12‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "This should be the last application",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "16/01/2025, 4:36:22‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will share your essays",
    "answer": "Hey Areeb Any updates from any of the unis",
    "timestamp": "20/01/2025, 5:25:34‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "I have submitted Michigan without the add info",
    "answer": "Cool",
    "timestamp": "2025-01-02T12:31:10",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "This is the question @‚Å®Areeb Masood USA‚Å© please try put together some pointers or have a call with me to discuss",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Areeb Masood USA‚Å©",
    "timestamp": "26/06/2025, 11:55:55‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can we call right now to start discussing ideas for the essay",
    "answer": "let sadaf respond. shes in europe rn. so not sure if shes up",
    "timestamp": "28/06/2025, 11:48:15‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Then I can start creating a draft",
    "answer": "Yes let her respond pls coordinate time wit her",
    "timestamp": "28/06/2025, 11:51:26‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Let‚Äôs speak your morning @‚Å®Areeb Masood USA‚Å©. I‚Äôm flexible with time just msg me when you are up",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Areeb Masood USA‚Å© pls confirm",
    "timestamp": "28/06/2025, 2:49:30‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Or a later time in your time zone",
    "answer": "Let her respond to you in an hour or so",
    "timestamp": "2025-02-07T10:41:50",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "I can call right now",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Areeb Masood USA‚Å© have you spoken to sadaf",
    "timestamp": "2025-02-07T21:37:02",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi @‚Å®Areeb Masood USA‚Å© were you able to put something down for the first prompt ?",
    "answer": "When is deadline for submission",
    "timestamp": "2025-09-07T14:35:53",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "It is 4 am on the 11th your time",
    "answer": "Ok so pls can you send the draft",
    "timestamp": "2025-09-07T14:39:37",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I will have something tomorrow very soon",
    "answer": "Tomorrow as in the 9th yes ?",
    "timestamp": "2025-09-07T14:40:17",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I finish the other prompt later today",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å©",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-07T06:55:11",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "here is my short answer",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "2025-11-07T06:43:19",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "any update on the second prompt",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "timestamp": "2025-12-07T00:51:19",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thank you for helping on the essays",
    "answer": "Great",
    "timestamp": "2025-12-07T02:37:39",
    "student_name": "Areeb Masood",
    "student_phone": "+8229393140",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes",
    "answer": "hamda pls make sure when he comes he fills the activity list form as well",
    "timestamp": "17/09/2021, 10:33:00‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do I need to bring anything for today‚Äôs meeting?",
    "answer": "no just come in . Sadaf will meet you, make you read a few essays and you need to complete the activity list",
    "timestamp": "17/09/2021, 2:45:08‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôll ask him and let you know",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "17/09/2021, 2:47:48‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "Asad try coming in tomorrow to read some more essays as well",
    "timestamp": "17/09/2021, 2:52:00‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "And his meeting is scheduled for 3 on Monday",
    "answer": "Great",
    "timestamp": "17/09/2021, 7:47:10‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sure what time?",
    "answer": "Come anytime tomorrow to read. @‚Å®Hamda Khan Dignosco‚Å© just make sure he gets the book to read",
    "timestamp": "17/09/2021, 7:48:48‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Would tomorrow at 1 work?",
    "answer": "Yes you can come",
    "timestamp": "17/09/2021, 8:28:32‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes",
    "answer": "Thanks",
    "timestamp": "17/09/2021, 10:50:29‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes",
    "answer": "hello",
    "timestamp": "25/09/2021, 10:46:31‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also for the OUAC is there any thing that I need to bring in with me (report cards, passport, etc.) ?",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Hamda Khan Dignosco‚Å©",
    "timestamp": "27/09/2021, 11:43:19‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "UCAS Login Details: https://accounts.ucas.com/Account/Login Email: abasadbilwani@gmail.com Password: Asadshabbir1! UCAS ID: 1602805761",
    "answer": "hamda has his OUAC been sorted",
    "timestamp": "30/09/2021, 12:57:28‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "No I haven‚Äôt done the activities section",
    "answer": "Pls do so we can meet",
    "timestamp": "2021-05-10T13:10:53",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "extracurriculars"
  },
  {
    "question": "Put every internship for now",
    "answer": "Hamda can you schedule meeting with me for Tuesday at 3:30",
    "timestamp": "2021-05-10T14:19:36",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "internships"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can we do Wednesday?",
    "answer": "We can do Thursday",
    "timestamp": "2021-09-10T11:48:49",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hello Asad, This is to remind you that your meeting is confirmed for today at 4:30 PM. Also, please bring your laptop.",
    "answer": "Asad",
    "timestamp": "14/10/2021, 6:32:39‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes will do it today",
    "answer": "Asad pls do so we can submit by tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "22/10/2021, 12:55:09‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do I include that?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "timestamp": "22/10/2021, 1:02:11‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôll include it in my OUAC application",
    "answer": "cool",
    "timestamp": "22/10/2021, 10:11:15‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "So how far back should I list my activities",
    "answer": "From class 9 onwards",
    "timestamp": "23/10/2021, 1:25:04‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "extracurriculars"
  },
  {
    "question": "I haven‚Äôt put this yet as I‚Äôm unsure of what date to put alongside it",
    "answer": "Put sept-Oct",
    "timestamp": "23/10/2021, 2:07:45‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "For program choices my dad is saying to make sure we have kept one safety school",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "23/10/2021, 2:35:36‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also don‚Äôt submit it just yet my dad is saying he wants to take one final look tonight before it‚Äôs submitted",
    "answer": "Yes you will be submitting not us",
    "timestamp": "23/10/2021, 2:42:46‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay will submit it tonight",
    "answer": "Share pdf here so I review once again before you do",
    "timestamp": "23/10/2021, 2:46:17‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "How much importance do the universities give to the activities?",
    "answer": "They‚Äôll eventually ask you stuff in either essay questions /video interviews",
    "timestamp": "23/10/2021, 2:53:36‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "extracurriculars"
  },
  {
    "question": "I feel that the activity section is lacking a bit",
    "answer": "Let‚Äôs add some more stuff then pls",
    "timestamp": "23/10/2021, 2:54:53‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "extracurriculars"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you please send a list of the top 10 universities in Canada for my program",
    "answer": "Please call me",
    "timestamp": "24/10/2021, 1:03:27‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hello I have completed my OUAC application and only the payment is remaining. Rizwan can you please go over it one time and then give me the green light to pay and submit.",
    "answer": "Pls share login details",
    "timestamp": "30/10/2021, 10:45:15‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also for the activities section will I be required to show a certificate for each activity?",
    "answer": "No",
    "timestamp": "30/10/2021, 10:49:53‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "extracurriculars"
  },
  {
    "question": "OUAC Login Details Link to Login: https://www.ouac.on.ca/apply/undergraduate/en_CA/user/login Username: asadbilwani12 Password:  Asadbilwani21*",
    "answer": "u have chosen the wrong one at western",
    "timestamp": "30/10/2021, 10:54:41‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "you can check the program order once",
    "timestamp": "30/10/2021, 11:08:17‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I haven‚Äôt done it yet but I plan on doing it",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "timestamp": "30/10/2021, 11:09:21‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I am submitting it right now",
    "answer": "Great",
    "timestamp": "30/10/2021, 12:57:55‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Greatüëçüèª",
    "answer": "Asad what‚Äôs the status of the UK personal statement",
    "timestamp": "30/10/2021, 4:27:33‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© can we schedule a meeting for Monday?",
    "answer": "We need to set some type of target date for drafting the essay",
    "timestamp": "2021-01-11T15:54:15",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "Asad did you check on the Canadian universities",
    "timestamp": "2021-01-11T15:55:57",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Friday will be really difficult can we keep it on Saturday?",
    "answer": "Then let‚Äôs stick to Monday",
    "timestamp": "2021-03-11T07:51:32",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I got a reply from western university",
    "answer": "?",
    "timestamp": "2021-04-11T18:13:50",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "To sign up on their website",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "2021-04-11T18:15:02",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "On my way",
    "answer": "whats the progess on PS",
    "timestamp": "18/11/2021, 3:41:19‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "When we getting the draft",
    "timestamp": "23/11/2021, 11:15:26‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Asad I was expecting the draft",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Asad Bilwani‚Å© when are you sharing the draft",
    "timestamp": "2021-01-12T22:38:01",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sadaf I have shared it with u from before",
    "answer": "Please can you share draft in word format",
    "timestamp": "2021-02-12T07:07:47",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay I will email it as well",
    "answer": "havent received any email",
    "timestamp": "2021-02-12T07:13:35",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I have your email address?",
    "answer": "Rizwan.javed@dignosco.org",
    "timestamp": "2021-02-12T16:09:00",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hello what is the update on my personal statement",
    "answer": "Will take a few days before we revert",
    "timestamp": "2021-06-12T14:23:19",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hello is there any update on my personal statement?",
    "answer": "Working on it",
    "timestamp": "2021-12-12T20:37:11",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéYou added Raza Zaidi",
    "answer": "Give a few days",
    "timestamp": "2021-12-12T20:38:08",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hello what is the update on the ps",
    "answer": "Sadaf will discuss comments with you shortly today",
    "timestamp": "17/12/2021, 12:33:33‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Perfect",
    "answer": "Update ?",
    "timestamp": "17/12/2021, 12:36:56‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Working on it",
    "answer": "when can i expect",
    "timestamp": "20/12/2021, 8:51:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hopefully by tonight",
    "answer": "waiting",
    "timestamp": "21/12/2021, 12:05:22‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will try my best to complete it today so sorry for the delay",
    "answer": "Pls this is important",
    "timestamp": "24/12/2021, 7:26:41‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Please acknowledge you have received it",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "28/12/2021, 8:26:50‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://my.ieltsessentials.com/IELTS Please get yourself registered from here and select academic ielts",
    "answer": "Have you registered ?",
    "timestamp": "2022-04-01T13:58:01",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thank you",
    "answer": "üëå",
    "timestamp": "2022-10-01T15:17:02",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hey Rizwan, UCAS has been completed from my end. Please review it once and let me know. Thank you.",
    "answer": "Hamda get authorisation forms signed from him",
    "timestamp": "17/01/2022, 3:16:35‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are these?",
    "answer": "Uni forms ‚Äé[17/01/2022, 6:08:08‚ÄØPM] Hamda Khan Dignosco: Durham University.pdf ‚Ä¢ ‚Äé1 page ‚Äédocument omitted ‚Äé[17/01/2022, 6:08:09‚ÄØPM] Hamda Khan Dignosco: Warwick - Steps.pdf ‚Ä¢ ‚Äé1 page ‚Äédocument omitted",
    "timestamp": "17/01/2022, 5:11:55‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Asad please check your email you must have received an email from kings. Please accept and confirm once done",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Asad Bilwani‚Å© [Image] ‚Äé[19/01/2022, 11:34:15‚ÄØPM] Asad Bilwani: ‚Äéimage omitted [Image]",
    "timestamp": "19/01/2022, 9:59:41‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why is this needed?",
    "answer": "For uni forms",
    "timestamp": "19/01/2022, 11:36:20‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Submitted too",
    "answer": "Any updates ??",
    "timestamp": "27/01/2022, 8:25:49‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "All applications have been submitted but haven‚Äôt heard back from any uni yet",
    "answer": "Any updates ?",
    "timestamp": "2022-04-02T14:08:19",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Not yet",
    "answer": "?",
    "timestamp": "2022-07-03T22:06:33",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I got an offer for LSE",
    "answer": "‚Ä¶.",
    "timestamp": "20/04/2022, 10:29:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "As per my parents wishes [Image]",
    "answer": "hope parents are happy",
    "timestamp": "20/04/2022, 10:31:00‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the next steps now",
    "answer": "Let‚Äôs discuss overall a call tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "20/04/2022, 10:32:11‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Kings and UCL both rejected",
    "answer": "It‚Äôs ok we have LSE which matters",
    "timestamp": "27/04/2022, 2:10:23‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "How come LSE, which is usually seen as a better school, sent an acceptance but kings and UCL didnt",
    "answer": "There‚Äôs never a straight answer",
    "timestamp": "27/04/2022, 2:13:13‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéYou added Saad Ahmed",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Saad Ahmed‚Å© guide on TB appointment",
    "timestamp": "26/07/2022, 2:20:53‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Student",
    "answer": "did u get the TB test date",
    "timestamp": "26/07/2022, 2:54:01‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "They‚Äôve scheduled me for 8 August",
    "answer": "Ok and I hope your bank account is in order",
    "timestamp": "2022-02-08T15:36:32",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you please send information on how to register for the ielts test",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Saad Ahmed‚Å©",
    "timestamp": "2022-08-08T18:25:32",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you please send the template for the affidavit of support [Image]",
    "answer": "For UK visa app please note that you have to mention your last ten year travel history. Please make sure that you put your travel history down on a word document. There is a separate question on travel to UK. Separate question for travel to Europe, America and Australia Separate question for travel to rest of the world. You will need to specify date of entry and exit, country travelled  and number of days in that particular year. Please compile this data from 2012-2022 asap so you donot waste time while completing the visa app.",
    "timestamp": "2022-09-08T21:28:41",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay will do thank you for informing",
    "answer": "offer unconditional ?",
    "timestamp": "14/08/2022, 9:52:00‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I received an email from ucas saying congratulations your place has been confirmed but I have not received any email from lse yet",
    "answer": "Ok so we‚Äôre still good",
    "timestamp": "18/08/2022, 1:15:34‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "What‚Äôs the next step",
    "answer": "email lee for cas",
    "timestamp": "18/08/2022, 1:21:35‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asad Bilwani",
    "student_phone": "+2429064562",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéYou created group ‚ÄúAsher Siddique apps‚Äù",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Zannirah Rehman‚Å©",
    "timestamp": "13/10/2023, 1:50:30‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "alright, please come at 4:30",
    "answer": "Nixor2024",
    "timestamp": "14/10/2023, 12:14:07‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok will meet him soon.",
    "answer": "Hey Asher",
    "timestamp": "17/10/2023, 8:21:32‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "will discuss it tonight and get back to you",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "18/10/2023, 10:03:58‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi, i was going through the list and we havent put UBC",
    "answer": "That‚Äôs not part of OUAC",
    "timestamp": "18/10/2023, 7:10:18‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "oh okay",
    "answer": "These are Ontario universities",
    "timestamp": "18/10/2023, 7:10:39‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "what documents do i need to get from school",
    "answer": "for now, submit the OUAC",
    "timestamp": "18/10/2023, 7:15:29‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "so no transcripts needed to submit it?",
    "answer": "For US universities they have to upload your teacher recommendations and counsellor report on common app",
    "timestamp": "18/10/2023, 7:16:03‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "OUAC has been submitted",
    "answer": "Ok great",
    "timestamp": "18/10/2023, 8:14:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "before namaz",
    "answer": "Hey Asher",
    "timestamp": "2023-02-11T18:08:35",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "should i come right now?",
    "answer": "Not today",
    "timestamp": "2023-07-11T17:15:58",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I think he‚Äôs already there",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© was there a meeting scheduled ?",
    "timestamp": "2023-07-11T17:45:39",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "he was a bit late, i met him for a few minutes for UC, but hes coming in again tomm.",
    "answer": "Ok thanks",
    "timestamp": "2023-07-11T17:47:20",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "2) specific details about the polio campaign (location, date, number of people helped, funding)",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Zannirah Rehman‚Å© whats the status of Ashers activities and forms for UC",
    "timestamp": "2023-09-11T17:30:06",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "research_opportunities"
  },
  {
    "question": "i can come in on saturday",
    "answer": "Asher",
    "timestamp": "17/11/2023, 12:34:48‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéYou added Harry Siddiqui",
    "answer": "Hey Asher",
    "timestamp": "23/11/2023, 10:35:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "i can come around 4",
    "answer": "ok come",
    "timestamp": "24/11/2023, 3:29:41‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "for uoft what do i select for english language in the course name",
    "answer": "What options is it showing [Image]",
    "timestamp": "15/12/2023, 10:25:11‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "english language",
    "answer": "So just put that",
    "timestamp": "15/12/2023, 10:31:48‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "and examination date would be may 2022",
    "answer": "yea if that's when u took it",
    "timestamp": "15/12/2023, 10:32:24‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "and for my economics grade what do i put in the as level part",
    "answer": "yes math is fine",
    "timestamp": "15/12/2023, 10:43:44‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "jan 10th",
    "answer": "can you write pending?",
    "timestamp": "15/12/2023, 10:45:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "nope",
    "answer": "what are options",
    "timestamp": "15/12/2023, 10:45:28‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "math we have a grade",
    "answer": "yea so econ",
    "timestamp": "15/12/2023, 10:47:37‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "and leave the grade box empty?",
    "answer": "yup",
    "timestamp": "15/12/2023, 10:49:02‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "for may 2024",
    "answer": "ok so you can add the predicted ones. what have they given",
    "timestamp": "15/12/2023, 10:52:56‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay",
    "answer": "what's Econ predicted rn",
    "timestamp": "15/12/2023, 10:53:36‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "C",
    "answer": "put the A level predicted for Math. for Econ see if we can leave empty for now",
    "timestamp": "15/12/2023, 10:53:51‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay",
    "answer": "if result improves predicted changes",
    "timestamp": "15/12/2023, 10:54:24‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "and what about cambridge pre u",
    "answer": "? ‚Äé[15/12/2023, 10:55:10‚ÄØPM] Asher Siddique: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "timestamp": "15/12/2023, 10:54:34‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "this isnt letting me choose an option",
    "answer": "what isnt",
    "timestamp": "15/12/2023, 10:57:02‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "pre u",
    "answer": "then if you can ignore",
    "timestamp": "15/12/2023, 10:57:33‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay",
    "answer": "if it lets you move forward",
    "timestamp": "15/12/2023, 10:58:35‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "and we dont have a predicted grade for urdu",
    "answer": "ok maybe you can get on a call with Zannirah on this tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "15/12/2023, 11:00:26‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "so will that make a difference",
    "answer": "see you don't have your Econ grade",
    "timestamp": "15/12/2023, 11:02:34‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay",
    "answer": "its only recommended for those who haven't taken retakes",
    "timestamp": "15/12/2023, 11:03:22‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay yes",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Zannirah Rehman‚Å© can you schedule a call",
    "timestamp": "15/12/2023, 11:03:49‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Maybe we should send to the UCs as well. Remember to discuss this tomorrow as well",
    "answer": "Yes send the sat score to UC also pls",
    "timestamp": "18/12/2023, 8:36:39‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôm at the office working on my common app. What else do i need to do",
    "answer": "Once you leave pls share common app login details",
    "timestamp": "19/12/2023, 5:13:00‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "You choose other and then write independent research",
    "answer": "hey Asher",
    "timestamp": "20/12/2023, 10:36:25‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "research_opportunities"
  },
  {
    "question": "4",
    "answer": "share your common app login",
    "timestamp": "20/12/2023, 11:49:38‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi what schools should i choose for rutgers",
    "answer": "arts sciences",
    "timestamp": "21/12/2023, 1:01:36‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© pleae advice him on management programs in UK he can target as well",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-01T15:18:51",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "career_guidance"
  },
  {
    "question": "Should Ashar do accelerated math ?",
    "answer": "I mean that‚Äôs A1 and A2 combined",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-01T15:55:06",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ashar thinks he can do it so I thought we will get a second opinion  from his counsellor",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-01T16:09:08",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "career_guidance"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay",
    "answer": "Hey pls have your portals checked",
    "timestamp": "15/01/2024, 11:34:46‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay",
    "answer": "pls come in tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "16/01/2024, 4:04:21‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "will do",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Zannirah Rehman‚Å© what time works",
    "timestamp": "16/01/2024, 4:05:42‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "are the transcripts to be submitted by the school",
    "answer": "yes ask school to submit them pls ‚Äé[31/01/2024, 8:00:31‚ÄØPM] Asher Siddique: Siddique_Ashar_1802715965 2.pdf ‚Ä¢ ‚Äé10 pages ‚Äédocument omitted ‚Äé[01/02/2024, 9:18:42‚ÄØPM] Asher Siddique: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "timestamp": "31/01/2024, 5:34:40‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéReham Aslam UK left",
    "answer": "Yes [Image]",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-02T13:12:37",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "toronto metropolitan",
    "answer": "What was program here",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-02T18:24:02",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "bachelor of commerce-business management",
    "answer": "The UK personal statement could be used",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-02T18:24:58",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay got jt",
    "answer": "Because that‚Äôs management",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-02T18:25:16",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "this is the only part to be altered",
    "answer": "Ok shouldn‚Äôt be an issue",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-02T18:29:21",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "is this done",
    "answer": "In search of answers, I aspire to study at Toronto Metropoliton University, renowned globally for its academic rigour, state of the art  research facilities and one of the most diverse International student body. ‚Äé[04/02/2024, 1:55:48‚ÄØPM] Asher Siddique: ‚Äéimage omitted ‚Äé[04/02/2024, 2:00:02‚ÄØPM] Asher Siddique: ‚Äéimage omitted ‚Äé[04/02/2024, 2:00:22‚ÄØPM] Asher Siddique: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-02T23:08:11",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay",
    "answer": "any update",
    "timestamp": "2024-04-02T14:18:23",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "SOAS condition BBB Westminster condition BBC",
    "answer": "üëçüëç",
    "timestamp": "13/02/2024, 9:04:45‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "queen mary rejected",
    "answer": "Amazing",
    "timestamp": "27/02/2024, 3:54:37‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "york",
    "answer": "üëåüëå",
    "timestamp": "2024-07-03T21:00:02",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "uc davis and uc irvine rejected",
    "answer": "No worries",
    "timestamp": "2024-09-03T15:46:37",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "hi sorry just gathering all the decisions and updating u",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "24/03/2024, 9:29:51‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Asher Siddiqui",
    "student_phone": "+6782928923",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok üëç see you [Image] ‚Äé[17/09/2024, 10:38:37‚ÄØPM] Azhaan Saya: ‚Äéimage omitted ‚Äé[17/09/2024, 10:39:18‚ÄØPM] Azhaan Saya: ‚Äéimage omitted ‚Äé[17/09/2024, 10:39:44‚ÄØPM] Azhaan Saya: ‚Äéimage omitted ‚Äé[17/09/2024, 10:41:06‚ÄØPM] Azhaan Saya: ‚Äéimage omitted ‚Äé[17/09/2024, 10:42:01‚ÄØPM] Azhaan Saya: ‚Äéimage omitted ‚Äé[17/09/2024, 10:42:19‚ÄØPM] Azhaan Saya: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "answer": "ill review and tell you which one to pick in the morning",
    "timestamp": "16/09/2024, 4:12:00‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes sire",
    "answer": "thanks",
    "timestamp": "17/09/2024, 10:42:59‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://www.coursera.org/courseraplus/special/global-thirty-2024?utm_source=gg&utm_medium=sem&utm_campaign=b2c_apac_coursera-plus_coursera_ftcof_subscription_arte_dec-23_dr_geo-pk_sem_rsa_gads_lg-all&utm_content=b2c&campaignid=20882940687&adgroupid=160111577194&device=c&keyword=coursera&matchtype=e&network=g&devicemodel=&adpostion=&creativeid=711600631579&hide_mobile_promo&gad_source=1&gclid=CjwKCAjw0aS3BhA3EiwAKaD2ZVIRa8xchQaIFNh76VyC4HQeRL6yYJJ9S_JEABQQgKoUxamePKWg2hoCX0IQAvD_BwE",
    "answer": "yes that would be solid",
    "timestamp": "17/09/2024, 10:44:08‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "No it‚Äôs not needed for the UK application",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Azhaan Saya‚Å© do the become an entrepreneur one first",
    "timestamp": "17/09/2024, 10:51:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Azhaan Saya‚Å©",
    "timestamp": "18/09/2024, 3:03:52‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "Azhaan can we meet tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "18/09/2024, 7:20:17‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yea sure what time",
    "answer": "4:30?",
    "timestamp": "23/09/2024, 12:45:36‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yea sure I‚Äôll be there",
    "answer": "great",
    "timestamp": "23/09/2024, 1:28:34‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "UCAS login : azhaansaya1@gmail.com Steve@7860",
    "answer": "Asa can we meet tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "24/09/2024, 5:10:26‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yea sure what time",
    "answer": "4:15?",
    "timestamp": "29/09/2024, 11:20:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "5",
    "answer": "Cool",
    "timestamp": "30/09/2024, 7:15:41‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "Hey, please be at the office on October 5, 2024. The head of International office from University of Edinburgh will be visiting our office from 1:45 PM till 3:15 PM. We will discuss program choices, location and any specific questions you may have pertaining to the university.",
    "timestamp": "30/09/2024, 7:40:51‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "It‚Äôs the UkVI academic on computer right",
    "answer": "Yes üëç [Image]",
    "timestamp": "30/09/2024, 10:43:28‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one should I choose",
    "answer": "UKVI",
    "timestamp": "30/09/2024, 10:44:36‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "What should I write for the ID issuing authority ??",
    "answer": "Pakistan",
    "timestamp": "30/09/2024, 10:57:34‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Faisal.saya@alrahimtextile.com",
    "answer": "Home addy",
    "timestamp": "30/09/2024, 11:08:54‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "And the spot for the test is reserved it‚Äôs on next Friday the 11th at 12:20",
    "answer": "okk",
    "timestamp": "30/09/2024, 11:09:59‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yea sure what time",
    "answer": "Azhaan",
    "timestamp": "2024-07-10T16:58:57",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I booked the test last week I was just updating the info",
    "answer": "yea cool",
    "timestamp": "2024-07-10T17:32:56",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "What time is the meeting with alvi and momin today one is saying 4:45 one‚Äôs saying 4",
    "answer": "4:30",
    "timestamp": "2024-09-10T09:29:30",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi guys I was just wondering when we would have a meeting so we can finalise dates for applications and schools lists as well as I need to inform my teacher for the recommendation she needs details of the stuff I‚Äôve done so I need to tell her specific details and I need to sort all of that out with you guys so I can make the necessary documents",
    "answer": "Hey Azhaan . Wanna do sat ?",
    "timestamp": "2024-10-10T17:40:51",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yea sure",
    "answer": "Hi the SOAS head of International office will be visiting our premises on Monday at 4:10PM Please come and attend the session. This will address all questions related to the university and the admissions process.",
    "timestamp": "2024-10-10T19:08:13",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can we do a bit earlier ??",
    "answer": "Let me coordinate time in a bit",
    "timestamp": "2024-11-10T21:22:56",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "We can do 2:30 ish ?",
    "timestamp": "2024-11-10T21:48:31",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yea sure I can come at 2:30",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "2024-12-10T11:16:20",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi guys I was just wondering how much would a really high sat score affect acceptance‚Äôs ‚Äé<This message was edited>",
    "answer": "Hey Azhaan for UK SAT plays a minimal role",
    "timestamp": "16/10/2024, 10:48:25‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "But what about for first year when I re apply ??",
    "answer": "Yea even then UK doesn‚Äôt ask",
    "timestamp": "16/10/2024, 10:59:07‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok thank you",
    "answer": "lets meet",
    "timestamp": "16/10/2024, 10:59:34‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi guys can you guys send me a picitre of my activity list I need to send it to my teacher for the recommendation",
    "answer": "I‚Äôll send shortly",
    "timestamp": "2024-01-11T12:46:58",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "They are due later didn‚Äôt miss anything",
    "answer": "Yea don‚Äôt worry",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-11T12:20:42",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "This is a typed out list of all my actives I‚Äôve added one and explained the passion project this way it‚Äôll be easier to put the activities on college apps",
    "answer": "amazing",
    "timestamp": "2024-05-11T19:36:26",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "Seeing you tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "2024-05-11T20:03:21",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi guys can we please do Tmr after 3 I completely forgot today",
    "answer": "Let me confirm",
    "timestamp": "2024-08-11T17:53:33",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yea sure what time",
    "answer": "ltes keep 4:30",
    "timestamp": "2024-10-11T15:20:43",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yea I took it I got a 7 should I take it again ?? ‚Äé[10/11/2024, 3:37:49‚ÄØPM] Azhaan Saya: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "answer": "no all ok for now",
    "timestamp": "2024-10-11T15:37:47",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one is that ?? ‚Äé<This message was edited>",
    "answer": "thats the official result u get through mail",
    "timestamp": "2024-10-11T15:41:46",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôm confused idk what you mean I‚Äôll bring my laptop on Tuesday and show it to you",
    "answer": "so they send an official result which has your picture etc",
    "timestamp": "2024-10-11T16:07:59",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "This is the only email I got with the results",
    "answer": "Keep checking you‚Äôll get . They mail the original through courier also",
    "timestamp": "2024-10-11T16:09:38",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi guys I just wanted to see what‚Äôs happening we still haven‚Äôt finalised majors and uni lists and when we have to apply as well as the personal statements I just want to finalise eveytbing because I will be travelling in late December so I‚Äôm not sure how that conflicts with the application due dates",
    "answer": "Hey Azhaan call me tomorrow I‚Äôll brief you",
    "timestamp": "24/11/2024, 8:51:50‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "Azhaan call me",
    "timestamp": "24/11/2024, 9:01:39‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "He should be there soon",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "13/12/2024, 4:37:29‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å©Hi guys I was just wondering what gpa do I need to make my application look strong because it‚Äôs not coming as what I was expecting and I was wondering where we‚Äôre at with the personal statement and other things for unis like kings and Warwick",
    "answer": "Above a 3.1- 3.2 atleast",
    "timestamp": "15/12/2024, 12:41:09‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "I think I‚Äôll end up with at 3.6 for this semester",
    "answer": "Let it come [Image]",
    "timestamp": "15/12/2024, 12:49:50‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can we set a meeting to discuss the personal statement and all the other things for applications",
    "answer": "Yup",
    "timestamp": "16/12/2024, 10:51:54‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yea sure",
    "answer": "https://www.kcl.ac.uk/study/international/courses/business-management-social-sciences",
    "timestamp": "17/12/2024, 7:39:04‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay what time",
    "answer": "Azhaan pls keep for tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "14/01/2025, 6:12:31‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yea sure what time",
    "answer": "4ish?",
    "timestamp": "15/01/2025, 3:49:09‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Earliest i can come is at 6:30",
    "answer": "Let sadaf confirm",
    "timestamp": "15/01/2025, 3:52:59‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "azhaansaya1@gmail.com",
    "answer": "Azhan come tomorrow so we submit icas",
    "timestamp": "17/01/2025, 11:11:55‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok what time ?",
    "answer": "4:30",
    "timestamp": "20/01/2025, 5:29:17‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© have the reply‚Äôs from Surrey and Sussex first year come back yet",
    "answer": "Let me follow up again",
    "timestamp": "2025-11-02T17:35:03",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes will do",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Azhaan Saya‚Å© when do u wanna come to wrap up Warwick",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-03T19:12:38",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I can come any time tmr also my dad wants to do a meeting with you aswell to talk about three year management options",
    "answer": "lets do midweek? ill confirm in a bit if im in tomorrow. if i am you can come",
    "timestamp": "2025-07-03T12:55:03",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://www.ucl.ac.uk/languages-international-education/preparation-courses/upc-foundation/your-future-degree/optional-subject-guide#index-c ‚Äé[14/05/2025, 11:27:30‚ÄØAM] Azhaan Saya: 78602932_27_05142025_112341_87384626.PDF ‚Ä¢ ‚Äé1 page ‚Äédocument omitted",
    "answer": "bro any update from Kings",
    "timestamp": "2025-12-05T15:57:41",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "No not yet",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "20/05/2025, 12:26:01‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Azhaan Saya",
    "student_phone": "+1422755606",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok perfect. Thanks",
    "answer": "Hamid pls copy the following in all your emails: Rizwan.javed@dignosco.org Sadaf.khan@dignosco.org Ata.rahman@dignosco.org Abrar.rahman@dignosco.org",
    "timestamp": "2018-07-06T17:38:46",
    "student_name": "Hamid Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8731584758",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok sure.",
    "answer": "Hamid can you use the resume guide, put your existing resume in the template and share",
    "timestamp": "2018-08-06T13:12:37",
    "student_name": "Hamid Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8731584758",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I was hoping to work together on my CV",
    "answer": "yes will start that",
    "timestamp": "2018-08-06T13:14:25",
    "student_name": "Hamid Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8731584758",
    "category": "career_guidance"
  },
  {
    "question": "Rizwan, free to talk on phone?",
    "answer": "Yes [Image]",
    "timestamp": "2018-08-06T13:15:29",
    "student_name": "Hamid Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8731584758",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Lemme know what you guys think. Thanks",
    "answer": "Hamid can you please email",
    "timestamp": "2018-08-06T16:46:27",
    "student_name": "Hamid Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8731584758",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sure",
    "answer": "Hey Hamid responded to your email",
    "timestamp": "2018-08-06T17:31:44",
    "student_name": "Hamid Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8731584758",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi. Yeah i rcvd it. Just wanted you to have a look at it before putting it in the format u sent. Ill send the revised to you hopefully by tomo. Thanks",
    "answer": "Ok cool, yes please do so we can start reviewing it comprehensively",
    "timestamp": "2018-09-06T00:12:48",
    "student_name": "Hamid Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8731584758",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi guys. I should be rcving my transcripts by 23rd hopefully. Ill try to have my cv complete by today. Whats next?",
    "answer": "Hamid please send the CV across",
    "timestamp": "2018-12-06T12:54:11",
    "student_name": "Hamid Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8731584758",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there anything else you need from me?",
    "answer": "also I‚Äôll check with Ata for a call with you this week",
    "timestamp": "2018-12-06T12:56:18",
    "student_name": "Hamid Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8731584758",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok. Any specific agenda where i need to gather documents before hand?",
    "answer": "Will discuss oxford app plus recs",
    "timestamp": "2018-12-06T12:57:27",
    "student_name": "Hamid Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8731584758",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tbh havent started prep",
    "answer": "I think registration is key",
    "timestamp": "2018-12-06T12:58:35",
    "student_name": "Hamid Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8731584758",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok. Ill register for 2nd of july",
    "answer": "great",
    "timestamp": "2018-12-06T12:59:34",
    "student_name": "Hamid Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8731584758",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi. Any updates?",
    "answer": "Hey will revert soon",
    "timestamp": "13/06/2018, 11:38:15‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Hamid Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8731584758",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will we be able to manage it by these dates?",
    "answer": "Hamid don‚Äôt think deadline is a problem. We have enough days, hopefully will get done with resume soon. Your discussion with Abrar will be on the essays plus recs",
    "timestamp": "13/06/2018, 1:55:43‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Hamid Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8731584758",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi guys. Any updates?",
    "answer": "Hamid Abrar will revert today",
    "timestamp": "19/06/2018, 1:59:27‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Hamid Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8731584758",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Guys, if i give my gmat on the 2nd (which is the last deadline for oxford), official report will be available after 20 days which is the 22nd. Is that going to be a problem?",
    "answer": "don‚Äôt think it‚Äôll be a major issue",
    "timestamp": "27/06/2018, 11:47:22‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Hamid Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8731584758",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "No issue",
    "answer": "Through email",
    "timestamp": "27/06/2018, 11:48:03‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Hamid Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8731584758",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok.",
    "answer": "Have you given any practise exams yet?",
    "timestamp": "27/06/2018, 11:50:24‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Hamid Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8731584758",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "No i have not",
    "answer": "you should do a few so you get an idea of score",
    "timestamp": "27/06/2018, 11:51:57‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Hamid Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8731584758",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yup",
    "answer": "plus test is 3 1/2 hour type",
    "timestamp": "27/06/2018, 11:52:40‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Hamid Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8731584758",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéSahrish Dignosco left",
    "answer": "Hi Hamid",
    "timestamp": "17/08/2018, 12:43:44‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Hamid Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8731584758",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thank you!! [Image]",
    "answer": "Great",
    "timestamp": "2019-10-04T16:17:39",
    "student_name": "Hamid Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8731584758",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéAbrar Rahman left [Image] [Image]",
    "answer": "Great",
    "timestamp": "29/05/2019, 2:40:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Hamid Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8731584758",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yup [Image]",
    "answer": "Congrats man",
    "timestamp": "2019-11-06T22:48:41",
    "student_name": "Hamid Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8731584758",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Leadership in Ismail Foundation Unilever Partnership on water projects starting in RYk [Image]",
    "answer": "Need to send the EA score and CV to LBS",
    "timestamp": "2023-08-04T14:12:09",
    "student_name": "Hamid Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8731584758",
    "category": "extracurriculars"
  },
  {
    "question": "Looks good to me",
    "answer": "Good to go",
    "timestamp": "2023-07-06T21:40:05",
    "student_name": "Hamid Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8731584758",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Let you know",
    "answer": "Amazing :))",
    "timestamp": "2023-06-07T22:32:27",
    "student_name": "Hamid Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8731584758",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚Äé~‚ÄØNavid Chamdia added you",
    "answer": "Thanks",
    "timestamp": "27/06/2019, 10:33:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Hamza chamdia",
    "student_phone": "+2578113664",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "passport scan",
    "answer": "Great can you share the documents as welll",
    "timestamp": "27/06/2019, 10:46:43‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Hamza chamdia",
    "student_phone": "+2578113664",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which documents?",
    "answer": "Ok no worries",
    "timestamp": "27/06/2019, 11:00:22‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Hamza chamdia",
    "student_phone": "+2578113664",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Great calling on Skype in two mins",
    "answer": "What‚Äôs the status on UCs",
    "timestamp": "2019-08-07T18:26:29",
    "student_name": "Hamza chamdia",
    "student_phone": "+2578113664",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Currently working on it",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "17/11/2019, 9:29:42‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Hamza chamdia",
    "student_phone": "+2578113664",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I have an interview for the university of Manchester tomorrow",
    "answer": "Ok gl",
    "timestamp": "17/11/2019, 9:30:04‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Hamza chamdia",
    "student_phone": "+2578113664",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "So I'll be sending those shortly",
    "answer": "Ok once you do please send them so we can work and close soon",
    "timestamp": "17/11/2019, 9:30:57‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Hamza chamdia",
    "student_phone": "+2578113664",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© in view of the current situation in the city can we postpone the meeting today?",
    "answer": "Maria that‚Äôs fine",
    "timestamp": "18/02/2020, 12:41:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Maria Shah Masters",
    "student_phone": "+2590091660",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thanks so much",
    "answer": "no issues",
    "timestamp": "18/02/2020, 12:43:55‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Maria Shah Masters",
    "student_phone": "+2590091660",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Would it be possible for me to come again and do a test tomorrow?",
    "answer": "yes you can come",
    "timestamp": "2020-04-03T13:00:48",
    "student_name": "Maria Shah Masters",
    "student_phone": "+2590091660",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôll print my own test.",
    "answer": "Sure",
    "timestamp": "2020-05-03T20:11:29",
    "student_name": "Maria Shah Masters",
    "student_phone": "+2590091660",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Please confirm",
    "answer": "@‚Å®~Maria Shah‚Å© kindly go through the website and share link here",
    "timestamp": "21/11/2021, 12:21:00‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Maria Shah Masters",
    "student_phone": "+2590091660",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéYou created group ‚ÄúMekail Aamir Apps‚Äù",
    "answer": "Hey Mekail we will use this group to communicate",
    "timestamp": "20/01/2024, 8:27:00‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What time",
    "answer": "Will coordinate time on Tuesday",
    "timestamp": "20/01/2024, 9:03:00‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the timings for the match?",
    "answer": "@923176557777 ?",
    "timestamp": "22/01/2024, 4:35:49‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi can i come in on saturday",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "timestamp": "25/01/2024, 11:06:06‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ill come by 3",
    "answer": "Ok ask Fida to give you the common app file",
    "timestamp": "27/01/2024, 12:28:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I have left",
    "answer": "ok cool",
    "timestamp": "27/01/2024, 3:56:15‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "When do we meet next",
    "answer": "IA in the coming week",
    "timestamp": "27/01/2024, 4:07:52‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tomorrow?",
    "answer": "Let sadaf revert",
    "timestamp": "29/01/2024, 1:07:37‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Should I do the SAT in april?",
    "answer": "It‚Äôs in March",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-02T08:52:12",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Should i do it?",
    "answer": "I think yes",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-02T09:22:37",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "No centre is available for the SAT",
    "answer": "Is there a waitlist",
    "timestamp": "2024-04-02T18:42:28",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok let me see",
    "answer": "Yea usually if you get a waitlist",
    "timestamp": "2024-04-02T18:47:37",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Great",
    "answer": "yes pls do. which sub do we compete in",
    "timestamp": "2024-06-02T21:35:30",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What else?",
    "answer": "Ok will ask sadaf and sort one soon",
    "timestamp": "2024-12-02T13:02:25",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is summer school useful in apps?",
    "answer": "Depends if it‚Äôs some experiential learning thing then yes",
    "timestamp": "2024-12-02T13:42:24",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "When r we meeting",
    "answer": "We can target Thursday or Friday",
    "timestamp": "13/02/2024, 10:10:50‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What time r we doing tomorrow",
    "answer": "will be post jumma",
    "timestamp": "15/02/2024, 4:25:08‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I had to be with my mom",
    "answer": "It‚Äôs ok we will just reschedule",
    "timestamp": "16/02/2024, 4:38:23‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "And theyre trying to help",
    "answer": "Ok but you need to make your you don‚Äôt miss it",
    "timestamp": "23/02/2024, 1:31:11‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "If its a problem from their end then i dont think they can not let me register",
    "answer": "Hmm",
    "timestamp": "23/02/2024, 1:31:53‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ill be looking at the other things today since i got free from test week",
    "answer": "Ok [Image]",
    "timestamp": "23/02/2024, 1:32:37‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you guys have initiatives",
    "answer": "When is this due",
    "timestamp": "23/02/2024, 7:43:03‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "extracurriculars"
  },
  {
    "question": "I recommend implementing a \"Community Tutoring Program,\" integrated as part of the current structure of the Peer Tutoring Society (PTS). The initiative aims to collaborate with institutions under the PTS, educating underprivileged children across Karachi, providing volunteer opportunities for students to teach subjects aligned with their interests. This presents a platform for students to contribute to our overall society‚Äôs betterment whilst also gaining a comprehensive appreciation of its members.",
    "answer": "are there any schools etc who have done community tutoring programs etc generall",
    "timestamp": "24/02/2024, 5:16:19‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "internships"
  },
  {
    "question": "Its just a brief descriptiom",
    "answer": "and could maybe narrow down a bit",
    "timestamp": "24/02/2024, 5:43:06‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ill try though",
    "answer": "Sure pls reshare one more draft",
    "timestamp": "24/02/2024, 5:43:25‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I tbink the best i could do is give an example",
    "answer": "i like the earlier version better",
    "timestamp": "24/02/2024, 10:46:32‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Its on june 1sy",
    "answer": "if you feel you can manage with AS then yea its cool",
    "timestamp": "26/02/2024, 11:51:27‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Nstc",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "29/02/2024, 11:28:48‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I know what topic will we be looking at",
    "answer": "Research about how incorporating Social Sciences and Liberal Arts (SSLA) curricula in education can foster critical thinking, empathy and tolerance thereby reducing susceptibility to extremist ideologies.",
    "timestamp": "2024-01-03T14:51:08",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "When do we start on this",
    "answer": "Coming week [Image]",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-03T15:45:08",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is this?",
    "answer": "some math comp",
    "timestamp": "2024-04-03T13:56:09",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Quantum mechanics for engineers 2 Money, markets and morals Entrepreneurship in emerging economies",
    "answer": "Share links",
    "timestamp": "27/03/2024, 12:47:25‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "He used this wensite and had a yale mentor help him",
    "answer": "Yea know about this",
    "timestamp": "27/04/2024, 6:32:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "And my dad and chacho r working with it",
    "answer": "Is it that digital bank ?!",
    "timestamp": "25/06/2024, 5:32:25‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Since its building up right now",
    "answer": "Yea it‚Äôll be nice",
    "timestamp": "25/06/2024, 5:34:31‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "My moms trying to talk to them",
    "answer": "Hmm",
    "timestamp": "29/06/2024, 1:31:53‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Because its not my fault since they didnt write it",
    "answer": "Buy a pair of pants from near by",
    "timestamp": "29/06/2024, 1:36:15‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi shiraz im here",
    "answer": "Mekail",
    "timestamp": "2024-01-08T15:59:47",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Got 4A‚Äôs alhamdullilah",
    "answer": "MA",
    "timestamp": "13/08/2024, 10:41:46‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "People are saying I should get it written from dignosco and get it submitted from them cuz they prolly wont write a good one",
    "answer": "We don‚Äôt write recommendations",
    "timestamp": "2024-01-09T10:45:31",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can we have a meeting tomorrow",
    "answer": "When. Is sat out I also wanna discuss college list",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-09T09:06:45",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok that‚Äôs good. Let‚Äôs discuss about taking it again",
    "answer": "gg",
    "timestamp": "2024-06-09T16:39:47",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "I started 2 weeks ago this time",
    "answer": "As long as it doesn‚Äôt mess with your other stuff",
    "timestamp": "2024-06-09T18:26:22",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Its for some mun tuing but its till friday [Image]",
    "answer": "Solid stuff",
    "timestamp": "2024-10-09T16:08:55",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay no worries! Hope u feel better soon!",
    "answer": "Hayazahid@gmail.com",
    "timestamp": "16/09/2024, 6:04:28‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes sure",
    "answer": "@923333575290 lets also do his college list",
    "timestamp": "18/09/2024, 7:56:47‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you want we can do online any time today anything is fine with me",
    "answer": "pls share UCAS login",
    "timestamp": "23/09/2024, 2:15:59‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Perf! Will look in abit",
    "answer": "@923176557777 what do i review in your UCAS",
    "timestamp": "26/09/2024, 10:35:14‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "üëçüèΩ",
    "answer": "@923176557777 also discuss the resume thing with sadaf",
    "timestamp": "28/09/2024, 11:01:08‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Zoom user is inviting you to a scheduled Zoom meeting. Topic: Zoom user's Zoom Meeting Time: Sep 28, 2024 12:30 PM Asia/Karachi Join Zoom Meeting https://us05web.zoom.us/j/87862272806?pwd=QyPa5uvaNtf8TJyAItInREa7CPBvXE.1 Meeting ID: 878 6227 2806 Passcode: uwZz3r",
    "answer": "For now our strategy will be to trim to only an academic resume and the email",
    "timestamp": "28/09/2024, 11:01:36‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923176557777 please call me",
    "answer": "@923176557777 what‚Äôs the update on ucas recommendation",
    "timestamp": "29/09/2024, 6:50:34‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will give an update tom",
    "answer": "Has to be very thorough",
    "timestamp": "30/09/2024, 1:01:38‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok I shall",
    "answer": "also what about brown email",
    "timestamp": "30/09/2024, 1:28:28‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "He‚Äôs coming in at 3 today to finalise that",
    "answer": "k",
    "timestamp": "30/09/2024, 1:33:31‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "yea perfect [Image] [Image]",
    "answer": "Cool",
    "timestamp": "2024-01-10T06:08:54",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sure",
    "answer": "@923176557777 what are the other 4 uni choices",
    "timestamp": "2024-08-10T17:35:29",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yea we have other 3 but sadaf and I are yet to decide on the last one",
    "answer": "put the other 3 here",
    "timestamp": "2024-09-10T21:52:38",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yup doing it",
    "answer": "Which courses are we putting",
    "timestamp": "2024-09-10T21:56:31",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "LSE there is economics, econometrics and mathematical economics, and economics with economic history",
    "answer": "@923333575290 i am tilted towards option 3",
    "timestamp": "2024-09-10T21:57:48",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "That was already decided",
    "answer": "and UCL?",
    "timestamp": "2024-09-10T22:03:33",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Same! Or management",
    "answer": "have told him we will finalise these by midday kal",
    "timestamp": "2024-09-10T22:43:08",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923018379777 @923333575290 just need confirmed courses",
    "answer": "Yes by midday",
    "timestamp": "2024-10-10T08:11:28",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yess if there‚Äôs no qualms in doing economics then that‚Äôll be good",
    "answer": "@923176557777 call me",
    "timestamp": "2024-10-10T12:19:15",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "At school rn",
    "answer": "Ok waiting",
    "timestamp": "2024-10-10T13:12:13",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@14374840028 please discuss with me",
    "answer": "Mikael",
    "timestamp": "17/10/2024, 3:30:32‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "sure",
    "answer": "https://pjss.bzu.edu.pk/index.php/pjss/about/contact",
    "timestamp": "29/10/2024, 1:21:39‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "December 1st. And you would need to take ielts. Earlier you had said you didn‚Äôt want to. Just confirming",
    "answer": "Also have you completed the UC app I wanna review",
    "timestamp": "13/11/2024, 12:41:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Nope I shall do it soon",
    "answer": "Pls Yaar let‚Äôs wrap",
    "timestamp": "13/11/2024, 5:53:30‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "As discussed let‚Äôs get the next one ready by tomorrow",
    "answer": "have u sent sat scores",
    "timestamp": "16/11/2024, 6:14:45‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes",
    "answer": "cool",
    "timestamp": "18/11/2024, 6:55:20‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923018379777 please do final review on the UC app",
    "answer": "On it",
    "timestamp": "30/11/2024, 12:50:50‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is everything fine and ready to be submitted",
    "answer": "Yup",
    "timestamp": "30/11/2024, 1:03:47‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Submitted",
    "answer": "cool",
    "timestamp": "30/11/2024, 1:41:49‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Then padel 5-6",
    "answer": "Haaahh",
    "timestamp": "2024-12-12T18:29:55",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "But you need to do the work I gave you [Image]",
    "answer": "Hey we should submit Middlbury , Colby , northeastern tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "2024-12-12T19:00:07",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚Äé‚ÄéShiraz Ali Larik Canada changed their phone number to a new number. ‚ÄéTap to message or add the new number.",
    "answer": "ok to submit Penn, Dartmouth, CMU & Swarthmoe",
    "timestamp": "20/12/2024, 1:33:39‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Got in UMICH AH",
    "answer": "Amazing man",
    "timestamp": "25/01/2025, 9:46:00‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéRehab UK left",
    "answer": "Cheers @923176557777",
    "timestamp": "22/05/2025, 5:19:42‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thank you!!",
    "answer": "@923176557777 they‚Äôve shared version one of the video. But I have lots of issues, maybe you can have a look too, give some input and me and sadaf will be giving them comprehensive feedback tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "22/05/2025, 5:35:37‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "do i give ur guys‚Äô information",
    "answer": "Can give mine",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T15:24:52",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "says 2",
    "answer": "Can ask sadaf if she‚Äôs ok",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T15:25:17",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "dignoscos",
    "answer": "Yup",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T15:26:26",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sure you can give mine also [Image]",
    "answer": "This is your video. I honestly feel if we have your own voice over it‚Äôll be amazing",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-06T15:36:28",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yea sure",
    "answer": "Ok Aisha is calling you",
    "timestamp": "2025-03-07T14:56:35",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Haven‚Äôt come out since",
    "answer": "are they showing any dates",
    "timestamp": "2025-03-07T17:21:08",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Nope",
    "answer": "any one who got yet",
    "timestamp": "2025-03-07T17:22:02",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "He got them when they opened",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "2025-03-07T17:22:39",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Perfect",
    "answer": "buddy can ya send the voice over",
    "timestamp": "2025-03-07T17:33:35",
    "student_name": "Mikael Amir",
    "student_phone": "+8176765490",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéYou created group ‚ÄúMikael Rafay Apps‚Äù",
    "answer": "Hi the SOAS head of International office will be visiting our premises on Monday at 4:10PM Please come and attend the session. This will address all questions related to the university and the admissions process.",
    "timestamp": "2024-10-10T23:05:33",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok I will be there",
    "answer": "reminder for tom",
    "timestamp": "2024-11-10T20:33:40",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tomorrow I‚Äôm going to court",
    "answer": "ok lets meet saturday",
    "timestamp": "15/10/2024, 2:05:21‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hello, for the US colleges I will be using common app right?",
    "answer": "yup",
    "timestamp": "16/10/2024, 3:25:00‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many recommenders do I need",
    "answer": "2 teacher",
    "timestamp": "16/10/2024, 3:25:09‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I come in tomorrow",
    "answer": "ok cool",
    "timestamp": "16/10/2024, 3:25:32‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "Let‚Äôs do 4pm",
    "timestamp": "16/10/2024, 3:25:48‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can we do 5?",
    "answer": "Ok üëç",
    "timestamp": "16/10/2024, 10:01:28‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok Thankyou",
    "answer": "hey mikael",
    "timestamp": "16/10/2024, 10:01:43‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hello",
    "answer": "'when u travelling",
    "timestamp": "23/10/2024, 9:54:54‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I am in Doha right now",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "23/10/2024, 9:56:22‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "hey you back?",
    "timestamp": "23/10/2024, 9:56:48‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes just got back",
    "answer": "lets meet fri",
    "timestamp": "29/10/2024, 11:56:48‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "3:45?",
    "timestamp": "30/10/2024, 12:06:16‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "cool",
    "timestamp": "2024-01-11T13:44:07",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Im here",
    "answer": "Come in",
    "timestamp": "2024-01-11T16:19:55",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "will be for UK apps",
    "timestamp": "2024-10-11T15:15:07",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôm getting my transcript tomorrow",
    "answer": "OK",
    "timestamp": "2024-10-11T15:16:24",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I come at 4:30 I have to drop My sister home from school",
    "answer": "Ok ‚Äé[19/11/2024, 4:54:51‚ÄØPM] Sadaf Khan: Brainstorming Round 1.docx ‚Ä¢ ‚Äé1 page ‚Äédocument omitted",
    "timestamp": "19/11/2024, 3:28:06‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "When should I come in next",
    "answer": "Come tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "25/11/2024, 10:20:19‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay what time?",
    "answer": "Anytime",
    "timestamp": "25/11/2024, 10:20:36‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "Mikael",
    "timestamp": "27/11/2024, 8:48:37‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "i can get the unoffical transcript from last quarter i sent you",
    "answer": "ok send that and the last 3 year ones too",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-12T10:52:59",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "Waiting",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-12T15:47:30",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "But I can skip it if I can‚Äôt come after",
    "answer": "lets target 4PM tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "2024-09-12T12:52:24",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "need to add NYU, Penn state and Ohio state to the list",
    "timestamp": "2024-09-12T13:09:28",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "mikailrafay08@gmail.com",
    "answer": "https://www.kcl.ac.uk/study/international/courses/liberal-arts-social-sciences",
    "timestamp": "13/12/2024, 7:27:02‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes will share in a couple of days",
    "answer": "also wer are Not doing GW",
    "timestamp": "24/12/2024, 2:44:42‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Have shared UVA supplement. @‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å©",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "25/12/2024, 1:14:23‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Not yet",
    "answer": "he will do today",
    "timestamp": "28/12/2024, 1:01:53‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "And I‚Äôll add it",
    "answer": "ok message when done",
    "timestamp": "28/12/2024, 1:11:02‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "??",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "28/01/2025, 8:22:54‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "3:30?",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "28/01/2025, 8:23:06‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "so im a little confused about that",
    "answer": "We should amend",
    "timestamp": "28/01/2025, 2:54:50‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Anytime",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Hira Zubair Fellow‚Å© we need to call him tomorrow to draft an email for SOAS",
    "timestamp": "29/01/2025, 12:26:41‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "Hello",
    "timestamp": "2025-12-06T23:49:28",
    "student_name": "Mikael Rafay",
    "student_phone": "+4963500345",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéYou're now an admin",
    "answer": "Hamda pls schedule a zoom session with Sadaf for this week",
    "timestamp": "20/06/2021, 1:14:51‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://www.kcl.ac.uk/study/postgraduate/taught-courses/dental-public-health-msc Dental public health program - KCL",
    "answer": "https://www.kcl.ac.uk/study/postgraduate/taught-courses/global-health-msc",
    "timestamp": "23/06/2021, 4:27:44‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://gradschool.cornell.edu/financial-support/tuition-rates/ It says 39k on their website",
    "answer": "Yes that‚Äôs Tution, plus living is roughly 25k at Cornell per annum",
    "timestamp": "23/06/2021, 4:42:16‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ohh",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "timestamp": "23/06/2021, 4:46:21‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi Can we schedule another meeting?",
    "answer": "Yes will do soon",
    "timestamp": "24/06/2021, 2:58:13‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "And I couldn‚Äôt find any health admin programs in northeastern or BU",
    "answer": "Look at University of Illinois Chicago",
    "timestamp": "24/06/2021, 3:05:49‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "career_guidance"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yeah I did",
    "answer": "Also look at Urbana Champagne",
    "timestamp": "24/06/2021, 3:07:27‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "There‚Äôs a dental public health program at UCL that I‚Äôm interested in",
    "answer": "share link",
    "timestamp": "24/06/2021, 3:08:09‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "research_opportunities"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also, There‚Äôs MHA program in UNC",
    "answer": "Share link",
    "timestamp": "24/06/2021, 3:09:42‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "research_opportunities"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://sph.unc.edu/hpm/hpm-residentialmha/",
    "answer": "ok will have a look in a while",
    "timestamp": "24/06/2021, 3:12:25‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hey What about our meeting today?",
    "answer": "Hey Misbah I will speak to you in just a bit",
    "timestamp": "26/06/2021, 3:07:05‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okayy",
    "answer": "Misbah tried calling earlier but couldn‚Äôt get through",
    "timestamp": "26/06/2021, 3:10:39‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sorry I missed your call",
    "answer": "I had called again today but couldn‚Äôt get through",
    "timestamp": "26/06/2021, 6:08:20‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "Join Zoom Meeting https://us04web.zoom.us/j/73353345457?pwd=NWFXRWFzTDJaYUFBb0tMclJic2ZUZz09 Meeting ID: 733 5334 5457 Passcode: 0HuzPm",
    "timestamp": "28/06/2021, 12:47:11‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://www.bu.edu/sph/education/degrees-and-programs/master-of-public-health-programs/",
    "answer": "https://www.kcl.ac.uk/study/postgraduate/apply/entry-requirements/international#P",
    "timestamp": "28/06/2021, 3:49:37‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Rizwan.javed@dignosco.org",
    "answer": "reverted",
    "timestamp": "28/06/2021, 4:58:21‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "All my undergrad transcripts? Or just the final year one?",
    "answer": "entire 4 years",
    "timestamp": "28/06/2021, 8:25:40‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôve sent the email",
    "answer": "ok cool",
    "timestamp": "28/06/2021, 8:31:21‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Got an email from ucl I Have forwarded it to you",
    "answer": "Ok will have a look at it shortly",
    "timestamp": "30/06/2021, 4:18:23‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes and can you please take a look at these",
    "answer": "will do later. today",
    "timestamp": "2021-05-07T12:43:34",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://www.lse.ac.uk/study-at-lse/Graduate/degree-programmes-2021/MSc-Global-Health-Policy",
    "answer": "Ok will have a look soon",
    "timestamp": "2021-07-07T16:10:42",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://www.wes.org/advisor-blog/pakistani-degree-evaluation/",
    "answer": "Pls start this process and do it",
    "timestamp": "2021-08-07T13:51:36",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is the meeting still on?",
    "answer": "Misbah sorry will speak on Saturday",
    "timestamp": "15/07/2021, 3:53:01‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi Can you please take a look at this And can we schedule a zoom meeting for Monday?",
    "answer": "Hey yes",
    "timestamp": "17/07/2021, 7:05:46‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi What about our meeting today?",
    "answer": "Hey yes in ten min",
    "timestamp": "27/07/2021, 3:19:07‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": ".",
    "answer": "Boston Univeristy",
    "timestamp": "27/07/2021, 4:02:30‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi Are we going to have a zoom meeting today?",
    "answer": "MYbe later today else tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "31/07/2021, 3:37:25‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay Please let me know the time",
    "answer": "2pm?",
    "timestamp": "31/07/2021, 3:42:57‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Suffolk university-mha",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "2021-01-08T14:09:04",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "For which universities?",
    "answer": "Suffolk and Texas a&m",
    "timestamp": "2021-01-08T15:21:23",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can we speak today?",
    "answer": "will speak either later today or tomorrow for sure",
    "timestamp": "2021-02-08T15:38:02",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes",
    "answer": "Ok will send you link shortly",
    "timestamp": "2021-03-08T12:16:34",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Deadlines: Ohio state and university of minnesota: priority deadline Dec 1 University of washington: Jan 15 Boston University : priority deadline Jan 15 John hopkins: rolling admissions.Deadline Jan 15",
    "answer": "Ok let‚Äôs start with Ohio first",
    "timestamp": "2021-03-08T15:12:05",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôm on it",
    "answer": "Hmm",
    "timestamp": "2021-03-08T17:45:45",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "MHA",
    "answer": "So health services management and policy is the only thing we need to see",
    "timestamp": "2021-03-08T17:47:18",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes",
    "answer": "Does it get covered in any capacity in your UG degree ?",
    "timestamp": "2021-03-08T17:49:08",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "No I don‚Äôt think so",
    "answer": "I would also suggest manybe you can do an online course around this",
    "timestamp": "2021-03-08T17:49:37",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "There are biostatistics courses online [Image]",
    "answer": "Check Edx ‚Äé[03/08/2021, 5:52:24‚ÄØPM] Misbah Asif Grad: 047340.pdf ‚Ä¢ ‚Äé4 pages ‚Äédocument omitted",
    "timestamp": "2021-03-08T17:50:48",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "Transcripts",
    "answer": "Misbah Mail is fine",
    "timestamp": "2021-03-08T17:52:33",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "All the universities require a personal statement Only BU has mentioned specific questions that need to be answered in the statement",
    "answer": "Ok great",
    "timestamp": "2021-05-08T14:51:39",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "And I‚Äôve been going through online courses",
    "answer": "Where she will guide you on how to put an essay together",
    "timestamp": "2021-05-08T14:52:33",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "extracurriculars"
  },
  {
    "question": "Both ohio state and minnesota require basic courses in accounting , stats and microeconomics",
    "answer": "have u emailed them",
    "timestamp": "2021-05-08T14:54:38",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "Courses*",
    "answer": "id say do both pls",
    "timestamp": "2021-05-08T15:00:53",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "Just Got a reply from ohio state I have forwarded it to you",
    "answer": "Ok I‚Äôve seen it",
    "timestamp": "2021-06-08T23:52:38",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© can you please schedule a zoom with her for PS",
    "timestamp": "2021-07-08T00:04:19",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Got an email  from university of Minnesota I have forwarded it to you",
    "answer": "Read it",
    "timestamp": "2021-10-08T19:22:45",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi Can we speak today? @‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å©",
    "answer": "hey lets keep tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "16/08/2021, 2:08:27‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "whats the update on PS",
    "timestamp": "16/08/2021, 2:09:26‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "Hey did you guys speak",
    "timestamp": "27/08/2021, 4:34:30‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Please work on revised draft as discussed and @‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© do have a chat with her when you can as she wants to alter her colleges and consider getting some funding as well. I have highlighted that will be difficult within the US",
    "answer": "Funding scene is not gonna work",
    "timestamp": "2021-01-09T21:14:23",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi @‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© Can we speak today?",
    "answer": "Hi we can on Saturday",
    "timestamp": "2021-02-09T12:54:17",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "Hey we can speak today",
    "timestamp": "2021-02-09T13:22:15",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi Sorry I just saw your message Can you please suggest another time that‚Äôs convenient for you",
    "answer": "Hey I‚Äôll check if not today then tomorrow iA",
    "timestamp": "2021-04-09T13:24:14",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okayy",
    "answer": "Free to chat ?",
    "timestamp": "2021-04-09T15:44:38",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I call you now?",
    "answer": "Misbah I‚Äôm free in the mornings",
    "timestamp": "2021-07-09T14:53:49",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I have patients till 2 pm",
    "answer": "Ok let‚Äôs do it later in the evening today on a call",
    "timestamp": "2021-07-09T14:56:39",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Let‚Äôs keep the meeting in the evening",
    "answer": "you can call me post 7",
    "timestamp": "2021-07-09T14:58:00",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I call you now?",
    "answer": "pls share the essay for uni of washington",
    "timestamp": "2021-07-09T19:07:23",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôm still working on the changes that need to be made Will share it in a day or two",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "2021-08-09T15:25:13",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "I will send it tonight Haven‚Äôt had the chance to finish the book so still need to make some changes",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "13/09/2021, 3:18:47‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi I would like to apply to some of your partner universities for spring intake as well Can you please let me know the relevant programs",
    "answer": "Yes can",
    "timestamp": "17/09/2021, 7:21:34‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "hey what have u been up 2",
    "timestamp": "17/09/2021, 7:34:26‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôll be taking the GRE next week",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "20/09/2021, 2:52:56‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://www.imperial.ac.uk/business-school/programmes/msc-international-health-management/admissions/entry-requirements/ Can we also start working on the application for this program",
    "answer": "Let‚Äôs do the ones we agreed on pls",
    "timestamp": "20/09/2021, 3:01:20‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "We decided to go for kings and university of washington first But can we work on this next?",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "20/09/2021, 3:17:17‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "USA Options, Suffolk University Hofstra University of South Carolina University of Dayton American University Adelphi University DePaul University - Public health Texas A&M Corpus Christi University - Healthcare administration",
    "answer": "should target DePaul and AU for sure",
    "timestamp": "20/09/2021, 3:27:48‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "U can search them on google",
    "answer": "Hamda best if you can share the links",
    "timestamp": "20/09/2021, 3:42:22‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Hamda Khan Dignosco‚Å© Can you share UK options also",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Hamda Khan Dignosco‚Å©",
    "timestamp": "27/09/2021, 6:37:28‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://www.ed.ac.uk/studying/postgraduate/degrees/index.php?r=site/view&edition=2021&id=933",
    "answer": "Misbah which one are you working on abhi",
    "timestamp": "29/09/2021, 3:07:03‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Btw I‚Äôll get my consolidated marksheet and provisional certificate by 20th oct",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "29/09/2021, 3:18:06‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes have reviewed will have a meeting or call set up",
    "answer": "Sadaf can you please set a meeting with her",
    "timestamp": "2021-06-10T13:13:28",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Misbah Asif Grad‚Å© have emailed PS with comments. Need to cater this draft to a particular college. Please decide which one",
    "answer": "Misbah have a call with me later today to sort",
    "timestamp": "13/10/2021, 11:43:48‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hey @‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© Can we speak today? There are certain things I‚Äôd like to discuss",
    "answer": "sure",
    "timestamp": "21/10/2021, 2:29:46‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I took the gre today Got 302",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "2021-02-11T15:17:32",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Btw what are the preferred scores And should I retake the gre?",
    "answer": "Should retake",
    "timestamp": "2021-02-11T18:20:03",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "Misbah we need to finalise the uni list now",
    "timestamp": "2021-02-11T18:24:20",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Penn state",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "2021-02-11T18:56:09",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "And the partner universities Edinburgh AU and de paul",
    "answer": "Ok @‚Å®Hamda Khan Dignosco‚Å© please let‚Äôs apply to AU and DePaul asap",
    "timestamp": "2021-02-11T19:15:53",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "For what program?",
    "answer": "Please share options around healthcare [Image] [Image] [Image]",
    "timestamp": "2021-02-11T19:48:30",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "And LSE",
    "answer": "Edinburgh is part of the normal ones",
    "timestamp": "2021-02-11T19:56:00",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Let‚Äôs go with LSE then",
    "answer": "Also where are we with the personal statement",
    "timestamp": "2021-02-11T20:01:16",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also, are we applying for the fall 2022 or Spring 2022?",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Hamda Khan Dignosco‚Å© fall",
    "timestamp": "2021-03-11T13:05:03",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "Hello what‚Äôs the status",
    "timestamp": "29/11/2021, 12:31:07‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi just an update will give the supplement at the end of the day",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Hamda Khan Dignosco‚Å© have we put apps in any partner universities yet",
    "timestamp": "2021-07-12T09:54:47",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "We have submitted American University Depaul Also, Misbah have you created KCL portal? Please confim",
    "answer": "Any update from them",
    "timestamp": "2021-07-12T12:01:52",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "I haven‚Äôt yet",
    "answer": "hamda why dont we make the account through r portal",
    "timestamp": "2021-07-12T14:35:44",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes",
    "answer": "Hey what‚Äôs the update so far",
    "timestamp": "2021-07-12T15:19:15",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi When are we planning to submit Washington application?",
    "answer": "What‚Äôs the status of essay",
    "timestamp": "24/12/2021, 7:41:55‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi I have completed the washington application Can you please review it Id- misbahasif909@gmail.com Password- 23december+ https://webapps.grad.uw.edu/applForAdmiss/login.aspx",
    "answer": "Yes will do shortly",
    "timestamp": "2022-04-01T15:09:03",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Btw I also got this email from AU [Image]",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Hamda Khan Dignosco‚Å©",
    "timestamp": "19/01/2022, 2:42:07‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay sure [Image] [Image]",
    "answer": "Update ?",
    "timestamp": "20/01/2022, 7:40:13‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Hamda Khan Dignosco‚Å© Are you going to submit this app through your portal?",
    "answer": "Hamda pls can you share the pdf so I can review",
    "timestamp": "23/01/2022, 2:00:41‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "you'll have to login",
    "answer": "Ok share details I‚Äôll just review soon",
    "timestamp": "23/01/2022, 2:28:43‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "ID: misbah-90@hotmail.com Password: misbah12*",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "23/01/2022, 2:44:25‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok will do that",
    "answer": "üëç",
    "timestamp": "23/01/2022, 3:20:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Misbah please prepare Warwick application for submission. I will send statement to you later tonight or early morning",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Hamda Khan Dignosco‚Å© make sure authorisation forms are signed",
    "timestamp": "26/01/2022, 5:41:43‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Please review her app once you are free",
    "answer": "Ok I‚Äôll do it in a bit",
    "timestamp": "27/01/2022, 6:48:49‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok cool Rizwan will have a look when free",
    "answer": "Will do today",
    "timestamp": "29/01/2022, 1:16:54‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://www.lse.ac.uk/study-at-lse/Graduate/degree-programmes-2022/MSc-International-Health-Policy",
    "answer": "Pls submit",
    "timestamp": "29/01/2022, 1:29:43‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôve submitted the application",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "30/01/2022, 7:35:38‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi I got an email from university of Washington [Image]",
    "answer": "That is amazing",
    "timestamp": "2022-06-02T20:02:05",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Now how to prepare for this interview",
    "answer": "Will help you [Image]",
    "timestamp": "2022-06-02T20:18:44",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "internships"
  },
  {
    "question": "What should I do next?",
    "answer": "Give her some slots which work for you",
    "timestamp": "2022-07-02T21:21:33",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay Can I include saturdays ?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "timestamp": "2022-07-02T21:59:22",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "extracurriculars"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay thanks [Image]",
    "answer": "Ok let‚Äôs speak today or tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "2022-07-02T22:03:34",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôll call you tomorrow around 7 pm And I‚Äôm taking the gre tom Should I send score reports to universities right after the exam?",
    "answer": "Yea",
    "timestamp": "2022-09-02T15:26:44",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© can I have a call with you today? And what time ?",
    "answer": "Yes you can call me today at 7:15",
    "timestamp": "2022-11-02T09:08:40",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi @‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© can you please review this and let me know if I need to add anything else",
    "answer": "Why is it important to me should include how this masters will help you achieve your ultimate goals of improving the Public health systems in Pak",
    "timestamp": "2022-12-02T20:57:03",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôve completed the application Please review @‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å©",
    "answer": "I‚Äôll do it later today",
    "timestamp": "13/02/2022, 3:40:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "is the program at Imperial",
    "timestamp": "13/02/2022, 4:23:35‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "No I haven‚Äôt The documents ps and references have to be uploaded after submitting the application",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "14/02/2022, 2:10:51‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Then I‚Äôll have to enter the planned date",
    "answer": "so do it",
    "timestamp": "14/02/2022, 2:12:38‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay ‚Äé[17/02/2022, 11:29:10‚ÄØAM] Misbah Asif Grad: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "answer": "can be anything about u which is not copvered in any other part of the app",
    "timestamp": "14/02/2022, 2:14:20‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay thanks [Image] [Image]",
    "answer": "Yes apply for sure",
    "timestamp": "18/02/2022, 7:22:55‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay [Image]",
    "answer": "It‚Äôs ok",
    "timestamp": "23/02/2022, 2:39:37‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Please review I‚Äôve completed the application",
    "answer": "Ok will do tomorrow morning",
    "timestamp": "25/02/2022, 6:12:41‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi Have you reviewed lse application @‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å©",
    "answer": "No will do today",
    "timestamp": "28/02/2022, 8:02:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also what about my partner college applications?",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Hamda Khan Dignosco‚Å© what‚Äôs the update",
    "timestamp": "28/02/2022, 8:04:07‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "I have sent a reminder email",
    "answer": "ok ive reviewed",
    "timestamp": "28/02/2022, 8:57:07‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "They need the degree and IELTS [Image] [Image]",
    "answer": "Please help complete all discrepancies [Image]",
    "timestamp": "2022-01-03T08:41:28",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "This is for AU right What about de paul?",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Hamda Khan Dignosco‚Å© [Image] ‚Äé[03/03/2022, 10:34:25‚ÄØAM] Hamda Khan Dignosco: DePaul Student Declaration Form Draft 7 Aug 2019.docx ‚Äédocument omitted",
    "timestamp": "2022-03-03T00:12:57",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "we submitted the kings app in jan When can we expect a reply from them",
    "answer": "I can message and ask for update",
    "timestamp": "2022-03-03T11:29:11",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "Misbah",
    "timestamp": "2022-03-03T12:37:57",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôm planning to take the exam on 13th",
    "answer": "What‚Äôs your email",
    "timestamp": "2022-03-03T15:59:09",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "And since I‚Äôve gotten the ilelts result now so we can complete the partner college applications",
    "answer": "Sure [Image]",
    "timestamp": "21/03/2022, 7:11:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "The deadline for warwick is 13th I haven‚Äôt heard back from kings yet And even waiting for decision on lse second choice program What should I do",
    "answer": "What is warwick asking to pay",
    "timestamp": "2022-05-04T18:44:46",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "I‚Äôm sure they will never extend the deadline",
    "timestamp": "2022-05-04T20:41:02",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay let‚Äôs see [Image]",
    "answer": "Have we done Durham !",
    "timestamp": "2022-05-04T20:41:34",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What‚Äôs the update on other partner universities ?",
    "answer": "Where all have we applied can you pls list here",
    "timestamp": "2022-08-04T23:56:10",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "AU and depaul",
    "answer": "Ok I will check on AU tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "2022-08-04T23:57:42",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ilelts score report ^",
    "answer": "cool",
    "timestamp": "2022-09-04T00:09:41",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "and will have a call with you as well",
    "timestamp": "2022-09-04T00:10:12",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "When can we have a call?",
    "answer": "will call in just a bit",
    "timestamp": "2022-09-04T13:54:25",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "https://www.city.ac.uk/prospective-students/courses?query=health&meta_level_sand=postgraduate+taught+degree [Image]",
    "timestamp": "2022-09-04T13:57:47",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can we apply to queen mary?",
    "answer": "Yes can",
    "timestamp": "2022-11-04T21:01:36",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://www.qmul.ac.uk/postgraduate/taught/coursefinder/courses/global-public-health-and-policy-msc/",
    "answer": "Let me get back on this tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "2022-11-04T21:57:15",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "MPH is available in Adelphi",
    "timestamp": "2022-11-04T23:28:09",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://www.ucl.ac.uk/global-business-school-health/study/postgraduate-taught/msc-global-healthcare-management-routes Can you please review this program Can we apply to this now?",
    "answer": "This program is one of the tightest to crack",
    "timestamp": "13/04/2022, 12:47:42‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "research_opportunities"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can we apply to more universities now ?",
    "answer": "Let me revert with some options",
    "timestamp": "13/04/2022, 12:51:16‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Please review this one also https://www.lshtm.ac.uk/study/courses/masters-degrees/public-health",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "13/04/2022, 4:14:59‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "Sadaf let‚Äôs look at this one pls for her",
    "timestamp": "13/04/2022, 4:24:53‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok üëç",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© need update on her ps [Image]",
    "timestamp": "15/04/2022, 1:17:30‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Misbahasif909@gmail.com",
    "answer": "Misbah saad will email you an English test called idap",
    "timestamp": "21/04/2022, 3:45:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I just received a conditional offer from lse",
    "answer": "Wooow",
    "timestamp": "22/04/2022, 7:36:27‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôll forward the email",
    "answer": "üëç",
    "timestamp": "22/04/2022, 7:38:16‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "The deadline is 28th apr",
    "answer": "You‚Äôll massively weaken the case for visa imo",
    "timestamp": "22/04/2022, 7:39:24‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I have to submit transcript copy and ilelts score",
    "answer": "So that‚Äôs hardly a condition then",
    "timestamp": "22/04/2022, 7:46:25‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "There‚Äôs a small problem My name on the portal is Misbah Misbah Asif",
    "answer": "You can tell them to fix",
    "timestamp": "22/04/2022, 7:47:29‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Should I email them?",
    "answer": "Yup",
    "timestamp": "22/04/2022, 7:48:08‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi @‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© can we have a call ? I have some queries regarding the lse offer that I‚Äôd like to discuss",
    "answer": "Sure call me exactly at 1",
    "timestamp": "26/04/2022, 11:53:31‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Once offer is unconditional then you can apply for CAS [Image]",
    "answer": "Great",
    "timestamp": "23/05/2022, 12:23:10‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you please review",
    "answer": "Looks ok to me",
    "timestamp": "15/06/2022, 6:57:12‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "I got my cas letter",
    "answer": "Great",
    "timestamp": "20/06/2022, 7:10:34‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôve got my tb test appointment on 28th",
    "answer": "Nice",
    "timestamp": "20/06/2022, 7:13:19‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© My father spoke to the branch manager but they dont issue such certificates in dubai What should I do ?",
    "answer": "Then you proceed without",
    "timestamp": "2022-01-07T19:22:43",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "But my visa is valid till nov",
    "answer": "Yes it gets extended in uni",
    "timestamp": "27/07/2022, 10:00:19‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Misbah Asif Masters",
    "student_phone": "+8509112565",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéYou created group ‚ÄúMoiz Hasan Apps‚Äù",
    "answer": "Asa we will use this group to communicate",
    "timestamp": "15/09/2024, 1:16:44‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéYou added Hasan Ameer Saqlain",
    "answer": "Moiz let‚Äôs speak tomorrow to first discuss the ED and EA choices",
    "timestamp": "15/09/2024, 1:17:13‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Wsalam can we discuss the ED EA choices today since I‚Äôm off today and tomorrow I have school",
    "answer": "Ok let me see if evening is possible today",
    "timestamp": "15/09/2024, 1:40:09‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "Asa Moiz",
    "timestamp": "15/09/2024, 2:52:02‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Aoa Right now Moiz is taking Physics class,he will be free around 5:30 PST",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "15/09/2024, 5:07:22‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Moiz Hassan has invited you to join a video meeting on Google Meet. Join the meeting: https://meet.google.com/opy-upit-gct",
    "answer": "Sure gimme 5 min",
    "timestamp": "15/09/2024, 5:32:43‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "University of Rochester University of rhodes island St. Olaf Montclair State University Pace University Adelphi University Rowan University University of Miami (Miami, FL) fordham Molloy University Rice RIT Siena College hofstra Caldwell University Monmouth University Bloomfield College NYU Cornell Casewestern Northwestern bardnard northeastern [Image]",
    "answer": "please look at following choices for ED:",
    "timestamp": "15/09/2024, 5:42:04‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://admissions.rochester.edu/academics/rems/",
    "answer": "Early Action: 1. NorthEastern 2. Case Western 3. University of Wisconsin-Madison 4. Rutgers University",
    "timestamp": "15/09/2024, 5:59:45‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "In one minute",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "15/09/2024, 6:21:44‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Email: Moizhassan2007@icloud.com Password Hs@0567927116 ‚Äé<This message was edited>",
    "answer": "Also pls call me for a min",
    "timestamp": "15/09/2024, 6:26:17‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "BS/MD program im looking at the 3+4 MD program with St. George‚Äôs University",
    "answer": "Moiz lets agree on a time for tomorrow so Sadaf is also available",
    "timestamp": "15/09/2024, 6:45:28‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôm also available 6-7pm UAE time",
    "answer": "ok ill confirm in the morning",
    "timestamp": "15/09/2024, 10:33:18‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will send you the essays we discussed",
    "answer": "@‚Å®~Moiz‚Å© as we had discussed pls also share your weekly schedule of school and tuitions",
    "timestamp": "16/09/2024, 7:33:53‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "My classes change weekly",
    "answer": "will speak tomorrow.",
    "timestamp": "17/09/2024, 1:51:53‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "But for this week Tuesday: free after 5pm UAE time Wednesday:6-7pm UAE time I have class ‚Äé<This message was edited>",
    "answer": "and added some stuff",
    "timestamp": "17/09/2024, 1:52:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "ok will speak tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "17/09/2024, 1:53:08‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Salam! Yes sending shortly",
    "answer": "ASA",
    "timestamp": "17/09/2024, 8:14:55‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok what time?",
    "answer": "are you at school?",
    "timestamp": "18/09/2024, 11:21:26‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes at school",
    "answer": "sure let him message and ill coordinate atime",
    "timestamp": "18/09/2024, 11:46:22‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "After that he will be free",
    "answer": "i will coordinate with hime eithe before or after",
    "timestamp": "18/09/2024, 11:47:19‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sure ,he will be available at 6-7 PST",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "18/09/2024, 11:51:30‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "So 6-7pm pk time",
    "answer": "I‚Äôll call you 6pm pak time",
    "timestamp": "18/09/2024, 5:32:16‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "you can send the google meet link",
    "timestamp": "18/09/2024, 5:35:41‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "You can join this",
    "answer": "2 min ‚Äé[18/09/2024, 6:11:42‚ÄØPM] ~‚ÄØMoiz: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "timestamp": "18/09/2024, 6:00:32‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "extracurriculars"
  },
  {
    "question": "What time are we meeting?",
    "answer": "let Sadaf coordinate with you for the brainstorm",
    "timestamp": "19/09/2024, 5:46:22‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can we meet at these times?",
    "answer": "Let sadaf confirm",
    "timestamp": "20/09/2024, 2:02:32‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Salam can we meet for discussing activities today. I‚Äôm free from 10am-11am Uae time I have a class from 11am-1pm uae time And then I‚Äôm free from 1pm-3pm uae time",
    "answer": "WAS",
    "timestamp": "21/09/2024, 1:56:39‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok we can meet at 2:30-3:00pm uae time",
    "answer": "Can we do 3:00-3:30 UAE time",
    "timestamp": "21/09/2024, 1:53:32‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å©?",
    "answer": "I will still need 15 min",
    "timestamp": "21/09/2024, 3:15:04‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "sending link in 5 min",
    "timestamp": "21/09/2024, 3:31:03‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "Join Zoom Meeting https://us04web.zoom.us/j/79788995342?pwd=lalrNqKR953IZrv2dJNuSr6uQQwaMg.1 Meeting ID:  797 8899 5342 Passcode: M2L23q",
    "timestamp": "21/09/2024, 3:51:09‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also miss could you please send me some essays on the prompt \"why us\"",
    "answer": "i logged in your common app",
    "timestamp": "21/09/2024, 4:33:00‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sure I had to go out yesterday but I‚Äôm working on it right now",
    "answer": "cool",
    "timestamp": "22/09/2024, 3:12:06‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thanks have shared some sample NYU essays with you",
    "answer": "https://cssprofile.collegeboard.org/",
    "timestamp": "23/09/2024, 6:12:11‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôm free after 5:30pm UAE time",
    "answer": "let‚Äôs coordinate for Wednesday",
    "timestamp": "23/09/2024, 9:41:59‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "this is the neural science major at NYU website https://as.nyu.edu/departments/cns/UndergraduateProgram.html",
    "answer": "Asa",
    "timestamp": "25/09/2024, 12:18:36‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "Wsalam sure can we discuss at 7pm UAE time?",
    "answer": "can we do 6:30 your time pls",
    "timestamp": "26/09/2024, 2:33:27‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sure",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "26/09/2024, 2:36:30‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© can we start?",
    "answer": "WAS",
    "timestamp": "26/09/2024, 7:32:00‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://www.careeronestop.org/Toolkit/Training/find-scholarships.aspx?curPage=1&studyLevelfilter=High%20School&awardTypefilter=Scholarship",
    "answer": "Moiz once you make the changes in the actvities ill review today",
    "timestamp": "26/09/2024, 8:06:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Salam I‚Äôve completed that",
    "answer": "ok ill review at somepoint in the morning or later tonight",
    "timestamp": "27/09/2024, 2:48:11‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Salam mrs @‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© when can we meet today? ‚Äé<This message was edited>",
    "answer": "@‚Å®~Moiz‚Å© lets keep a meeting for tomorow to discuss your early choices with me pls",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-10T18:01:43",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "So would it be possible to meet today?",
    "answer": "Let sadaf revert . If not today can do tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "2024-05-10T20:52:37",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Salam what time will we meet today? I‚Äôm free from 4pm pak time.",
    "answer": "@‚Å®~Moiz‚Å© have you also added the honors in the education section",
    "timestamp": "2024-06-10T12:33:35",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes",
    "answer": "Ok and the grades etc",
    "timestamp": "2024-06-10T13:02:20",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes",
    "answer": "Ok I will review today",
    "timestamp": "2024-06-10T13:06:29",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Could you please go through it to let me know if i missed anything or need to restrcture anything?",
    "answer": "Will do today",
    "timestamp": "2024-09-10T01:31:29",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "I have to email the teachers by tonight",
    "answer": "WAS I will check in a bit",
    "timestamp": "2024-09-10T20:29:00",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "And for my computer science teacher:                     Academic participation: Could you please portray me as someone who is always inclined to help others. A specific example is when I noticed a few of my classmates struggling with iteration loops in pseudocode. I took the initiative to sit down with him after class, and explained it to him. Additionally, I had Zoom sessions with a few of my classmates outside of school to explain concepts like LED and LCD screens. By the end of these sessions, my classmates had fully understood the concepts. ‚Äé<This message was edited>",
    "answer": "üëç",
    "timestamp": "2024-10-10T00:21:43",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "extracurriculars"
  },
  {
    "question": "Salam miss @‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© can we meet today to discuss the other supplements?",
    "answer": "I believe it‚Äôll be tomorrow . She‚Äôs on a flight rn",
    "timestamp": "16/10/2024, 5:01:38‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok üëç Also what‚Äôs the next thing we have to do? I‚Äôve completed the supplemental, main and additional information essay. I‚Äôve made the activities it just has to be structured by the team. I‚Äôm made the CSS profile.",
    "answer": "Will review during the weekend",
    "timestamp": "16/10/2024, 7:12:50‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Salam miss @‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å©‚Ä¨‚Å© is it possible to meet today to discuss the essays, I‚Äôve completed university of rochesters both essays and baylors why us essay? I‚Äôm free after 8pm pk time. ‚Äé<This message was edited>",
    "answer": "I think she‚Äôs on a flight",
    "timestamp": "22/10/2024, 6:13:02‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "So I want to try to get the application ready within these days so could we arrange meeting tomorrow ? ‚Äé<This message was edited>",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "22/10/2024, 9:16:33‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hello, my C.S teacher wrote another draft with examples ‚Äé<This message was edited>",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "27/10/2024, 1:09:22‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "ok",
    "answer": "Good to go",
    "timestamp": "27/10/2024, 1:10:23‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Salam Sir @‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© and miss @‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© can we meet today to discuss the activities section and the honors?",
    "answer": "I can speak with you today",
    "timestamp": "28/10/2024, 5:16:26‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "extracurriculars"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok üëç",
    "answer": "We can speak in 15 min",
    "timestamp": "28/10/2024, 5:33:18‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "send link",
    "timestamp": "28/10/2024, 6:12:20‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Salam sir @‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© my CSS profile login details are moizhassan2007@icloud.com and password: Hs@0567927116 could you please check it",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "28/10/2024, 10:56:08‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "049109",
    "answer": "share code again",
    "timestamp": "29/10/2024, 1:04:19‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Salam can we meet to finalize the common app today and then submit it?",
    "answer": "Let‚Äôs keep it for tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "29/10/2024, 6:32:01‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© let‚Äôs coordinate submission for tomorrow",
    "answer": "Yup let‚Äôs do in afternoon and wrap this [Image]",
    "timestamp": "29/10/2024, 8:45:28‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "This applies to me correct?",
    "answer": "Pell grant is offered through fafsa",
    "timestamp": "29/10/2024, 11:28:39‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay but for now I‚Äôll just tick ‚Äúyes‚Äù?",
    "answer": "Yup",
    "timestamp": "29/10/2024, 11:48:36‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "WAS! Moiz had already reviewed it yesterday. Just did so again. You can coordinate with Rizwan and submit whenever you are ready",
    "answer": "Also Moiz we need to report SAT for NYU",
    "timestamp": "31/10/2024, 7:15:40‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "submitted?",
    "timestamp": "31/10/2024, 9:52:10‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Not yet I‚Äôm in school right now",
    "answer": "??",
    "timestamp": "31/10/2024, 3:22:27‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also dr Chung sat math for digital sat is a book to use along with Erica meltzer books for sat English digital version. You should be able to find online versions for these",
    "answer": "Moiz you dont wanna do UT Austin right?",
    "timestamp": "2024-07-11T06:51:16",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®~Moiz‚Å© can you speak today at 7:30/8 my time",
    "answer": "@‚Å®~Moiz‚Å©",
    "timestamp": "13/11/2024, 10:40:35‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I should have them done by the end of the weekend",
    "answer": "@‚Å®~Moiz‚Å© my suggestion is we start on Johns Hopkins",
    "timestamp": "14/11/2024, 9:18:53‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok üëç",
    "answer": "have u sent sat score to NYU",
    "timestamp": "18/11/2024, 12:36:40‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "That‚Äôs my only concern about UT Austin",
    "answer": "let it go",
    "timestamp": "18/11/2024, 7:03:32‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéThis message was deleted.",
    "answer": "any update om anything?",
    "timestamp": "19/11/2024, 2:35:31‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®~Moiz‚Å© please do this",
    "answer": "https://studentaid.gov/fsa-id/create-account/launch",
    "timestamp": "19/11/2024, 10:12:23‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thank you",
    "answer": "Moiz",
    "timestamp": "2024-06-12T23:12:21",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Salam I had one question if in every university I apply for financial aid won‚Äôt it be lowering my chances by a lot since I‚Äôm an international student applying for financial aid?",
    "answer": "It does but then when we have budget constraints we have to incorporate all of that",
    "timestamp": "17/12/2024, 8:15:18‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will it make any difference?",
    "answer": "So if you enhance your budget it obviously helps. Let me have a chat with you on this and give some suggestions",
    "timestamp": "17/12/2024, 9:16:48‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "can we speak rn",
    "timestamp": "17/12/2024, 9:33:22‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "InshaAllah tomorrow he will call you",
    "answer": "Ok no issues",
    "timestamp": "17/12/2024, 10:41:28‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Wsalam sure",
    "answer": "send link",
    "timestamp": "19/12/2024, 2:08:53‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I got 700 in English on my SAT",
    "answer": "ok and what was Math",
    "timestamp": "20/12/2024, 5:47:05‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "we can superscore it so superscore total is 1500",
    "answer": "earlier math was 800?",
    "timestamp": "20/12/2024, 5:53:08‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "20/12/2024, 5:56:22‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "but im free now",
    "answer": "send link",
    "timestamp": "20/12/2024, 7:53:10‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://meet.google.com/kzc-tdah-mjt",
    "answer": "Johns Hopkins-done Emory-done University of virginia-done Boston University-done Northwestern University-done NYU-submitted University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill-done University of Wisconsin-Madison-exams fone Northeastern-submitted Case Western-submitted Baylor-submitted University of Rochester-submitted Penn state ready",
    "timestamp": "20/12/2024, 7:55:42‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Even Madison I‚Äôll share",
    "answer": "Moiz",
    "timestamp": "20/12/2024, 8:09:13‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes we‚Äôre ready I‚Äôm just double checking the common app",
    "answer": "Yes ok once ready lemme known",
    "timestamp": "20/12/2024, 10:24:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Have these been submitted?@‚Å®~Moiz‚Å© @‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å©",
    "answer": "I dunno I‚Äôve been chasing him daily",
    "timestamp": "23/12/2024, 5:44:17‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok please do that and then move onto Florida Miami Lafayette",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© his northwestern number 3 is 244 words",
    "timestamp": "23/12/2024, 6:43:57‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "The version I have sent is 195 words",
    "answer": "Moiz then pls fix",
    "timestamp": "25/12/2024, 10:59:48‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Lafayette Macalester University of Florida Stony brooks These are all Jan 15th",
    "answer": "Moiz",
    "timestamp": "26/12/2024, 11:54:02‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Moiz Hassan has invited you to join a video meeting on Google Meet. Join the meeting: https://meet.google.com/tdz-vnuy-dai",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© we will remove Duke",
    "timestamp": "28/12/2024, 3:17:43‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok agreed it‚Äôs a good decision",
    "answer": "Moiz lemme know which one you deciding on",
    "timestamp": "28/12/2024, 3:30:51‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Salam I‚Äôll be choosing fordham University ‚Äé<This message was edited>",
    "answer": "WAS ok",
    "timestamp": "29/12/2024, 1:05:54‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok üëç",
    "answer": "Mubarak @‚Å®~Moiz‚Å© on amazing admissions",
    "timestamp": "15/01/2025, 5:58:02‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚Äé‚Äésheza adnan Lyceum changed their phone number to a new number. ‚ÄéTap to message or add the new number.",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Hasan Ameer Saqlain‚Å© keep in mind UNC chapell Hill is literally an Ivy level university",
    "timestamp": "18/06/2025, 2:22:41‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚Äé‚Äé~‚ÄØMoiz changed their phone number to a new number. ‚ÄéTap to message or add the new number.",
    "answer": "Asa",
    "timestamp": "13/07/2025, 12:12:11‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Moiz Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+3308013670",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéMessages and calls are end-to-end encrypted. Only people in this chat can read, listen to, or share them.",
    "answer": "@923353797821",
    "timestamp": "13/06/2024, 7:16:17‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sure",
    "answer": "We need to make one",
    "timestamp": "13/06/2024, 5:26:13‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "2019",
    "answer": "Resume looks good @923353797821 ‚Äé[14/06/2024, 12:31:51‚ÄØPM] Zannirah Rehman: Momin Shahid .pdf ‚Ä¢ ‚Äé1 page ‚Äédocument omitted",
    "timestamp": "13/06/2024, 11:58:51‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thank you",
    "answer": "this looks good",
    "timestamp": "14/06/2024, 1:11:32‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "yes",
    "answer": "@923353797821 pls can you book a meeting with him for this week",
    "timestamp": "14/06/2024, 1:39:11‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôll be occupied with my internship so can we do 7 pm Friday?",
    "answer": "Late evening can be zoom",
    "timestamp": "17/07/2024, 3:34:18‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "internships"
  },
  {
    "question": "basically, what is the best cause I can help with so i can write more in my essay.",
    "answer": "@923353797821 pls have a chat with him on this",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-08T19:46:50",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Done",
    "answer": "Hey, please be at the office on October 5, 2024. The head of International office from University of Edinburgh will be visiting our office from 1:45 PM till 3:15 PM. We will discuss program choices, location and any specific questions you may have pertaining to the university.",
    "timestamp": "23/09/2024, 5:38:50‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok sure.",
    "answer": "Reminder for the session tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "30/09/2024, 9:07:08‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôll be a little late.",
    "answer": "Momin",
    "timestamp": "2024-05-10T14:26:47",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can we do both things on Wednesday ouac and US universities",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "2024-06-10T18:22:37",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also, the last time i came for my ouac account I barely got any help we just made our account just for the sake of it and we didn‚Äôt make it properly. I‚Äôm looking forward to make some progress tomorrow and finish it up.",
    "answer": "Momin I already discussed that we would do this tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "2024-08-10T18:26:03",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "I understand. I‚Äôm talking about Sir Muneeb I barely get any help from him.",
    "answer": "No issues will sort all of this tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "2024-08-10T18:28:54",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thank you.",
    "answer": "Pls put your OuAC and common app login heee",
    "timestamp": "2024-08-10T18:29:19",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay sure",
    "answer": "Thx",
    "timestamp": "2024-08-10T18:30:00",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ouac login Username: MuhammadMominShahid Password: jihxew-8wukbU-tuvzoz",
    "answer": "Thanks",
    "timestamp": "2024-08-10T21:52:26",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Nw ‚Äé<This message was edited>",
    "answer": "Hi the SOAS head of International office will be visiting our premises on Monday at 4:10PM Please come and attend the session. This will address all questions related to the university and the admissions process.",
    "timestamp": "2024-08-10T22:16:06",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "üëç",
    "answer": "reminder for tom",
    "timestamp": "2024-11-10T19:32:10",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Done",
    "answer": "Hey Momin let‚Äôs meet Monday",
    "timestamp": "13/10/2024, 5:31:50‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay what time",
    "answer": "will cooridnate time on sunday",
    "timestamp": "18/10/2024, 5:18:10‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I do 12 noon on Monday because I‚Äôm busy after.",
    "answer": "Hopefully should be ok",
    "timestamp": "19/10/2024, 12:24:37‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "My tuition‚Äôs cancelled so I can also do 2 today",
    "answer": "12 is fine",
    "timestamp": "21/10/2024, 8:28:38‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "Momin",
    "timestamp": "21/10/2024, 8:56:24‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Not yet my dad came back yesterday I have to show him first",
    "answer": "Momin lets meet tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "24/10/2024, 5:39:34‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I thought we were meeting today",
    "answer": "lets meet tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "28/10/2024, 5:13:09‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "called back",
    "timestamp": "31/10/2024, 4:27:21‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéSadaf Khan added Hira Zubair Fellow. Tap to change who can add other members.",
    "answer": "Momin we need to submit OuAC tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "2024-05-11T07:45:18",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay I‚Äôll come 4:15ish",
    "answer": "make it like 4:50",
    "timestamp": "2024-05-11T19:54:58",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay thank you",
    "answer": "Ielts ??",
    "timestamp": "2024-06-11T19:18:55",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Let‚Äôs do today by 5 then @923218256422",
    "answer": "when is his meeting",
    "timestamp": "2024-11-11T14:18:59",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sure",
    "answer": "Hello",
    "timestamp": "2024-11-11T19:00:25",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "Momin, pls can you check your canada portals?",
    "timestamp": "19/11/2024, 4:05:10‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôm done with uoft York western",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "20/11/2024, 4:14:19‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "is that possible",
    "answer": "Momin Sheza comes at 3",
    "timestamp": "20/11/2024, 8:58:35‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I was making my uc account right now and there‚Äôs isn‚Äôt an option to add pe",
    "answer": "Can we add manually ?",
    "timestamp": "22/11/2024, 2:58:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôm sorry I‚Äôll be a little late today",
    "answer": "when?",
    "timestamp": "27/11/2024, 4:01:44‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "4:30",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "27/11/2024, 4:07:18‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Coursera Business Analytics course Upenn - Business course on coursera -Skills- Customer Analytics, Operations Analytics, People Analytics, Accounting analytics and Business Analytics Capstone. What I learned. -Explain how data is used for recruiting and performance evaluation - Model supply and demand for various business scenarios. - Solve business problems with data-driven decision-making - Understand the tools used to predict customer behavior - 15. Green Team - the green team is an organization in Karachi American school which specialises in disposing waste around the campus and recycling them and conducts field trips to certain areas in Karachi with immense amounts of waste and basically helps the environment. 16. SAISA Volleyball - South Asian Inter-Scholastic Association competition between ten international schools in South Asia and the Middle East.",
    "answer": "Feroze 1888 is a leading Manufacturer and Exporter of specialised Yarn & Textile products not only in Pakistan but across the globe. The company began its journey in 1970s, with each passing year adding immense value and progression, aligning and integrating seamlessly with the innovative advancements & globalization, becoming an emblem of Excellent Execution Every time.",
    "timestamp": "29/11/2024, 4:22:36‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "extracurriculars"
  },
  {
    "question": "Please ensure that your school uploads your transcript by *tomorrow* maximum. If they don‚Äôt then your application will get declined as the deadline is Wednesday.",
    "answer": "@923218256422 pls note",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-12T15:37:05",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Uoft account Username : shahidm6 Password : Mominuoft8747@",
    "answer": "is it working now",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-12T17:25:40",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Western Login Username : mshahi69 Password : Mominwestern8747@# [Image]",
    "answer": "Thanks Zahra",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-12T18:35:04",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéYou pinned a message",
    "answer": "Can we add his UC also",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-12T08:59:08",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "yes can you send the login details",
    "answer": "Momin pls provide",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-12T09:03:08",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "The same problem that happened yesterday",
    "answer": "Stop using iPad",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-12T15:43:13",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "IT*",
    "answer": "Zahra maybe you can send him a screenshot",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-12T15:51:34",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "He doesn‚Äôt care",
    "answer": "its clearly working",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-12T15:56:48",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Green Crescent Trust",
    "answer": "Share dates of these as wel",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-12T19:57:52",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "2024",
    "answer": "Make sure whatever you give they will probably ask for proof",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-12T20:12:34",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "And Dubai 7th - 14th July",
    "answer": "Make sure whatever dates you put, take a screen shot Zahra",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-12T20:44:20",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Send",
    "answer": "Zahra send me screenshot when done",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-12T20:59:19",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "@923362282777 submitted ?",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-12T21:08:56",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes",
    "answer": "Thank you. Great work",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-12T21:18:49",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thank you so much for helping me. I appreciate it!",
    "answer": "Momin how many APs will you have in total",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-12T21:22:19",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "also",
    "answer": "@923328234782 pls can you call him to fill the common app",
    "timestamp": "2024-07-12T18:00:35",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "When you‚Äôre doing my majors can you also pls check the pre calc and calc requirements because most business subjects do require pre calc and I don‚Äôt have it",
    "answer": "US is ok",
    "timestamp": "2024-11-12T17:41:01",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": ".",
    "answer": "Monday",
    "timestamp": "14/12/2024, 1:16:19‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "We also haven‚Äôt finished common app unis yet",
    "answer": "Momin we call you in daily",
    "timestamp": "14/12/2024, 1:40:06‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "So can we pls do that too?",
    "answer": "yes you need to pls take out time and come on monday",
    "timestamp": "14/12/2024, 1:54:12‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Does that work for you?",
    "answer": "yup",
    "timestamp": "14/12/2024, 1:55:43‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "and can we also discuss my personal statement",
    "answer": "What time are you in today",
    "timestamp": "14/12/2024, 1:59:12‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "IA",
    "answer": "https://www.kcl.ac.uk/study/international/courses/liberal-arts-social-sciences",
    "timestamp": "18/12/2024, 10:20:23‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923218256422 when can you come?",
    "answer": "@923218256422",
    "timestamp": "19/12/2024, 3:58:31‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tomorrow?",
    "answer": "now",
    "timestamp": "19/12/2024, 4:23:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "and right now I‚Äôm at volleyball",
    "answer": "So come after",
    "timestamp": "19/12/2024, 4:24:07‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "extracurriculars"
  },
  {
    "question": "It‚Äôs at school so I‚Äôll reach at 6-6:15",
    "answer": "this way we won't be able to finish work",
    "timestamp": "19/12/2024, 4:29:49‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sure @923218256422 Please come by 4 tomorrow. Hope that‚Äôs okay with you. I don‚Äôt come in on Saturdays. Only coming for your essay",
    "answer": "Momin kindly make sure you‚Äôre there",
    "timestamp": "20/12/2024, 6:27:01‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes IA",
    "answer": "Momin pls be in office tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "21/12/2024, 2:43:38‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "For the writing part in the questions section we‚Äôre only done with 3 unis that are Rochester, Bentley and Umass Amherst. 4 are left -University of Miami -University of Wisconsin- Madison -Penn State -University of Washington",
    "answer": "Momin we didn‚Äôt discuss these universities",
    "timestamp": "23/12/2024, 1:06:35‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Penn state and wisconsin I discussed with you it‚Äôs in our document that I made with you ‚Äé<This message was edited>",
    "answer": "Let‚Äôs do Penn state",
    "timestamp": "23/12/2024, 1:18:53‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôm removing minnesota and michigan state",
    "answer": "where are you",
    "timestamp": "23/12/2024, 1:24:51‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôll reach at 4:30 ‚Äé[23/12/2024, 5:03:22‚ÄØPM] Momin Shahid: ‚Äéimage omitted ‚Äé[23/12/2024, 5:03:33‚ÄØPM] Momin Shahid: ‚Äéimage omitted ‚Äé[23/12/2024, 5:05:46‚ÄØPM] Momin Shahid: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "answer": "You have these supplements",
    "timestamp": "23/12/2024, 3:30:34‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "also are the essay concerns sorted? ‚Äé[23/12/2024, 5:14:48‚ÄØPM] Momin Shahid: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "timestamp": "23/12/2024, 5:14:27‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "He had asked for a couple more changes we will have revised version tonight",
    "answer": "Momin",
    "timestamp": "23/12/2024, 5:23:20‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mc master is not working",
    "answer": "Pls come to office and then have them checked with Sheza on Monday",
    "timestamp": "2025-11-01T12:55:15",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tomorrow",
    "answer": "Come to office by 4",
    "timestamp": "2025-12-01T22:57:33",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Rochester login Email : School email Pin: given Password : Mominrochester8747@#",
    "answer": "What have they asked",
    "timestamp": "13/01/2025, 5:27:34‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Today",
    "answer": "Momin",
    "timestamp": "14/01/2025, 10:40:46‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sorry will be late I‚Äôll reach at 1:30",
    "answer": "@923328234782",
    "timestamp": "14/01/2025, 12:54:53‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What about this one",
    "answer": "We can just write these",
    "timestamp": "14/01/2025, 3:14:10‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôll do the 600 character one",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "14/01/2025, 3:18:05‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Coming for kings today",
    "answer": "let Sadaf confirm if PS is ready",
    "timestamp": "17/01/2025, 2:52:33‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Isn‚Äôt it optional",
    "answer": "They need it",
    "timestamp": "19/01/2025, 4:31:10‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923018379777 reminder to re-check my Waterloo portal if everything is finished.",
    "answer": "Kindly coordinate with sheza",
    "timestamp": "20/01/2025, 3:49:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Because my Counciler‚Äôs leaving for mun",
    "answer": "Momin you‚Äôre supposed to do this transcript upload with the school",
    "timestamp": "20/01/2025, 5:34:09‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I don‚Äôt know how to check",
    "answer": "Sheza just see pls",
    "timestamp": "20/01/2025, 5:34:55‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923328234782 can you pls confirm if my Waterloo transcript is uploaded ‚Äé<This message was edited>",
    "answer": "momin it doesnt allow us to login",
    "timestamp": "21/01/2025, 3:15:40‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Just on google you have to type Waterloo login go on the first link and I‚Äôm sending my Waterloo login",
    "answer": "It‚Äôs asking for A QR code",
    "timestamp": "21/01/2025, 4:09:08‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I can‚Äôt come",
    "answer": "We have 4/5 times",
    "timestamp": "21/01/2025, 4:09:42‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I told you on the weekend I can‚Äôt come before Wednesdays nd tmrw after school I have to submit my transcript s",
    "answer": "@923328234782",
    "timestamp": "21/01/2025, 4:09:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Jopos travelling and if it‚Äôs due 31st I won‚Äôt be able to upload it again",
    "answer": "@923328234782",
    "timestamp": "21/01/2025, 4:10:26‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "and the university of Rochester portal isn‚Äôt working [Image]",
    "answer": "Momin sheza doesn‚Äôt come on Saturday",
    "timestamp": "24/01/2025, 6:52:54‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "@923328234782 please can you go through with hun",
    "timestamp": "24/01/2025, 12:40:05‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pls let me know who I have to forward all my emails to so they can re check.",
    "answer": "Momin if you wanna check pls come to office , sit with Sheza and do it",
    "timestamp": "29/01/2025, 7:58:56‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "and I‚Äôm busy this week",
    "answer": "whats going to take time",
    "timestamp": "29/01/2025, 8:01:31‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I want it to be purely business focused please ‚Äé<This message was edited>",
    "answer": "We are applying for the liberal arts program",
    "timestamp": "2025-01-02T23:53:26",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "career_guidance"
  },
  {
    "question": "Personal^",
    "answer": "for manchester and City we will have the apps submitted and which course do u wanna target at warwick",
    "timestamp": "2025-11-02T16:39:04",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you please send me my new kings foundation personal statement",
    "answer": "We are going with liberal arts program yes",
    "timestamp": "13/02/2025, 3:54:52‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "I want to add everyday essentials regardless of what program I choose",
    "answer": "We will add it and then that‚Äôs final from our end",
    "timestamp": "13/02/2025, 3:57:37‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you scroll up you‚Äôll find",
    "answer": "@923002271104 add everyday essentials and his changes",
    "timestamp": "13/02/2025, 4:09:17‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "It‚Äôs a quarterly grading system [Image]",
    "answer": "Then pls ask school to respond",
    "timestamp": "14/02/2025, 2:15:00‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I alr did",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "14/02/2025, 5:42:59‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I can‚Äôt miss the deadline",
    "answer": "Call",
    "timestamp": "14/02/2025, 5:43:38‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pls text me I can‚Äôt call rn",
    "answer": "Call when free",
    "timestamp": "14/02/2025, 5:44:25‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you pls send me ubc‚Äôs admissions email",
    "answer": "admissions.inquiry@ubc.ca.",
    "timestamp": "16/02/2025, 11:31:14‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Rejected [Image]",
    "answer": "Kindly read so we can close on this",
    "timestamp": "22/02/2025, 1:24:52‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéZahra Banatwala left",
    "answer": "?",
    "timestamp": "24/02/2025, 10:26:45‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôm doing these 2 modules",
    "answer": "@923002271104 can you incorporate changes to first three points please. Momin UK PS is academic and activities mentioned correlate with study interests, so that‚Äôs totally ok .",
    "timestamp": "25/02/2025, 12:45:17‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes doing so. Submitting in an hour",
    "answer": "thank u",
    "timestamp": "25/02/2025, 1:47:57‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes it‚Äôs good ‚Äé[25/02/2025, 4:02:33‚ÄØPM] Momin Shahid: ‚Äéimage omitted ‚Äé[25/02/2025, 4:04:19‚ÄØPM] Momin Shahid: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "25/02/2025, 3:34:26‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "??",
    "answer": "We‚Äôll use the same template we have for kings",
    "timestamp": "28/02/2025, 9:33:47‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Before the applications close",
    "answer": "Kings is business also",
    "timestamp": "2025-01-03T08:08:22",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "Pls identify the stream https://warwick.ac.uk/study/international-foundation-programme/courses/",
    "timestamp": "2025-01-03T09:12:19",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "This link has details but as I said ir states they don‚Äôt take this update [Image]",
    "answer": "Pls draft something and we can help edit",
    "timestamp": "2025-09-03T20:51:04",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do I see the letter",
    "answer": "un block your pop up [Image] [Image]",
    "timestamp": "2025-03-04T00:18:44",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ive sent my mid year grades already [Image]",
    "answer": "If any tests etc have taken place since this app was submitted send those",
    "timestamp": "2025-03-04T01:26:00",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "And they keep telling me to send my updated grades when I‚Äôve already sent them",
    "answer": "Ok I guess for now you wait",
    "timestamp": "2025-03-04T14:46:42",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": ".",
    "answer": "Momin pls send",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-04T14:03:00",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What‚Äôs 85% Canadian percentage to American gpa",
    "answer": "roughly a 4.0",
    "timestamp": "2025-11-04T16:42:02",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "According to the ontario scale ‚Äé[11/04/2025, 4:56:02‚ÄØPM] Momin Shahid: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "answer": "usually is over 3.7 plus",
    "timestamp": "2025-11-04T16:54:27",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Waterloo offer",
    "answer": "@923218256422 pls coordinate a meeting with Hira",
    "timestamp": "2025-11-04T17:01:07",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "I won‚Äôt be able to",
    "answer": "@hira",
    "timestamp": "19/06/2025, 2:57:16‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéYou added Aneeqa Anis Shaikh Intern",
    "answer": "Anicca pls call him in",
    "timestamp": "24/06/2025, 1:23:38‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Momin Shahid",
    "student_phone": "+8941791247",
    "category": "internships"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also what time should my brother come",
    "answer": "Please tell him to submit his forms anytime",
    "timestamp": "27/10/2017, 7:02:53‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok I'll be there at 3:00",
    "answer": "Please meet me and Sadaf on Wednesday",
    "timestamp": "2017-04-11T12:45:43",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I'll come at 2:30",
    "answer": "Ok [Image]",
    "timestamp": "2017-06-11T21:20:19",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I just come on Friday",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "13/03/2018, 8:24:34‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Still waiting for the call",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Sahrish Dignosco‚Å© why didn‚Äôt this call happen or did it ?",
    "timestamp": "20/04/2018, 5:27:20‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tuesday I have my math paper",
    "answer": "Nameera this meeting is important",
    "timestamp": "18/05/2018, 6:14:39‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "I can come tomorrow",
    "answer": "This meeting is on the phone",
    "timestamp": "24/05/2018, 7:32:21‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay.",
    "answer": "Sahrish pls tie up Nameeras meeting with Sohaib",
    "timestamp": "29/05/2018, 1:27:51‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Please respond to sehrish about today's meeting",
    "answer": "Khalida also add Alizeh Maqbool here",
    "timestamp": "2018-05-06T11:36:55",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Sohaib Nasir US‚Å© you have to add meeting comments to Nameera's file for the meeting you had yesterday.",
    "answer": "Sohaib pls don‚Äôt delay this",
    "timestamp": "2018-06-06T12:55:21",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I did already",
    "answer": "Files need to be updated",
    "timestamp": "2018-07-06T02:06:45",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "For everyone I met with",
    "answer": "Ok cool",
    "timestamp": "2018-07-06T02:06:49",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I totally forgot that it was my graduation today",
    "answer": "When is this call happening ??",
    "timestamp": "19/06/2018, 11:12:02‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes",
    "answer": "Nameera there was an elp meeting",
    "timestamp": "21/06/2018, 4:07:57‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "10 am and pm work for me",
    "answer": "Sohaib?",
    "timestamp": "22/07/2018, 2:27:58‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéSahrish Dignosco left",
    "answer": "Sohaib she is looking to change her majors",
    "timestamp": "17/08/2018, 12:40:50‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôm also leaning towards actuarial",
    "answer": "Ok cool",
    "timestamp": "24/08/2018, 6:09:09‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "career_guidance"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéYou added Momina Iftikhar Counselling",
    "answer": "I need to meet",
    "timestamp": "24/08/2018, 3:47:31‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is that fine ?",
    "answer": "Sohaib",
    "timestamp": "28/08/2018, 1:44:56‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Same at ucl and kings college as well",
    "answer": "I don‚Äôt think we can attempt Acturial without further math",
    "timestamp": "28/08/2018, 8:56:18‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I am studying further",
    "answer": "Hey I met Nameera today",
    "timestamp": "28/08/2018, 9:41:26‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "and if so, when am I receiving the work for it",
    "answer": "Acturial most probably",
    "timestamp": "31/08/2018, 9:25:04‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which subject should I focus on",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Ata Rehman‚Å© we are deciding between economics and philosophy type versus Acturial",
    "timestamp": "31/08/2018, 6:54:19‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "Should go with econ",
    "answer": "Nameera please list grades subject wise here",
    "timestamp": "31/08/2018, 7:03:53‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "Bio A* Chem A* physics A Math A",
    "answer": "Will it be ok to do eco without having it in A levels? Or should we do eco privately this year ?",
    "timestamp": "31/08/2018, 7:07:00‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "course_selection"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can do privately this year",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Ata Rehman‚Å© @‚Å®Sohaib Nasir US‚Å© if we do economics and philosophy at LSE what should we pick at Cambridge ?",
    "timestamp": "31/08/2018, 7:27:36‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "internships"
  },
  {
    "question": "Most accurate info wud be available on each uni‚Äôs website for that particular degree in terms of what subjects are required etc",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Sohaib Nasir US‚Å© we are moving with natural sciences as the UK program choice",
    "timestamp": "2018-03-09T12:06:10",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Need a* in math",
    "answer": "Don‚Äôt need Astar in math",
    "timestamp": "2018-05-09T00:25:31",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "There I‚Äôll start work on it",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "2018-05-09T13:21:50",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Or that is my understanding",
    "answer": "Nameera when will you share PS draft",
    "timestamp": "2018-06-09T01:26:44",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is it a requirement",
    "answer": "Yes it is",
    "timestamp": "18/09/2018, 2:08:56‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "The deadline was 5th September",
    "answer": "Kindly check if there is a later deadline",
    "timestamp": "18/09/2018, 3:27:17‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "There isn‚Äôt",
    "answer": "With extra fee etc",
    "timestamp": "18/09/2018, 3:27:42‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "Nameera there‚Äôs no other ngo in Khi",
    "timestamp": "27/09/2018, 6:11:29‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "For Harvard only main essay and add info is required",
    "answer": "No there‚Äôs a supplement as well",
    "timestamp": "30/09/2018, 6:38:52‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Nameera New‚Å© where",
    "answer": "What‚Äôs the status on PS?",
    "timestamp": "2018-03-10T16:21:09",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "She‚Äôll be here by 4:30 today to finalize draft",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Abrar Rahman‚Å© Nameera is also thinking of SAT 2 for Korean Lang",
    "timestamp": "2018-04-10T14:35:55",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© pls guide her",
    "answer": "Nameera call me in a bit",
    "timestamp": "2018-10-10T17:32:33",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Today",
    "answer": "Hi need to be in office by 8AM sharp tomorrow [Image]",
    "timestamp": "2018-12-10T11:38:12",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "It‚Äôs not letting me enter a value",
    "answer": "Click on the question mark [Image]",
    "timestamp": "2018-12-10T19:40:27",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also the logins details you shared isn‚Äôt working. Pls send again",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Nameera New‚Å© is this done",
    "timestamp": "13/10/2018, 12:16:32‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sir Mustufa said he‚Äôll send it tomorrow because he‚Äôs not home and will reach late",
    "answer": "This better not get messed up",
    "timestamp": "13/10/2018, 7:52:51‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "My mouse wasn‚Äôt working so I couldn‚Äôt edit out some errors will do that in the research office in the morning and then send.",
    "answer": "Korean not offered in pakistan",
    "timestamp": "19/10/2018, 1:20:06‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "research_opportunities"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can‚Äôt do anything about that then. Let it be",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Nameera New‚Å© please send add info and complete OUAC and McGill form",
    "timestamp": "22/10/2018, 10:08:33‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéYou added Mahnoor farooq",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Mahnoor farooq‚Å© please review her ouac",
    "timestamp": "26/10/2018, 11:51:25‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay, please fill it out today so i can review it [Image]",
    "answer": "Yea you can",
    "timestamp": "27/10/2018, 10:50:18‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Super amazing!",
    "answer": "She‚Äôs working to improve the background",
    "timestamp": "27/10/2018, 7:39:24‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thankyou",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Nameera New‚Å© please send the Penn supplement",
    "timestamp": "27/10/2018, 7:42:31‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Done",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Ata Rehman‚Å© she‚Äôs sent main essay also",
    "timestamp": "27/10/2018, 7:45:41‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Nameera New‚Å© Daim will be editing your upenn supplement @‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© get him added to email when she‚Äôs sending out email on back of chain",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "30/10/2018, 8:25:46‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "cool, will take a look soon",
    "answer": "Thx",
    "timestamp": "30/10/2018, 10:50:57‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "1. You immediately dive into what courses you want to take at penn without providing a smooth transition between the story of your grandmother and what lessons you took away from it/how penn will help you with it/ *what school you are interested in at Penn*so I would work on that transition",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Nameera New‚Å© ?",
    "timestamp": "31/10/2018, 2:13:10‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Let me know if you have any questions in-between, and I'll try to answer when I wake up",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Nameera New‚Å© please also share your gap year statement",
    "timestamp": "31/10/2018, 2:21:36‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôve done the activities and the gap year statement [Image]",
    "answer": "WWF",
    "timestamp": "31/10/2018, 8:33:33‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "extracurriculars"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© which other unis other than Waterloo and Toronto should I add",
    "answer": "Come in please [Image]",
    "timestamp": "2018-01-11T17:14:23",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay [Image]",
    "answer": "Put uoft above the 3rd Waterloo choice",
    "timestamp": "2018-01-11T17:57:30",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this fine",
    "answer": "Yea",
    "timestamp": "2018-01-11T18:13:10",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Ata Rehman‚Å© @‚Å®Daim Malik‚Å© what further changes should be made to the supplement",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Ata Rehman‚Å© ?",
    "timestamp": "2018-01-11T19:38:13",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "I should have said it sooner but I dosed off : Thankyou @‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© @‚Å®Ata Rehman‚Å© @‚Å®Abrar Rahman‚Å© @‚Å®Daim Malik‚Å© @‚Å®Aiman Chaudhary‚Å© @‚Å®Momina Iftikhar Counselling‚Å© , Sadaf I‚Äôm really grateful for all the help.",
    "answer": "Good luck :)",
    "timestamp": "2018-02-11T09:49:44",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thanks and definitely",
    "answer": "Have you sent sat scores",
    "timestamp": "2018-02-11T12:01:10",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mcgill and ouac sent",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Mahnoor farooq‚Å©",
    "timestamp": "2018-03-11T15:13:34",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Noted",
    "answer": "Please target submitting duke",
    "timestamp": "2018-03-11T17:14:57",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Just checked , not there",
    "answer": "Spam too?",
    "timestamp": "2018-08-11T20:27:42",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "It‚Äôs on 19th",
    "answer": "Ok cool",
    "timestamp": "2018-09-11T14:59:27",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok üëçüèæ [Image] [Image] [Image] [Image] [Image] [Image] [Image]",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Ata Rehman‚Å© comments",
    "timestamp": "2018-10-11T17:51:16",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Should have uploaded as an art supplement it‚Äôs great work",
    "answer": "Yea we are",
    "timestamp": "2018-10-11T21:11:59",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "extracurriculars"
  },
  {
    "question": "Should create labels as well",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Nameera New‚Å© do you have?",
    "timestamp": "2018-10-11T21:12:42",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Lol",
    "answer": "Hahah",
    "timestamp": "2018-12-11T20:30:51",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yeah",
    "answer": "Why don‚Äôt we ask them for a date extension",
    "timestamp": "17/11/2018, 1:37:12‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "For oxford or upenn",
    "answer": "Oxford",
    "timestamp": "17/11/2018, 2:29:01‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Called. It was closed",
    "answer": "Please draft an email",
    "timestamp": "17/11/2018, 9:31:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": ".....",
    "answer": "Call me in the night to discuss",
    "timestamp": "18/11/2018, 6:38:09‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are interviewers required to give u their card for later contact",
    "answer": "Not really",
    "timestamp": "19/11/2018, 9:41:27‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Go for Skype",
    "answer": "Ok cool",
    "timestamp": "20/11/2018, 3:20:54‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Abrar Rahman‚Å©",
    "answer": "Yea plus it‚Äôll put sat at risk as well",
    "timestamp": "20/11/2018, 3:21:08‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "üòá ... [Image]",
    "answer": "Yea I‚Äôve already informed your school",
    "timestamp": "20/11/2018, 4:47:52‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "üëå",
    "answer": "Please share revised activity list",
    "timestamp": "19/12/2018, 8:54:59‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚Äé‚ÄéDaim Malik changed their phone number to a new number. ‚ÄéTap to message or add the new number.",
    "answer": "Can we please finalise northwestern and duke so you can submit",
    "timestamp": "24/12/2018, 3:03:28‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sure",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Nameera New‚Å© ?",
    "timestamp": "27/12/2018, 11:57:00‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© @‚Å®Ata Rehman‚Å© ?",
    "answer": "Yea Sadaf is giving her feedback right now",
    "timestamp": "28/12/2018, 8:19:06‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are these done from your side?",
    "answer": "We can submit Wesleyan also",
    "timestamp": "29/12/2018, 9:46:43‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "*jan",
    "answer": "Nameera is northwestern final",
    "timestamp": "29/12/2018, 9:51:26‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes from me",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Ata Rehman‚Å© have you finalised it?",
    "timestamp": "29/12/2018, 11:05:53‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I don‚Äôt rem",
    "answer": "Nameera",
    "timestamp": "30/12/2018, 1:00:06‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sure",
    "answer": "You never sent this",
    "timestamp": "30/12/2018, 1:42:32‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sorry about that",
    "answer": "Have you submitted Pomona",
    "timestamp": "30/12/2018, 1:30:51‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pls share screenshot of dashboard [Image]",
    "answer": "Please submit swarthmore and duke",
    "timestamp": "31/12/2018, 9:28:19‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "?",
    "timestamp": "2019-01-01T18:35:59",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok so should I submit Williams?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "timestamp": "2019-01-01T23:16:18",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Should I send literature score",
    "answer": "I think Abrar had said don‚Äôt",
    "timestamp": "2019-02-01T00:48:52",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "standardized_tests"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok I‚Äôm not adding it then",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Nameera New‚Å© what about Harvard",
    "timestamp": "2019-02-01T01:04:45",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will do Yale and Dartmouth too",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Ata Rehman‚Å© please finalize harvard",
    "timestamp": "2019-02-01T03:16:41",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this for the page ?",
    "answer": "Yes [Image]",
    "timestamp": "2019-06-02T15:27:56",
    "student_name": "Nameera Dawood",
    "student_phone": "+7516729520",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay thanks",
    "answer": "Aqib when are you reverting on Nima's draft",
    "timestamp": "31/08/2017, 4:45:52‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nima Ashfaq",
    "student_phone": "+6842226676",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Aqib Fellow‚Å©I've written a new version of the first two paragraphs and sent that to you as well",
    "answer": "Aqib did you revert?",
    "timestamp": "2017-11-09T22:35:13",
    "student_name": "Nima Ashfaq",
    "student_phone": "+6842226676",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "I think those are good. Rizwan, any thoughts?",
    "answer": "I'd change warwick",
    "timestamp": "26/09/2017, 6:40:37‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nima Ashfaq",
    "student_phone": "+6842226676",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Apparently you‚Äôre meant to email them and send in the changes via email so I‚Äôve gotten the email address and I‚Äôll email them today after school",
    "answer": "Ucas ?",
    "timestamp": "2017-11-10T10:15:52",
    "student_name": "Nima Ashfaq",
    "student_phone": "+6842226676",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yup I‚Äôve read it",
    "answer": "1510",
    "timestamp": "20/10/2017, 6:46:35‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Nima Ashfaq",
    "student_phone": "+6842226676",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôve sent it",
    "answer": "When are we submitting?",
    "timestamp": "29/10/2017, 10:53:42‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nima Ashfaq",
    "student_phone": "+6842226676",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thank you!",
    "answer": "Congrats",
    "timestamp": "2017-10-11T21:24:27",
    "student_name": "Nima Ashfaq",
    "student_phone": "+6842226676",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which supplements should I start work on first? Claremont has no application fees before 30 November so I really wanna go for that and I‚Äôm thinking I‚Äôll apply to Berkeley but not UCLA because I‚Äôd go to Warwick over that",
    "answer": "Yes do the UC supps",
    "timestamp": "18/11/2017, 7:29:51‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nima Ashfaq",
    "student_phone": "+6842226676",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôm not applying to Cornell or John Hopkins",
    "answer": "So cut those out",
    "timestamp": "18/11/2017, 7:48:28‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nima Ashfaq",
    "student_phone": "+6842226676",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Should I start Harvard?",
    "answer": "Yeah you couldn‚Äôt",
    "timestamp": "18/11/2017, 7:49:12‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nima Ashfaq",
    "student_phone": "+6842226676",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Congrats!!",
    "answer": "Congrats",
    "timestamp": "23/11/2017, 8:09:40‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nima Ashfaq",
    "student_phone": "+6842226676",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I send the car now to pick up the books? What books do you have in the office?",
    "answer": "Office is shut",
    "timestamp": "26/11/2017, 12:45:47‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nima Ashfaq",
    "student_phone": "+6842226676",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay sure",
    "answer": "Nima when are you submitting",
    "timestamp": "27/11/2017, 10:48:52‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nima Ashfaq",
    "student_phone": "+6842226676",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôll submit today I just need to fill out some sections of the app which are left",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "28/11/2017, 3:08:51‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nima Ashfaq",
    "student_phone": "+6842226676",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Main supplement and q1 needs changes",
    "answer": "Nima",
    "timestamp": "29/12/2017, 8:04:49‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nima Ashfaq",
    "student_phone": "+6842226676",
    "category": "essay_writing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can u fwd us the acceptance email",
    "answer": "Amazing",
    "timestamp": "2018-10-01T16:19:45",
    "student_name": "Nima Ashfaq",
    "student_phone": "+6842226676",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thanks!",
    "answer": "Nima please forward the Yale and oxford acceptance emails",
    "timestamp": "2018-10-01T22:58:18",
    "student_name": "Nima Ashfaq",
    "student_phone": "+6842226676",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Congrats",
    "answer": "Congrats",
    "timestamp": "13/03/2018, 7:10:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Nima Ashfaq",
    "student_phone": "+6842226676",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also I got in to Berkeley",
    "answer": "Cool",
    "timestamp": "30/03/2018, 10:56:24‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Nima Ashfaq",
    "student_phone": "+6842226676",
    "category": "college_applications"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yayy",
    "answer": ":]]",
    "timestamp": "30/03/2018, 11:08:54‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Nima Ashfaq",
    "student_phone": "+6842226676",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéYou created group ‚ÄúRania Ahmed ‚Äù",
    "answer": "Rania well use this group to communicate",
    "timestamp": "2024-08-11T11:20:57",
    "student_name": "Rania Ahmed",
    "student_phone": "+5146875571",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "ok 1?",
    "answer": "3 works?",
    "timestamp": "2024-10-11T16:04:28",
    "student_name": "Rania Ahmed",
    "student_phone": "+5146875571",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "if not 1 then i‚Äôm fine w 3 aswell",
    "answer": "ill try, but if im outta office for a bit we can 12 or 3",
    "timestamp": "2024-10-11T16:05:15",
    "student_name": "Rania Ahmed",
    "student_phone": "+5146875571",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "3",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "2024-10-11T16:05:58",
    "student_name": "Rania Ahmed",
    "student_phone": "+5146875571",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "ok",
    "answer": "ok Rania sorry i confused you with theother rania",
    "timestamp": "13/11/2024, 2:06:42‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rania Ahmed",
    "student_phone": "+5146875571",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "UCAS username : raniaahmed910@gmail.com password : Rania910. [Image]",
    "answer": "Modern English Legal System",
    "timestamp": "13/11/2024, 4:48:20‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rania Ahmed",
    "student_phone": "+5146875571",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "ok thanks for letting me know",
    "answer": "Hello how far are we with the personal statement",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-12T10:09:19",
    "student_name": "Rania Ahmed",
    "student_phone": "+5146875571",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "of jan",
    "answer": "Ok but then we need to make sure all unis we target accept the Jan LNAT scores",
    "timestamp": "2024-11-12T16:18:48",
    "student_name": "Rania Ahmed",
    "student_phone": "+5146875571",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "hey @‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© when n how should i book my ilets",
    "answer": "Asap",
    "timestamp": "2025-07-01T11:35:53",
    "student_name": "Rania Ahmed",
    "student_phone": "+5146875571",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "n psyvh was j the same",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "2025-09-01T14:56:44",
    "student_name": "Rania Ahmed",
    "student_phone": "+5146875571",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "it‚Äôs a b and 2 cs currently",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "2025-09-01T15:35:27",
    "student_name": "Rania Ahmed",
    "student_phone": "+5146875571",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "i haven‚Äôt applied to any yet",
    "answer": "Yes once done then you can update",
    "timestamp": "2025-11-01T19:14:26",
    "student_name": "Rania Ahmed",
    "student_phone": "+5146875571",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "For all students who have applied to US universities with the SAT option, please make sure SAT scores are sent from Collegeboard website. If this doesn't apply to you please ignore the message.",
    "answer": "lets try closing UCAS",
    "timestamp": "13/01/2025, 3:53:39‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rania Ahmed",
    "student_phone": "+5146875571",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "?",
    "answer": "Hey",
    "timestamp": "15/01/2025, 12:59:27‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rania Ahmed",
    "student_phone": "+5146875571",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "eyesha1@hotmail.com ‚Äé[15/01/2025, 3:04:23‚ÄØPM] Rania Ahmed Nixor: ‚Äéimage omitted [Image] [Image] ‚Äé[15/01/2025, 6:46:14‚ÄØPM] Rania Ahmed Nixor: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "answer": "Thanks [Image]",
    "timestamp": "15/01/2025, 3:01:24‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rania Ahmed",
    "student_phone": "+5146875571",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "hey @‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© i got an email from sussex and durham",
    "answer": "Ok [Image]",
    "timestamp": "20/01/2025, 12:42:57‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rania Ahmed",
    "student_phone": "+5146875571",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "or original caie",
    "answer": "Ok let‚Äôs wait will give",
    "timestamp": "23/01/2025, 8:12:29‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rania Ahmed",
    "student_phone": "+5146875571",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hey i got my ilets result",
    "answer": "Ok pls share here too ‚Äé[27/01/2025, 9:44:08‚ÄØAM] Rania Ahmed Nixor: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "timestamp": "27/01/2025, 8:58:55‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Rania Ahmed",
    "student_phone": "+5146875571",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "also got an offer from city",
    "answer": "ok great pls share",
    "timestamp": "27/01/2025, 9:44:35‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Rania Ahmed",
    "student_phone": "+5146875571",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "so sorry i won‚Äôt be able to make it today but yes that sounds good",
    "answer": "Sure will do shortly",
    "timestamp": "2024-11-10T12:59:22",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "hello, just letting u know that tmr i have a tuition from 5-6 otherwise im free for the meeting [Image]",
    "answer": "@923332351730 please see this template and try filling",
    "timestamp": "13/10/2024, 9:41:35‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Give me a day or two",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "15/10/2024, 1:24:08‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi @923018379777 please coordinate a time with her for next meeting",
    "answer": "@923343299263 we will meet tomorrow in the afternoon",
    "timestamp": "16/10/2024, 2:27:00‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay just letting u know that i do have tuitions from 4-7",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "16/10/2024, 2:31:45‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok sure please share once done",
    "answer": "Hey Rashna",
    "timestamp": "22/10/2024, 2:18:44‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "hello i can meet tomorrow from 3-3:45",
    "answer": "can we do friday at 4",
    "timestamp": "30/10/2024, 3:36:27‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "hello i‚Äôve answered all the questions for the brainstorming doc",
    "answer": "lets schedule a meeting in coming week for main common app essay",
    "timestamp": "2024-01-11T20:11:08",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, yesterday i discussed with @923332351730 and he told me about ‚Äúthe Karachi collective‚Äù it is an online art research journal which is run by his friends. we can contact them and i can look into getting mentioned on it or maybe even write and publish an article for them. how does that sound ?",
    "answer": "both can work.",
    "timestamp": "2024-02-11T13:35:39",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "also from what they‚Äôre saying the work is very time consuming so im also worried about whether or not i‚Äôll be able to keep up w what they ask from me as the next two months are rlly busy but im willing to try if u guys think this could be useful",
    "answer": "When is timeline to respond",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-11T16:13:08",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "till 5th nov",
    "answer": "Ok so stem and art seems very interesting",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-11T16:38:04",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "hello i‚Äôm going to discuss this w them today, for the honours part can u guys clarify what exactly i should ask from them?",
    "answer": "Your name should be mentioned in Karachi Collective highlighting extent of involvement. And for the extent of involvement pls first let me know what they say",
    "timestamp": "2024-04-11T17:10:48",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "We have a meeting today at 6pm. We will let you know as soon we get the feedback",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "2024-04-11T17:14:25",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "and for the common app meeting, tmr i am free anytime",
    "answer": "Ok let sadaf confirm time",
    "timestamp": "2024-05-11T11:28:13",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Dear Sadaf and Rizwan, Hope both of you are doing well. As you know, Rashna and the entire A2 year group embarked on the Kashmir trip recently and were originally scheduled to return yesterday evening. However, due to the situation in Islamabad, they were unable to board their flight and have not yet been able to leave Muzaffarabad. Currently, the entire contingent is waiting for the clearance of roads to proceed. The school is actively in touch with higher authorities and is monitoring the situation closely. Well there is no confirmed timeline for when they will be able to fly back. I thought I should make both of you aware of it. Praying for their quick and safe return.",
    "answer": "IA",
    "timestamp": "26/11/2024, 1:51:07‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hello, when should I sit for an english proficiency test",
    "answer": "At the earliest",
    "timestamp": "2024-04-12T22:21:02",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "ielts or the duolingo test, which one is preferable",
    "answer": "Ielts",
    "timestamp": "2024-04-12T22:58:59",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "can i come tmr i dont have a car right now",
    "answer": "@923343299263 can you come for some submissions",
    "timestamp": "20/12/2024, 6:11:04‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "You can come later also",
    "answer": "?",
    "timestamp": "20/12/2024, 6:35:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay i will try come around 8:30",
    "answer": "hey see if you can do 8 or else 9:30?",
    "timestamp": "20/12/2024, 7:13:59‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay i‚Äôll come at 8",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "20/12/2024, 7:24:59‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "The following are the Acronyms I used in the Activity List:",
    "timestamp": "21/12/2024, 2:20:44‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923018379777",
    "answer": "T hanks",
    "timestamp": "21/12/2024, 10:57:00‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923333575290 finished rice supps and just finishing last uwash supp right now",
    "answer": "Rashna share list of all submissions",
    "timestamp": "23/12/2024, 9:01:36‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "submitted grinnell bates mount holyoke ready to submit barnard lafayette bryn mawr tufts colgate drexel union pending bard duke rice swarthmore wellesley macalester centre college vassar washu stlouis dartmouth or upenn",
    "answer": "@923343299263  submit Drexel , Lafayette , union , Bryn Mawr",
    "timestamp": "24/12/2024, 4:39:17‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "i think i accidentally filled css for 24-25..",
    "answer": "I‚Äôll review in the morning",
    "timestamp": "26/12/2024, 8:20:07‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "macalester jan 15th centre college feb 1st wellesley jan 8th",
    "answer": "So you need to keep it consistent",
    "timestamp": "28/12/2024, 3:01:09‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok I think swarthmore. @923018379777 thoughts?",
    "answer": "Swarthmore üëç [Image]",
    "timestamp": "2025-01-01T20:53:07",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "also what is the procedure to send tax documents",
    "answer": "That will only be needed if any uni asks for it",
    "timestamp": "2025-02-01T22:40:32",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923018379777 on css does taxable income refer to income before tax",
    "answer": "Yes income is before tax and tax deduction is shown as an expense",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-01T20:44:28",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "which uni are we doing through direct app",
    "answer": "I‚Äôll share details tomorrow [Image]",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-01T20:35:00",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923018379777",
    "answer": "Put fam contribution as 30k",
    "timestamp": "2025-12-01T14:08:44",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "CSS required Barnard bryn mawr Colgate dartmouth drexel lafayette mount holyoke rice union vassar Tax doc required barnard (website ) duke (idoc) mount holyoke (website) rice (website ) union (website ) vassar (idoc )",
    "answer": "Wherever they‚Äôre asked we need to provide",
    "timestamp": "2025-12-01T15:21:04",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "isn‚Äôt this only if they require u to send official scores ‚Äé<This message was edited> [Image]",
    "answer": "Nopes",
    "timestamp": "13/01/2025, 3:59:27‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "so i just put 0 then",
    "answer": "Can you write not applicable . If not 0 is fine",
    "timestamp": "14/01/2025, 9:56:00‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "also for europe",
    "answer": "I‚Äôll tell you in a day or so",
    "timestamp": "15/01/2025, 3:52:39‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923018379777 please review this app when you can so she can submit",
    "answer": "Share pdf here",
    "timestamp": "20/01/2025, 12:51:31‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923018379777",
    "answer": "This looks ok, have they asked for any resume",
    "timestamp": "20/01/2025, 5:06:23‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "no they haven‚Äôt [Image]",
    "answer": "Yup",
    "timestamp": "20/01/2025, 5:08:23‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "this is all filled however in this transcript my mid year report is also included and some people are saying that the school has decided to bump up the grades for students so there‚Äôs a chance they might change my transcript, will go to the counselling office tomorrow to confirm if they do change it then i‚Äôll ask them to send the new version and then submit the application",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "20/01/2025, 9:19:02‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923018379777 üôè",
    "answer": "DePaul Long Island NY UIC FIU James Madison (will have to check programs)",
    "timestamp": "21/01/2025, 8:07:25‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "üëç [Image]",
    "answer": ":)",
    "timestamp": "14/02/2025, 1:09:04‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "they keep saying that the text is duplicated on the pdf but i don‚Äôt see what‚Äôs wrong @923018379777",
    "answer": "Looks ok to me",
    "timestamp": "14/02/2025, 7:50:43‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "and i have submitted both documents converted in usd with the conversion rate as well",
    "answer": "Can you try calling them",
    "timestamp": "14/02/2025, 7:51:18‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay i‚Äôll see",
    "answer": "Yes keep me posted [Image] [Image] [Image]",
    "timestamp": "14/02/2025, 7:53:21‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "they keep assuming that i my documents are in PKR, when i already submitted everything in USD on the deadline‚Ä¶. i have tried explaining it to them so much üò≠üò≠üò≠ @923018379777",
    "answer": "Let me go through all of this",
    "timestamp": "15/02/2025, 8:46:34‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay",
    "answer": "So from what I gather they‚Äôre asking tax documents to be changed to USD",
    "timestamp": "15/02/2025, 8:55:19‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "no i didn‚Äôt",
    "answer": "Send me the docs again and because they have specified name of person I highly suggest you call",
    "timestamp": "15/02/2025, 10:03:01‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923018379777 what is difference between WO bachelor and HBO bachelor in netherlands universities",
    "answer": "i think usually an extra year in hbo",
    "timestamp": "17/02/2025, 2:30:27‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "for uni of amsterdam",
    "answer": "yup [Image] [Image]",
    "timestamp": "17/02/2025, 2:32:02‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Great! Congratulations",
    "answer": "https://www.unibocconi.it/en/applying-bocconi/bachelor-and-law-programs/funding/required-documentation-funding-application-ay-2025-26",
    "timestamp": "2025-12-03T15:39:34",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "can i come tomorrow 6:30 onwards [Image]",
    "answer": "Thank you Adeel bhai ‚ù§Ô∏è",
    "timestamp": "18/04/2025, 2:17:18‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "You can save this information. Handling instruction and certificate of authentications have been given with both the works",
    "answer": "Thank you . Well received :)",
    "timestamp": "2025-08-05T11:20:02",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hello hope you‚Äôre all well, i‚Äôve received my visa yesterday and im leaving for milan tonight. I just wanted to say thank you for all your help and guidance with my college apps and for putting me on the right track when i started. thank you! ‚ù§Ô∏è",
    "answer": "amazing yaar. good luck",
    "timestamp": "22/08/2025, 12:08:02‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Rashna Zafar",
    "student_phone": "+1533537198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéMessages and calls are end-to-end encrypted. Only people in this chat can read, listen to, or share them.",
    "answer": "Hi We will use this group to correspond",
    "timestamp": "13/08/2020, 6:24:39‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Please fill and send us back here or at hamda.khan@dignosco.org",
    "answer": "ASa Saad when will you drop the documents",
    "timestamp": "13/08/2020, 6:26:09‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Inshallah I'll give the documents by tomorrow",
    "answer": "Great [Image]",
    "timestamp": "17/08/2020, 3:16:09‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Dont know what to fill in the other one. [Image]",
    "answer": "Subject wise O level results grades",
    "timestamp": "17/08/2020, 10:20:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéThis message was deleted.",
    "answer": "IA from coming week",
    "timestamp": "22/08/2020, 10:47:12‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Rizwan, Sadaf, pls giide",
    "answer": "pls look at Duke of Edinburgh and Entreprenureial",
    "timestamp": "25/09/2020, 4:00:50‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What about MUN",
    "answer": "depends on types of MUN",
    "timestamp": "25/09/2020, 4:53:21‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "These and Robotics sound good. Also the Enrichment ones",
    "answer": "lets focus on 2-3 max and deliver and build work around them",
    "timestamp": "25/09/2020, 4:56:52‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Of course. That is why Saad wants to know which are more suitable to go for",
    "answer": "can i get an idea on what theyre planning to do in Robotics",
    "timestamp": "25/09/2020, 4:58:04‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sure, [Image]",
    "answer": "Cornell and overlain",
    "timestamp": "29/09/2020, 11:46:18‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok I'll choose Oberlin n Cornell",
    "answer": "Great [Image]",
    "timestamp": "29/09/2020, 10:31:44‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What about Clark",
    "answer": "No need",
    "timestamp": "29/09/2020, 10:37:56‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Brown is very good",
    "answer": "for sure",
    "timestamp": "2020-08-10T17:42:42",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "?",
    "answer": "Kgs",
    "timestamp": "28/10/2020, 4:55:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "N what should I type for month?",
    "answer": "Write June 2022",
    "timestamp": "28/10/2020, 5:04:29‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Should I do any of these exams?",
    "answer": "No need",
    "timestamp": "2020-03-11T22:31:24",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes immediately pls",
    "answer": "I don‚Äôt see any real need",
    "timestamp": "14/11/2020, 5:26:27‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Rizwan can you list recommended universities of UK and USA here",
    "answer": "Oxford/Cambridge Imperial UCL Kings LSE Durham Edinburgh Bath Sheffield",
    "timestamp": "14/11/2020, 5:59:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "For the SAT account what should I write for the current class?",
    "answer": "Grade 11",
    "timestamp": "2020-11-12T22:13:51",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "It's only saying current grade level",
    "answer": "Can you write AS level ?",
    "timestamp": "2020-11-12T22:16:19",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "‚ÄéYou deleted this message.",
    "timestamp": "2020-12-12T01:17:15",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Riz wrong window",
    "answer": "Lol sorry",
    "timestamp": "2020-12-12T10:04:18",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéThis message was deleted. [Image] [Image]",
    "answer": "Which form is this",
    "timestamp": "15/12/2020, 6:17:49‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "The meeting is confirmed for Thursday at 4:00 PM in the office.",
    "answer": "Hamda pls update file. We have recommended a management major for UK",
    "timestamp": "16/04/2021, 10:55:46‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "Saad so we are moving ahead with management then ya?",
    "timestamp": "22/04/2021, 11:16:48‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "During the meeting today I think it would be better if we talk about it because I want to have a clearer understanding of what business analytics is about",
    "answer": "I suggest you google business analytics up a bit",
    "timestamp": "22/04/2021, 3:22:50‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéThis message was deleted.",
    "answer": "That‚Äôs the interpretation they‚Äôve given here",
    "timestamp": "29/04/2021, 2:18:35‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "N should I apply to any UC college?",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "timestamp": "2021-04-08T19:53:13",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I need to mark on my school Application form",
    "answer": "san diego, irvine, davis, LA, Berkeley",
    "timestamp": "2021-04-08T19:54:11",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "üëç",
    "answer": "pls add zainab here",
    "timestamp": "2021-05-08T12:23:50",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "These are the universities I hv shortlisted for business for early decision/early action",
    "answer": "You are confusing yourself",
    "timestamp": "15/08/2021, 7:20:07‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I need to submit a form tonight regarding choice of early decision",
    "answer": "Add NYU for now",
    "timestamp": "15/08/2021, 7:34:52‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is it better to apply for Ed or Ea to a few universities with funding?",
    "answer": "you can only do ED to one university and its binding",
    "timestamp": "31/08/2021, 12:17:07‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Saad said only EA is binding",
    "answer": "ED is binding",
    "timestamp": "31/08/2021, 12:38:51‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is University of Chicago good?",
    "answer": "its harvard yale equivalent",
    "timestamp": "2021-04-09T14:08:18",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Waiting for list of universities for ED, and others",
    "answer": "What‚Äôs his SAT score",
    "timestamp": "19/09/2021, 11:36:51‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "1340. 620 + 720",
    "answer": "I don‚Äôt see any sense in doing Ed with this score",
    "timestamp": "20/09/2021, 8:24:40‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Saad will be retaking in December",
    "answer": "Yes Ed deadline is Nov 1 so should target Regular decision",
    "timestamp": "20/09/2021, 8:41:11‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Should he ?",
    "answer": "Yes why not",
    "timestamp": "27/09/2021, 6:14:48‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Collate University is no use cuz it only offer computer science",
    "answer": "?",
    "timestamp": "27/09/2021, 6:27:19‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Michigan, Berkeley, Babson offer management and Data Analytics programmes",
    "answer": "my final recommendation after having a long chat with Saad is to do the Global program at NYU versus babson",
    "timestamp": "27/09/2021, 6:28:48‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is that good?",
    "answer": "It‚Äôs a solid program",
    "timestamp": "30/09/2021, 12:28:03‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Rizwan, if for any reason, Saad doesn't get into Stern, then he will be stuck with Liberal arts program which is not what he should be doing.",
    "answer": "There always is a chance. He can always move into arts and sciences also do eco type majors",
    "timestamp": "30/09/2021, 1:15:36‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "No business related studies here.",
    "answer": "yes because the majors start in year 3",
    "timestamp": "30/09/2021, 1:33:29‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© should I be considering applying to University of Toronto",
    "answer": "Ok makes sense",
    "timestamp": "30/09/2021, 7:40:00‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Rizwan and Sadaf. ED idea has been dropped for now.",
    "answer": "If you wanna consider Canada then you can . Their business school Rotman is very good",
    "timestamp": "30/09/2021, 7:40:32‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Saad can you come in tomorrow or should I send you the links here so you can complete your applications?",
    "answer": "Pls do this immediately",
    "timestamp": "24/10/2021, 2:37:56‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "My last paper is actually on 18th November but there is break after 27nd October n that is y I hope to do it at that time",
    "answer": "Uoft priority deadline is Nov 1",
    "timestamp": "24/10/2021, 3:16:33‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Would it be a good idea to apply for priority decision",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "timestamp": "24/10/2021, 3:18:04‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© are Bocconi University's undergraduate programs good",
    "answer": "yes",
    "timestamp": "27/10/2021, 9:37:59‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© could you please review his ouac and add program choices whenever possible today?",
    "answer": "Ok I‚Äôll try",
    "timestamp": "31/10/2021, 12:46:46‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Just need to know one thing can I write the fact that I was nominated for position of head boy",
    "answer": "No",
    "timestamp": "31/10/2021, 6:25:06‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Logged out",
    "answer": "What major are you looking to do",
    "timestamp": "31/10/2021, 6:25:34‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Business management",
    "answer": "So I can plug major options accordingly",
    "timestamp": "31/10/2021, 6:26:00‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Just talked with abu n we have decided on marketing",
    "answer": "Ok I have added all the programs",
    "timestamp": "31/10/2021, 6:30:52‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Approximately how many words does it need to be",
    "answer": "UK PS?",
    "timestamp": "2021-05-11T23:32:40",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "üëç",
    "answer": "pls ineed the login details",
    "timestamp": "25/11/2021, 10:48:43‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "1Saad#saad",
    "answer": "saad we cant put like 6 awards for grade 9 all of which pretty much sound the same",
    "timestamp": "27/11/2021, 10:59:36‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok sure",
    "answer": "yes dont login abhi",
    "timestamp": "27/11/2021, 11:09:00‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I'll login at 12",
    "answer": "also i doint see the Day fresh one",
    "timestamp": "27/11/2021, 11:10:00‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I hv heard that because many students apply for Business, it is more difficult to get admission in that subject",
    "answer": "Eco",
    "timestamp": "27/11/2021, 11:53:48‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© how should I write about my results in grade 11 because we didn't receive any percentage from the school, only grades n the highest possible grade is A",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Hamda Khan Dignosco‚Å© pls can you guide",
    "timestamp": "28/11/2021, 4:49:30‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I am calling you wait",
    "answer": "have all the changes been done",
    "timestamp": "28/11/2021, 8:36:54‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Except for that everything is complete",
    "answer": "Ok pls do so I can review and close",
    "timestamp": "29/11/2021, 11:49:38‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "At school rn",
    "answer": "Can I review",
    "timestamp": "29/11/2021, 11:50:07‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "By 3 the application will be complete",
    "answer": "whats missing",
    "timestamp": "30/11/2021, 12:06:38‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tha activities which need to be changed",
    "answer": "?",
    "timestamp": "30/11/2021, 12:45:16‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes",
    "answer": "saad have u made changes again to activities i edited",
    "timestamp": "30/11/2021, 3:40:04‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I only edited the activities about Certificate of Outstanding achievement;initially there were 5 or 6 n since u had told me that there should be fewer so I wrote the same info about positions but in fewer activities",
    "answer": "i have deleted the animal farm one, its total crap",
    "timestamp": "30/11/2021, 4:01:00‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I just didn't know whether to mention the name Dayfresh or there or not",
    "answer": "Just let it be",
    "timestamp": "30/11/2021, 4:45:29‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Should I show SAT score rn or add Dec SAT result",
    "answer": "Show this one and we will send dec as well when they come",
    "timestamp": "30/11/2021, 4:49:43‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© you will need to double check the formatting of his essays in the actual app",
    "timestamp": "30/11/2021, 4:54:10‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "N I hv added 1 new activity: member of Cybernetics society",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "30/11/2021, 10:00:29‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "How should I do that",
    "answer": "will need to delete and re add",
    "timestamp": "30/11/2021, 10:02:18‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I think it's better like it is rn because there are chances of error",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "30/11/2021, 10:03:40‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "John Muir Earl Warren. Thurgood Marshall. Elenor Roosevelt. Seventh. Sixth. RevellLe.",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© pls see formating of the essays pls",
    "timestamp": "30/11/2021, 10:04:27‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok let me know when you log out I‚Äôll check",
    "answer": "im out",
    "timestamp": "30/11/2021, 10:05:04‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is ED binding for the whole world or for the country where the university is",
    "answer": "Country",
    "timestamp": "2021-09-12T12:32:12",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does ED mean here",
    "answer": "Early decision",
    "timestamp": "2021-09-12T13:26:35",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I know what it stands for but what does it mean in case for the country",
    "answer": "Means if you get in to a US uni through early decision , then you have to attend that uni only in the US",
    "timestamp": "2021-09-12T13:28:20",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Saad here- Should I apply to a few more universities now, maybe one or two ivy league ones [Image]",
    "answer": "Let‚Äôs discuss over a call",
    "timestamp": "23/12/2021, 2:33:52‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok üëç",
    "answer": "Things discussed. Apps to be submitted asap Babson Tufts CMU Michigan (feb 1) UIUC Uni of Southern California (15 jan )",
    "timestamp": "25/12/2021, 6:03:40‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "OK thanks",
    "answer": "Tufts essay 2 should be minimum 200 words",
    "timestamp": "27/12/2021, 6:34:18‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "There was another page which I saw rn while looking at the answer",
    "answer": "hmm",
    "timestamp": "28/12/2021, 2:44:59‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "Saad have you fixed everything",
    "timestamp": "28/12/2021, 6:13:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Submitted all the non liberal arts unis except CMU n BU",
    "answer": "What about the liberal arts ones",
    "timestamp": "30/12/2021, 10:03:59‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "Make sure sat score is sent officially to all universities",
    "timestamp": "2022-03-01T11:58:45",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Any ED options left in USA",
    "answer": "no",
    "timestamp": "2022-07-01T17:32:54",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© please confirm",
    "answer": "Ones which require it‚Äôs recommended that you send all",
    "timestamp": "2022-08-01T14:38:12",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I pls apply to other places around the world like University of Amsterdam, Monash, University of Melbourne etc",
    "answer": "Why tho",
    "timestamp": "2022-08-01T15:56:06",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I have spoken to him we aren‚Äôt doing",
    "answer": "Uni of Amsterdam ok but even then you have way better options",
    "timestamp": "2022-08-01T17:04:01",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok good job",
    "answer": "üëå",
    "timestamp": "2022-10-01T11:31:55",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Should I choose academic or general training",
    "answer": "Academic pls",
    "timestamp": "2022-12-01T19:45:58",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Should I opt for a computer delivered ielts?",
    "answer": "Yea",
    "timestamp": "2022-12-01T19:50:47",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many years of English language study should I right for ielts registering",
    "answer": "10-12 years",
    "timestamp": "2022-12-01T21:55:59",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "Pls share ucas login details",
    "timestamp": "14/01/2022, 12:02:46‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "#16Musfirah#",
    "answer": "you have only added one internship",
    "timestamp": "17/01/2022, 5:40:32‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "He doesn't have more",
    "answer": "Also I think Durham is a way better choice versus Edinburgh",
    "timestamp": "17/01/2022, 9:25:46‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do I need to fill the form rn or after offers",
    "answer": "Now",
    "timestamp": "20/01/2022, 1:35:52‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Should I submit my SAT score to Bocconi or sign up for their application test",
    "answer": "SAT",
    "timestamp": "25/01/2022, 8:39:15‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I can not see any payment option for the Bachelors program",
    "answer": "these are masters programs",
    "timestamp": "25/01/2022, 11:52:16‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "So you havent accepted it yet?",
    "answer": "Saad pls accept the kings email",
    "timestamp": "28/01/2022, 3:15:21‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "For the referee contact information at York University Leadership profile form do I need to give contact numbers of the places where I did the extracurricular activities",
    "answer": "Yes if they‚Äôve asked",
    "timestamp": "29/01/2022, 4:06:49‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Alhamdulillah offer received at Wilfrid Laurier University",
    "answer": "amazing MA",
    "timestamp": "30/01/2022, 8:49:32‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "IELTS result",
    "answer": "cool",
    "timestamp": "2022-02-02T14:33:19",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is confirmation of agent",
    "answer": "Dignosco is your agent",
    "timestamp": "2022-08-02T14:35:33",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Alhamdulillah offer received from Western University, Canada",
    "answer": "Congrats",
    "timestamp": "2022-11-02T16:08:15",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm trying to find their official email address",
    "answer": "Any updates",
    "timestamp": "2022-09-03T15:25:22",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Alhamdulillah unconditional offer of admission received from UC Davis",
    "answer": "Congrats great news",
    "timestamp": "2022-12-03T11:04:56",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Alhamdulillah",
    "answer": "congrats",
    "timestamp": "18/03/2022, 10:36:26‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "September is better I think",
    "answer": "Yes choose both",
    "timestamp": "19/03/2022, 10:32:29‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Kind of conditional",
    "answer": "Oh wow",
    "timestamp": "19/03/2022, 8:21:42‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Need to understand meaning of wait list.",
    "answer": "Means that they haven‚Äôt refused you",
    "timestamp": "20/03/2022, 4:14:48‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Babson, Bates, and couple of others so far",
    "answer": "Yes will discuss with saad and send some updates",
    "timestamp": "20/03/2022, 4:15:51‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "That‚Äôs great",
    "answer": "wow",
    "timestamp": "25/03/2022, 7:35:56‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this good university?",
    "answer": "It is fantastic",
    "timestamp": "25/03/2022, 7:38:30‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Congratulations Saad. Bocconi has a good name",
    "answer": "USC?",
    "timestamp": "25/03/2022, 7:46:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Didn't get in.",
    "answer": "BU?",
    "timestamp": "26/03/2022, 10:48:30‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "No from NYU and Dartmouth",
    "answer": "Abdullah will have a call today",
    "timestamp": "2022-02-04T00:57:22",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Would it be a good idea sending my resume n Rotaract president certificate to U of T Rotman",
    "answer": "sure do it",
    "timestamp": "17/04/2022, 10:49:02‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Masha Allah",
    "answer": "Very nice Ma",
    "timestamp": "20/04/2022, 12:48:38‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "If he gets in Babson or UIUC, sure. Or Dartmouth. Those are his top üëçüòÅ",
    "answer": ":/",
    "timestamp": "20/04/2022, 6:30:40‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© any idea when Rotman decision is going to be released",
    "answer": "It‚Äôs ok going",
    "timestamp": "20/04/2022, 6:32:43‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Wow. Congratulations beta. Proud of you",
    "answer": "WOW",
    "timestamp": "25/04/2022, 4:12:56‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 As including Mathematics",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Abdullah Akhtar‚Å© ab treat kara dou bhai",
    "timestamp": "25/04/2022, 4:17:09‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Work hard plz",
    "answer": "Saad send a pic pls [Image]",
    "timestamp": "25/04/2022, 4:31:19‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also received a no from UCL",
    "answer": "Saad I need your picture pls [Image]",
    "timestamp": "25/04/2022, 9:27:01‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Not seeing any option to do it on the website",
    "answer": "Has to be done on ucas",
    "timestamp": "28/04/2022, 12:33:31‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© when is the deadline for accepting the offer",
    "answer": "you have the month of may",
    "timestamp": "28/04/2022, 12:50:30‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Omg congratulations!!",
    "answer": "Congrats:)",
    "timestamp": "2022-03-05T10:52:14",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© @‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© is there any other medical test required?",
    "answer": "Pls mail them again and request for earlier appointment",
    "timestamp": "2022-08-08T12:41:10",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Rizwan, this is very disappointing that you have made a claim yesterday but could not show us while day when you sent the list before to Saad. And no one even checked with him nor discussed this list with him earlier. And this is a very important check list",
    "answer": "Abdullah my apologies",
    "timestamp": "2022-09-08T10:29:16",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "It didn't happen",
    "answer": "MHDISLAMABAD@iom.int",
    "timestamp": "2022-09-08T11:18:17",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéYou removed Anicca Usmani [Image]",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Saad Akhtar‚Å© did you send the email",
    "timestamp": "2022-09-08T12:11:28",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes",
    "answer": "ok if you dont get a response. pls mail them again by 1PM",
    "timestamp": "2022-10-08T10:32:39",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok üëç",
    "answer": "any update?",
    "timestamp": "2022-10-08T10:36:29",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Appointment got rescheduled to 22nd July at karachi branch",
    "answer": "August you mean?",
    "timestamp": "2022-10-08T20:18:27",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes",
    "answer": "Please mail again on same email chain",
    "timestamp": "2022-10-08T20:24:08",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Better",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Abdullah Akhtar‚Å© can you please prepare affidavit of support",
    "timestamp": "2022-10-08T20:30:13",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "InshaAllah",
    "answer": "Results ?",
    "timestamp": "2022-10-08T20:32:06",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Not yet",
    "answer": "Ok I think they‚Äôre out tho [Image]",
    "timestamp": "2022-11-08T10:14:53",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 As",
    "answer": "Some names in clearing: City University London Queen Mary London SOAS Sussex Cardiff (International Year 1) Newcastle Uni",
    "timestamp": "2022-11-08T10:34:41",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Computer Science n Management Science",
    "answer": "Ok we can look at that too",
    "timestamp": "2022-11-08T12:15:49",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Warwick not yet but hopefully soon",
    "answer": "I‚Äôm asking the warwick person",
    "timestamp": "2022-11-08T12:16:04",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© is it possible to add the Computer Science program in my UCAS profile",
    "answer": "we can call and find out from Edinburgh",
    "timestamp": "2022-11-08T12:18:49",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://digital.ucas.com/coursedisplay/courses/89cef5c3-64cc-74d5-d900-c58117c3ab48?academicYearId=2022",
    "answer": "For UK visa app please note that you have to mention your last ten year travel history. Please make sure that you put your travel history down on a word document. There is a separate question on travel to UK. Separate question for travel to Europe, America and Australia Separate question for travel to rest of the world. You will need to specify date of entry and exit, country travelled  and number of days in that particular year. Please compile this data from 2012-2022 asap so you donot waste time while completing the visa app. [Image]",
    "timestamp": "2022-11-08T14:07:10",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Abu n I both agreed to check Warwick, Edinburgh, UCL n KCL for clearing programs on 18th",
    "answer": "I think look at Cardiff also",
    "timestamp": "16/08/2022, 7:10:05‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "6 minutes remaining [Image]",
    "answer": "No LSE has rejected you",
    "timestamp": "18/08/2022, 12:09:31‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Saad you should go for remarking for Computer science and inform LSE immediately that you are doing this ‚Äé[18/08/2022, 12:43:32‚ÄØPM] Abdullah Akhtar: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "answer": "Pls go for the recheck",
    "timestamp": "18/08/2022, 12:42:42‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Applying to SOAS and getting admission does not affect USA plans, does it",
    "answer": "No",
    "timestamp": "18/08/2022, 12:52:21‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hello saad",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Saad Akhtar‚Å© pls provide him as application deadline for Royal Hollaway is tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "18/08/2022, 12:53:49‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Required documents:- * Passport clear copy * Academic certificate/transcripts * Current email address * Contact number * home address complete * Valid ielts result if you have",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Abdullah Akhtar‚Å© pls we need all this info",
    "timestamp": "18/08/2022, 12:59:11‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Passport ?",
    "answer": "Yes I will be sending them an email today as well [Image]",
    "timestamp": "18/08/2022, 1:20:53‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I don't want to apply to more than these",
    "answer": "But he said london ?",
    "timestamp": "18/08/2022, 1:26:12‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I just talked to abu n told him I don't want to apply to many places",
    "answer": "I‚Äôll speak with him also",
    "timestamp": "18/08/2022, 1:27:33‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Any",
    "answer": "Sept 2022",
    "timestamp": "18/08/2022, 1:40:25‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "It doesn't impact when the decision will be posted right?",
    "answer": "no",
    "timestamp": "18/08/2022, 1:40:42‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Then parents are fine with Jan 23 also",
    "answer": "I think let‚Äôs do sept 2022 for now",
    "timestamp": "18/08/2022, 1:41:28‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Any other nationality ?",
    "answer": "Sometimes these programs just don‚Äôt open in Jan also",
    "timestamp": "18/08/2022, 1:42:09‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "So u mean that there is a chance that a listed program may not actually begin in Jan?",
    "answer": "Warwick doesn't have any course",
    "timestamp": "18/08/2022, 1:42:57‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the program options available from these universities [Image]",
    "answer": "Edinburgh is also closed",
    "timestamp": "18/08/2022, 1:44:20‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Some forms also need to be filled for UC-SB",
    "answer": "Saad why don‚Äôt you call me so we can discuss",
    "timestamp": "18/08/2022, 1:57:04‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok sure",
    "answer": "pls send proper pdf copy",
    "timestamp": "18/08/2022, 1:58:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ty but I only want to apply to the 2 already agreed",
    "answer": "cool",
    "timestamp": "18/08/2022, 2:28:28‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "No",
    "answer": "hello",
    "timestamp": "18/08/2022, 2:47:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad AKHTAR",
    "student_phone": "+379644192",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "David Taylor from SOAS will be visiting the Dignosco Karachi Office on Friday October 12 between 3pm-5pm for a session for undergraduate and foundation related programs. Please attend.",
    "answer": "Hey Saad expecting you tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "2018-09-10T14:33:50",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What time?",
    "answer": "3",
    "timestamp": "2018-11-10T16:52:16",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I have tuition 2:15-4:15 tom",
    "answer": "Ok so come after",
    "timestamp": "2018-11-10T16:57:09",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "My school ptm is at 4-6 after that",
    "answer": "Yea leave at 4",
    "timestamp": "2018-11-10T20:09:20",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What do i need for tomorrow",
    "answer": "Bring pair of extra slippers",
    "timestamp": "2018-12-10T23:53:23",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Wednesday?",
    "answer": "Saad pls also share your weekly tuition schedule",
    "timestamp": "14/10/2018, 9:06:52‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Wednesday 3pm it is [Image]",
    "answer": "Saad when can we meet",
    "timestamp": "15/10/2018, 2:08:54‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Saad Noor‚Å© we need to make a resume for an internship",
    "timestamp": "22/11/2018, 4:15:51‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "When",
    "answer": "Come before Friday and make one",
    "timestamp": "19/12/2018, 7:37:30‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "When can I come in for a meeting",
    "answer": "you can come tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "19/12/2018, 10:56:46‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I won't be able to make it today, can I come tomorrow at 4:30 instead?",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "20/12/2018, 10:57:07‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1eAnqJCGXOxU_SMaBH-rki2BTGeH6fnoVRoVanNWxrZQ",
    "answer": "?",
    "timestamp": "21/12/2018, 9:00:31‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "My cv",
    "answer": "Please email in a word doc",
    "timestamp": "21/12/2018, 9:13:37‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I've sent it",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "22/12/2018, 12:26:56‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I've sent it again",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "22/12/2018, 1:55:49‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Any update on the internship?",
    "answer": "Please remind me tom",
    "timestamp": "26/12/2018, 11:12:26‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "^",
    "answer": "The Taamer bank president replied but said it can possibly happen in first week of jan",
    "timestamp": "27/12/2018, 5:16:36‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok [Image]",
    "answer": "We will have a session on Thursday at 4.30PM with  Ms Sharne Proctor, Head of International Admissions- Durham Univeristy. Please make sure you attend.",
    "timestamp": "2019-01-02T14:25:20",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I have a meeting on Wednesday instead of Monday",
    "answer": "Sure",
    "timestamp": "2019-10-02T21:45:03",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What time is my meeting tomorrow",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Momina Iftikhar Counselling‚Å©",
    "timestamp": "17/02/2019, 10:56:50‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes",
    "answer": "Saad please share a draft",
    "timestamp": "27/08/2019, 1:03:15‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I come tomorrow at 3:15",
    "answer": "Yes",
    "timestamp": "2019-05-09T22:14:51",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What time can I come tomorrow",
    "answer": "Come after school",
    "timestamp": "2019-10-09T23:04:14",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I come 3-6",
    "answer": "Yea",
    "timestamp": "2019-10-09T23:04:59",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "My predicted grades are 2 A*s 1A and 2Bs",
    "answer": "Great can you break them subject wise",
    "timestamp": "2019-12-09T22:42:31",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I would like to meet u guys regarding saads process",
    "answer": "Sure",
    "timestamp": "2019-12-09T22:57:13",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who should I meet regarding my personal statement?",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Zainab UK‚Å© please can you speak to him",
    "timestamp": "28/09/2019, 1:14:54‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Alright thanks",
    "answer": "Amy  Mitchell from SOAS will be coming to Dignosco on Friday between 2-6 PM to discuss all undergraduate and foundation programs for Fall 2020. You need to attend.",
    "timestamp": "2019-04-10T18:51:39",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I come tomorrow at 3",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Zainab UK‚Å© you need to have a chat with Saad. We need to wrap the ps soon",
    "timestamp": "2019-02-12T21:53:26",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also when can he submit his personal statement? It‚Äôs December",
    "answer": "We will finalise and submit in next few days",
    "timestamp": "2019-02-12T21:54:31",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "When can I discuss the draft",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Zainab UK‚Å©",
    "timestamp": "2019-06-12T20:25:52",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "üëç",
    "answer": "Cool",
    "timestamp": "17/12/2019, 6:37:24‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Now fingers crossed ü§û [Image]",
    "answer": "Please accept",
    "timestamp": "17/12/2019, 6:46:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is it?",
    "answer": "We‚Äôre official partners with kings",
    "timestamp": "2020-09-01T23:30:36",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "Any updates ?",
    "timestamp": "2020-09-01T23:31:10",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Saad has offers from king‚Äôs, queen Mary n soas so far!!! N Uof T from Canada",
    "answer": "Yes , it‚Äôs normal with LSE UCL",
    "timestamp": "2020-12-03T20:29:47",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Awesome!! Congratulations!!",
    "answer": "Amazing",
    "timestamp": "26/03/2020, 3:00:41‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thx [Image]",
    "answer": "What are we deciding",
    "timestamp": "26/03/2020, 3:59:49‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "A*A*A",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© best option seems to go for the certificate vs deferring",
    "timestamp": "2020-04-04T14:49:47",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "From CIE ‚Äé[07/04/2020, 10:13:16‚ÄØPM] Tanzeela Saads Mom: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "answer": "so seems its the teachers who will really make the final call",
    "timestamp": "2020-07-04T22:12:20",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "So we shall go ahead with  may 2020",
    "answer": "yea",
    "timestamp": "2020-07-04T22:17:42",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok no problem",
    "answer": "no news from lse?",
    "timestamp": "2020-08-04T14:32:25",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I think at the moment closed for Easter",
    "answer": "Not since last 10 days",
    "timestamp": "13/04/2020, 2:15:49‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Saad‚Äôs friend also got a similar call",
    "answer": "Was it someone from pakistan",
    "timestamp": "15/04/2020, 4:18:34‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes he can to be on the safe side but I doubt it will be conducted",
    "answer": "hell probably need it",
    "timestamp": "15/04/2020, 11:22:26‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "When should I reply to my UCAS offers",
    "answer": "What are we finalising",
    "timestamp": "23/04/2020, 9:11:43‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "If I accept my Canada offer, will it affect my UCAS?",
    "answer": "Not at all",
    "timestamp": "27/04/2020, 11:45:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also he‚Äôs choosing waterloo over UofT",
    "answer": "What‚Äôs his program",
    "timestamp": "27/04/2020, 11:46:52‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "But Waterloo accepted me for work placement which I would prefer over U of T",
    "answer": "ok besides that I see no other reason for picking Waterloo over uOfT",
    "timestamp": "27/04/2020, 11:48:43‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "So u say U of T",
    "answer": "yes",
    "timestamp": "27/04/2020, 11:50:49‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm accepting my UCAS offers right now",
    "answer": "Ok so Ucl and ?",
    "timestamp": "29/04/2020, 11:31:02‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Should I go ahead?",
    "answer": "I personally think you should",
    "timestamp": "29/04/2020, 11:36:33‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Both are A*AA but ucl specifies A* in maths",
    "answer": "I personally think it‚Äôs ok because QM is always open during clearing",
    "timestamp": "29/04/2020, 11:38:23‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Alright, I've submitted my choices",
    "answer": "Cool",
    "timestamp": "29/04/2020, 11:44:59‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there a change in policy",
    "answer": "https://my.ieltsessentials.com/IELTS?countryId=157&testCentreLocationId=2378&testVenueId=3657&isSELT=false&utm_source=facebook&utm_medium=facebook-cpc&utm_campaign=ielts-google-karachi-cd-fy21&gclid=Cj0KCQjwpNr4BRDYARIsAADIx9zorjWMzcjYMcCGG0B1rlFd-CxYNM9grdAsjat048RFAhn_ydXTjm0aAmQfEALw_wcB",
    "timestamp": "25/07/2020, 11:55:29‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I call ucl as well?",
    "answer": "It will update on track in 48 hours",
    "timestamp": "2020-11-08T10:15:41",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Should I call Kings as well?",
    "answer": "You can try",
    "timestamp": "2020-11-08T13:14:23",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "N hearing a lot of kids haven‚Äôt met their offers ‚Äé[11/08/2020, 6:41:26‚ÄØPM] Tanzeela Saads Mom: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "answer": "its the same issue with IB students, but honestly colleges wont budge too much",
    "timestamp": "2020-11-08T13:50:29",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.pakistantoday.com.pk/2020/08/11/controversy-mars-downgraded-cambridge-results/amp/",
    "answer": "They‚Äôve been quite unfair overall",
    "timestamp": "2020-12-08T00:25:52",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "But they should consider its very unfair",
    "answer": "???",
    "timestamp": "2020-12-08T00:30:44",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "It says for both ucl and King's the offer has not been met",
    "answer": "Share screenshot ‚Äé[13/08/2020, 12:49:52‚ÄØPM] Saad Noor: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "timestamp": "13/08/2020, 12:41:29‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I not apply through UCAS while doing a foundation course?",
    "answer": "You can‚Äôt do kings foundation",
    "timestamp": "13/08/2020, 10:44:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why?",
    "answer": "Because it‚Äôs closed",
    "timestamp": "14/08/2020, 12:07:36‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "But Saad‚Äôs friend Zain is applying for durham foundation course",
    "answer": "Yes Durham is open",
    "timestamp": "14/08/2020, 12:09:59‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "If I choose soas in clearing, but my school is also making an appeal for me, can I opt out of clearing if my appeal is successful? [Image]",
    "answer": "It might all work out Saad",
    "timestamp": "14/08/2020, 12:36:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Fingers crossed",
    "answer": "Let‚Äôs hope man",
    "timestamp": "17/08/2020, 8:48:25‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Otherwise it would b extremely unfair [Image]",
    "answer": "Oh wow",
    "timestamp": "17/08/2020, 9:07:05‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "It won't let me access the portal as I applied through an agent",
    "answer": "Share here",
    "timestamp": "18/08/2020, 7:38:16‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thx Rizwan",
    "answer": "No issues",
    "timestamp": "18/08/2020, 7:48:28‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© pls look into the matter",
    "answer": "Update will only happen when revised results are issued, and we will need to then send them to kings",
    "timestamp": "18/08/2020, 8:09:48‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Wouldn't it be better to do it now?",
    "answer": "Also this is neither on Kgs letterhead nor signed off by counsellor",
    "timestamp": "18/08/2020, 8:11:41‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "It's signed by Ms shumaila",
    "answer": "States her name but I can‚Äôt see a sign",
    "timestamp": "18/08/2020, 8:12:04‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "So that atleast we would've done our part",
    "answer": "Yes Hamda will do it",
    "timestamp": "18/08/2020, 8:12:44‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "She isn't on this group",
    "answer": "Sadaf pls add",
    "timestamp": "18/08/2020, 8:15:59‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Asa pls update the verified certificates on kings portal, thx üôèüèª",
    "answer": "Hamda pls do if it‚Äôs still not done",
    "timestamp": "19/08/2020, 10:49:39‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Should I upload it?",
    "answer": "Hamda pls do",
    "timestamp": "19/08/2020, 1:18:56‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you guys please call Kings and ask",
    "answer": "Would accept what",
    "timestamp": "19/08/2020, 2:15:08‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "They saying deadline is over",
    "answer": "So your O level English should be sufficient for ielts waiver",
    "timestamp": "19/08/2020, 2:19:08‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can u guys do something abt this pls",
    "answer": "Have you received predicted grades from Kgs",
    "timestamp": "19/08/2020, 2:19:56‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "School has told his grades hv changed",
    "answer": "What are new grades",
    "timestamp": "19/08/2020, 2:20:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "He‚Äôs meeting kings offer",
    "answer": "And UCL ?",
    "timestamp": "19/08/2020, 2:20:29‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Saad is talking to shumaila",
    "answer": "What was kings offer",
    "timestamp": "19/08/2020, 2:21:28‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "A*AA",
    "answer": "They didn‚Äôt need A* in math ya?",
    "timestamp": "19/08/2020, 2:25:38‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "No",
    "answer": "Ok great and I‚Äôm gonna shoot out an email to Kaitlyn in the next one hour",
    "timestamp": "19/08/2020, 2:25:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hope it works",
    "answer": "IA",
    "timestamp": "19/08/2020, 2:26:27‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are King's asking for it?",
    "answer": "no i am emailing",
    "timestamp": "19/08/2020, 3:21:17‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I never imagined we would hv to go through all this",
    "answer": "unfortunately non of this was in anyones control",
    "timestamp": "19/08/2020, 3:35:23‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes put in the id",
    "answer": "When was the ucas app submitted",
    "timestamp": "19/08/2020, 4:31:04‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Checking",
    "answer": "Was it Nov or dec last year",
    "timestamp": "19/08/2020, 4:31:25‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I think December last year",
    "answer": "Tell exact date pls",
    "timestamp": "19/08/2020, 4:31:42‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "One second",
    "answer": "Once it‚Äôs submitted you get an email from UCAS",
    "timestamp": "19/08/2020, 4:31:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Any update?",
    "answer": "so far theyre not budging",
    "timestamp": "19/08/2020, 4:46:02‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Shall I try for Queen Mary again if there's no positive response?",
    "answer": "yes there is no harm in that",
    "timestamp": "19/08/2020, 5:26:56‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I got in but declined it yesterday",
    "answer": "Pls call them and ask to restore",
    "timestamp": "19/08/2020, 5:38:23‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "They said they would email me",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "19/08/2020, 7:35:53‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I got my results from school",
    "answer": "Ok share pls [Image]",
    "timestamp": "19/08/2020, 8:36:44‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Should he call king‚Äôs again",
    "answer": "Yes pls call on the appeal number",
    "timestamp": "19/08/2020, 8:38:06‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can the King's Portal please be updated",
    "answer": "i am doing it Saad",
    "timestamp": "20/08/2020, 4:32:06‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Alright",
    "answer": "ive sent the message on the portal [Image] [Image]",
    "timestamp": "20/08/2020, 4:35:39‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I'm abit anxious it hasn't updated yet",
    "answer": "No issues it‚Äôll be sorted",
    "timestamp": "22/08/2020, 6:27:16‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "Saad they have outright rejected 7 of our candidates",
    "timestamp": "22/08/2020, 10:59:57‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "So I would get rejected outright if I applied",
    "answer": "If they‚Äôre open to it . Can think of a retake ?",
    "timestamp": "22/08/2020, 11:14:07‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "It would be tough to do a retake while studying at uni",
    "answer": "That‚Äôs true",
    "timestamp": "22/08/2020, 11:15:20‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Forget kings now, it‚Äôs chapter is closed",
    "answer": "Fair",
    "timestamp": "22/08/2020, 11:17:03‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "And they entertain 2nd year transfers as well",
    "answer": "Yes they do",
    "timestamp": "22/08/2020, 11:25:32‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Saad u can try",
    "answer": "https://www.lse.ac.uk/study-at-lse/uolip/entry-requirements",
    "timestamp": "22/08/2020, 11:26:27‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "It depends on how much better these are in terms of econ than Queen mary",
    "answer": "Durham is very top end",
    "timestamp": "22/08/2020, 11:30:02‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Isn't Durham more focused on the sciences?",
    "answer": "No very heavy on social sciences and business",
    "timestamp": "22/08/2020, 11:34:10‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Or is it just done on a grades basis",
    "answer": "Of course it‚Äôs a full fledged ucas app",
    "timestamp": "22/08/2020, 11:40:33‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "And the submission deadline is 15th Jan as well",
    "answer": "Yup [Image] [Image] [Image]",
    "timestamp": "22/08/2020, 11:48:44‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pls tell us",
    "answer": "Wow",
    "timestamp": "25/08/2020, 10:20:44‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Dear Mr Noor, Firstly, congratulations on receiving a conditional offer to study at King‚Äôs College London this year and thank you for selecting us as your Firm or Insurance choice University. We recognise the distress and disruption created by the global pandemic and we remain committed to a fair, flexible and consistent admissions process. Although we were initially unable to confirm your place, we have since reviewed your application and are delighted to confirm that you now meet the conditions of your offer! If you would like to take up your place on Political Economy BA/BSc (Full-time) (L200) at King‚Äôs, starting in September 2020, please refer your application to us via UCAS Track by 5pm on Thursday 27th August 2020. Referring your application on UCAS Track: If you are currently holding a place at another university, you will need to release yourself into Clearing before you can refer your application to us. To refer your application on Track, first select King‚Äôs College London (Institution code K60). When searching for your programme, you will need to: Select ‚Äúother‚Äù as your course choice. Then enter L200 . Please make sure to use capital letters when entering the course code otherwise it will not be recognised. Please ensure you refer yourself for L200 as this is the programme you were holding an offer for. If you refer yourself to a different programme on UCAS your application will be automatically rejected. Once you have completed these steps, we will update your offer Unconditional Firm on UCAS Track within 5 working days. If you no longer wish to take up your place at King‚Äôs, there is no further action required and we wish you the best of luck with your future studies. We know how hard students have worked to achieve the grades they deserve and to have the opportunity to study for their chosen degree at King‚Äôs. Thank you for your patience and understanding during this uncertain time and congratulations on securing your place! Best wishes, Lucy Burrowes Central Admission Officer, Political Economy, Faculty of Social Science & Public Policy (UG)",
    "answer": "This means you‚Äôre in [Image]",
    "timestamp": "25/08/2020, 10:21:59‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéThis message was deleted.",
    "answer": "You can call kings now",
    "timestamp": "25/08/2020, 10:25:34‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "It‚Äôs closed",
    "answer": "It‚Äôs 6.30 in london rn",
    "timestamp": "25/08/2020, 10:26:00‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "No they close at 5pm",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "25/08/2020, 10:26:06‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Maybe they r open",
    "answer": "Yea pls try [Image]",
    "timestamp": "25/08/2020, 10:26:19‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes. They had to manually accept it on UCAS so no way they can reject me now",
    "answer": "Saad can ya make a quick call to them and ask to update the portal so you can pay",
    "timestamp": "27/08/2020, 5:35:20‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do it now",
    "answer": "Pls before kings closes",
    "timestamp": "27/08/2020, 5:40:23‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "But put a message on the portal just in case",
    "answer": "Sadaf I‚Äôve sent the message on portal",
    "timestamp": "27/08/2020, 5:53:59‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Too much water in Bukhari",
    "answer": "Yes it‚Äôs been quite bad",
    "timestamp": "31/08/2020, 10:53:24‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "We hv water in our basement tooüò¨",
    "answer": "Just sad state of affairs",
    "timestamp": "31/08/2020, 11:11:45‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I still haven't received an update from King's, should I call them?",
    "answer": "Yes pls do",
    "timestamp": "2020-01-09T13:04:03",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "They've given me my CAS number",
    "answer": "Great",
    "timestamp": "2020-02-09T22:31:23",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I already declined them through UCAS when I got my King's offer but they're still sending me emails",
    "answer": "Yea",
    "timestamp": "2020-10-09T16:31:34",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Saad is doing online 1st semester",
    "answer": "ok have you guys paid the fee",
    "timestamp": "15/09/2020, 3:51:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Saad said first week October",
    "answer": "ok pls pay the tuition",
    "timestamp": "15/09/2020, 3:52:46‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Saad said they will send us invoice first week October",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "15/09/2020, 3:53:42‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "N then deadline is 31stcoctober",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "15/09/2020, 3:53:56‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Noor",
    "student_phone": "+5627616390",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© please note above are the three programs we are starting with",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "28/11/2024, 2:48:33‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hello all, when are we meeting this week?",
    "answer": "Let‚Äôs target Thursday",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-12T19:12:58",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "üëç",
    "answer": "Subject: Request for GMAT Waiver for Oxford EMBA Application Dear Admissions Team, I hope this email finds you well. I am writing to express my interest in the Oxford EMBA program at Sa√Ød Business School. As I prepare my application, I would like to inquire about the possibility of obtaining a GMAT/EMBA Assesment waiver. I have in depth work experience and have also been part of various startups as a founder/investor in the Pakistani eco system. I have attached my resume as well for your reference. I would greatly appreciate it if you could consider my request for this waiver. If there is any additional information I need to provide or if you require any further documentation, please let me know. Thank you for your time and consideration. I look forward to hearing from you soon. Best, Saad",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-12T19:20:45",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thanks Rizwan, any suggests on my CV before I send thr email",
    "answer": "So at this stage this is ok to be attached as is. We are going to eventually trim this down.",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-12T21:54:39",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok let‚Äôs wait a bit",
    "answer": "Cool",
    "timestamp": "2024-04-12T21:05:43",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "EMBA its already specified in the email",
    "answer": "just reply and say the EMBA anyways",
    "timestamp": "2024-05-12T13:59:29",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Oxford",
    "answer": "Hey Saad, can we have the fee collected ?",
    "timestamp": "2024-06-12T00:43:15",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is it a bank transfer or cash?",
    "answer": "Hey you can do cash or cash cheque . If you do cash cheque just make two pls",
    "timestamp": "2024-06-12T09:46:15",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "üëçapologies, but what was the the total amount again? And the payment terms are 100% upfront or different",
    "answer": "Hey Saad, Sadaf had discount your fee to USD 5000. Our base price is USD 8000 onwards. yup it‚Äôs up front. You can pay in pkr equivalent.",
    "timestamp": "2024-06-12T10:32:58",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Please share the name and the number of the person who will be collecting. My office will coordinate with him",
    "answer": "Zulfiqar",
    "timestamp": "2024-07-12T11:07:56",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok let‚Äôs meet Friday then",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Saad EMBA‚Å© btw any response from any of the schools on the waiver",
    "timestamp": "2024-12-12T06:55:59",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "And asked to also meet with the team",
    "answer": "ok pls share the response here",
    "timestamp": "2024-12-12T22:00:44",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes 1130-1145 I'll be there",
    "answer": "Hey Saad any reply from Oxford on the waiver",
    "timestamp": "13/12/2024, 11:03:47‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I'll email them again",
    "answer": "Ok [Image]",
    "timestamp": "18/12/2024, 4:30:12‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Emailed Oxford again",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "20/12/2024, 8:16:27‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Haven't heard back from Oxford regarding exemption",
    "answer": "Would be good to send a top up email today",
    "timestamp": "2025-07-01T07:02:28",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hello Rizwan let's speak around 3pm today",
    "answer": "Ok [Image] [Image] [Image]",
    "timestamp": "2025-08-01T10:37:18",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can we speak in the next 30mins?",
    "answer": "Saad sorry have been caught up",
    "timestamp": "14/01/2025, 11:56:40‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay tomorrow is fine",
    "answer": "Hey Saad called you today",
    "timestamp": "14/01/2025, 4:05:44‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What time tomorrow ?",
    "answer": "10:15?",
    "timestamp": "15/01/2025, 9:33:56‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "By then",
    "answer": "Ok [Image]",
    "timestamp": "15/01/2025, 10:19:26‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://interact.london.edu/application1.asp?m=apply&cid=",
    "answer": "Hey Saad",
    "timestamp": "22/01/2025, 10:52:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I will be sending it in a bit",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "23/01/2025, 11:22:43‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi @‚Å®Saad EMBA‚Å© free for a quick call?",
    "answer": "‚ÄéYou deleted this message.",
    "timestamp": "24/01/2025, 4:14:33‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© do we also need to have a call?",
    "answer": "hey ill be free post 4:30",
    "timestamp": "25/01/2025, 3:18:24‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "And they are good to go",
    "answer": "Ok pls pass me their details",
    "timestamp": "26/01/2025, 4:38:09‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi @‚Å®Saad EMBA‚Å© have sent you some documents over email for review. Please have a look",
    "answer": "Hey Saad",
    "timestamp": "26/01/2025, 7:47:23‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Let me know once you have reviewed",
    "answer": "hey is his last name Naeem",
    "timestamp": "26/01/2025, 7:50:59‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Naeem",
    "answer": "these dets too pls",
    "timestamp": "26/01/2025, 9:48:32‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I'll ask him this question and get bacn",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "26/01/2025, 9:49:19‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "ceo@biomasdar.com",
    "answer": "have invited him",
    "timestamp": "27/01/2025, 11:11:03‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Saad EMBA‚Å© can we have a call today at 6:30 my time ?",
    "answer": "both have been invited @‚Å®Saad EMBA‚Å© [Image]",
    "timestamp": "27/01/2025, 3:31:30‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi @‚Å®Saad EMBA‚Å© can we speak now",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Saad EMBA‚Å© also in the employment section. I added Falcon, but others you‚Äôll need to add as questions pertain to any income you make from them etc",
    "timestamp": "27/01/2025, 6:59:24‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "You want me to out all the attachments here?",
    "answer": "yea",
    "timestamp": "27/01/2025, 7:05:57‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hey @‚Å®Saad EMBA‚Å© update ?",
    "answer": "We should really close this out",
    "timestamp": "29/01/2025, 3:59:47‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "hello thanks guys for getting ths application through. when are we starting lbs/Columbia?",
    "answer": "Let‚Äôs discuss timelines tomorrow [Image] [Image]",
    "timestamp": "30/01/2025, 4:58:47‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also @‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© please schedule a meeting on recommendation and LBS/Columbia app",
    "answer": "We can speak later today",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-02T17:02:02",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hello, I hope this email finds you well. I am reaching out regarding the recommendation letter submitted on my behalf by Hasan Aziz Bilgrami. It has come to my attention through his secretary that an incorrect version of the recommendation was submitted in error. Given the importance of this document in accurately reflecting my qualifications and potential, I kindly request permission for Hasan Bilgrami to submit the correct version. If allowed, he is prepared to send the revised recommendation at the earliest convenience. Please let me know if this would be possible and if there are any specific steps we should follow to facilitate this correction. I appreciate your time and consideration and look forward to your response.",
    "answer": "Good to go",
    "timestamp": "2025-12-02T10:55:18",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok thanks for this. Also one more thing came to my mind for this. Let me call you and discuss briefly ‚Äé[12/02/2025, 1:35:53‚ÄØPM] Saad EMBA: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "answer": "ok send on the emba one",
    "timestamp": "2025-12-02T11:04:08",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Point is that we want to see it before he submits it to LBS. So he should work on revised version",
    "answer": "Hey Saad",
    "timestamp": "16/02/2025, 9:00:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "abigail.crichton@sbs.ox.ac.uk",
    "answer": "Dear Mr. Crichton, I hope you are doing well. I had earlier tried to call Alex as well, but somehow could not get through and was told to email you. I had earlier received an email (attached below) from Alex on February 7, which unfortunately i completely missed as i was in between a few travels. I am extremely apologetic for not reverting in time for the required things asked in the mail below, and would be extremely grateful if i am given a few days to send a letter demonstrating my English proficiency as well as elaborating on Question 3 of the essay part of my application. I had also earlier sent an email highlighting that there was an error from one of my recommenders assistant in the recommendation which was sent by them as they had sent an incorrect version, and i had requested if the new version could be mailed to the admissions office ( i am hoping for a reply on this too). I sincerely hope that i am given a little flexibility as Oxford is the only school i am considering for my EMBA.",
    "timestamp": "17/02/2025, 2:36:41‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Should I also mention i had emailed last week aswell but she now off on maternity leaves",
    "answer": "can",
    "timestamp": "17/02/2025, 3:21:37‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Dear Ms. Crichton, I hope you are doing well. I had attempted to reach Alex by phone earlier but was unable to get through and was advised to contact you via email. On February 7, I received an email from Alex (attached below), which I unfortunately missed due to work-related travel and a critical project delivery. I sincerely apologize for not responding in time to the requests outlined in the email. I would be extremely grateful if I could be granted a few additional days to submit a letter demonstrating my English proficiency, as well as to further elaborate on Question 3 of the essay section of my application. Additionally, I previously reached out regarding an error in one of my recommendation letters. The incorrect version was mistakenly submitted by my recommender‚Äôs assistant, and I had requested whether the updated version could be sent to the admissions office instead. I also emailed Hannah regarding this matter but have not yet received a response as she is on maternity leave. I would greatly appreciate any guidance on how to proceed. I truly appreciate your time and consideration and hope for some flexibility in this process, as Oxford is the only school I am considering for my EMBA. Please let me know if there is anything else I need to do to facilitate this. Looking forward to your response. Best regards,",
    "answer": "coo",
    "timestamp": "17/02/2025, 3:53:36‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "good to go",
    "answer": "yup",
    "timestamp": "17/02/2025, 3:55:16‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "made some changes please check",
    "answer": "üëç",
    "timestamp": "17/02/2025, 4:13:12‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok üëç and then let‚Äôs have the revised rec sorted incase they ask for it immediately",
    "answer": "saad is this done",
    "timestamp": "17/02/2025, 8:17:41‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok üëç please share with us before he uploads [Image] [Image] [Image] [Image] [Image] [Image] [Image] [Image]",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Saad EMBA‚Å© have you invited the recommenders on the lbs app ?",
    "timestamp": "20/02/2025, 10:50:44‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Please review other things above when you can",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Saad EMBA‚Å© we should try closing this app tonight pls",
    "timestamp": "24/02/2025, 9:42:38‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Lbs?",
    "answer": "Yup",
    "timestamp": "25/02/2025, 10:35:09‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes [Image]",
    "answer": "such good news",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-03T00:08:40",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What preparations do I need to do?",
    "answer": "Let‚Äôs discuss tomorrow [Image]",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-03T00:31:37",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Chat gpt",
    "answer": "cool",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-03T15:00:27",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yup this is fine also [Image] [Image]",
    "answer": "We should position this as review under LBS ideally",
    "timestamp": "2025-05-03T15:10:32",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Dear Tasfia, I hope you are doing well. I live and work between both Dubai and Karachi. However, my family resides in Dubai, and it would be most convenient for me to use Dubai as my primary location. Please let me know if you need any further clarification. Best regards, Saad",
    "answer": "You have dubai residency yes ?",
    "timestamp": "2025-07-03T11:09:30",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yup",
    "answer": "Dear Tasfia, I hope you are doing well. I work between both Dubai and Karachi. However, my family resides in Dubai, and it would be most convenient for me to use Dubai as my primary location. Please let me know if you need any further clarification. Best regards, Saad",
    "timestamp": "2025-07-03T11:18:14",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thanks",
    "answer": "Hey Saad when are you available to spealk",
    "timestamp": "2025-07-03T13:23:35",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "In 30mins [Image] [Image]",
    "answer": "üëçüëç",
    "timestamp": "2025-07-03T15:43:42",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hey guys let me know when we can connect for lbs and Oxfords interview",
    "answer": "Hey Saad we can connect 7:15 pak time today",
    "timestamp": "2025-08-03T16:42:55",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "At 7pm?",
    "answer": "We can speak in 40 minutes from now",
    "timestamp": "2025-08-03T16:58:34",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://www.sbs.ox.ac.uk/about-us/people/grant-phillips",
    "answer": "https://www.sbs.ox.ac.uk/oxford-experience/blogs/dr-piotr-szulc/taking-my-executive-mba-learning-home-grow-our-family-business?gad_source=1&gclid=Cj0KCQiAlbW-BhCMARIsADnwaso_SBhQVSmtZtKju0vhXCGqPizjs9x7HAs2I-FSfiMY-jmhlee0kg0aAvLjEALw_wcB",
    "timestamp": "2025-08-03T17:57:44",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did the interview go?",
    "answer": "Dear Alex, I hope you're doing well. I thoroughly enjoyed my interview with Grant. It was an insightful and engaging conversation, and I appreciate the opportunity to discuss my application. I am absolutely convinced post my conversation with Grant that the Oxford EMBA is the right fit for me at this time in my career. I would appreciate it if you could share when the Admissions Committee is expected to make its decision. Please let me know if there's anything further required from my side in the meantime. Looking forward to your update. Best regards, Saad",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-03T21:16:44",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I have my interview tomorrow around 8pm",
    "answer": "Can do evening today",
    "timestamp": "2025-11-03T10:18:36",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can we speak today ?",
    "answer": "Hey yea let me call you in 50 minutes",
    "timestamp": "2025-12-03T16:52:08",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://www.linkedin.com/in/georgia-green-aa676a150?utm_source=share&utm_campaign=share_via&utm_content=profile&utm_medium=android_app",
    "answer": "https://www.london.edu/masters-degrees/activities-clubs-and-groups",
    "timestamp": "2025-12-03T17:40:38",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay cool",
    "answer": "https://www.london.edu/masters-degrees/executive-mba/programme-content/core-courses",
    "timestamp": "2025-12-03T18:21:42",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "üëçüëç ‚Äé[20/03/2025, 1:51:03‚ÄØPM] Saad EMBA: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "answer": "WOW",
    "timestamp": "18/03/2025, 11:46:18‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Should I check with them or wait",
    "answer": "wait [Image]",
    "timestamp": "20/03/2025, 1:52:36‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Saad Salman MBA",
    "student_phone": "+7620206922",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Asslam o alikum",
    "answer": "WAS",
    "timestamp": "16/12/2024, 8:44:29‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéThis message was deleted.",
    "answer": "If you can send me O and AS results pls",
    "timestamp": "16/12/2024, 8:47:21‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "yes sharing in a bit",
    "answer": "Thank you",
    "timestamp": "16/12/2024, 8:48:40‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "ok",
    "answer": "also how is your schedule if we wanna meet tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "16/12/2024, 9:44:24‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "i have a test tomorrow 9-11 afterwards i‚Äôm free",
    "answer": "ok we will coordinate a time with you shortly [Image]",
    "timestamp": "16/12/2024, 9:46:33‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "common app username sireenumer@gmail.com password jykwoj-votfAk-0guqvu",
    "answer": "Thanks",
    "timestamp": "16/12/2024, 11:24:41‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay",
    "answer": "Also if you can share your year 1 alpha transcripts for review",
    "timestamp": "16/12/2024, 11:44:12‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can she come at 3pm?",
    "answer": "no issues",
    "timestamp": "17/12/2024, 12:34:03‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thank you",
    "answer": "https://imtiaz.com.pk/corporate-social-responsibility-initiatives/",
    "timestamp": "17/12/2024, 12:35:21‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "i‚Äôm free after 12. Is 1pm suitable?",
    "answer": "Come by 2",
    "timestamp": "17/12/2024, 8:34:05‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéYou added sheza adnan Lyceum",
    "answer": "Hey Sheza",
    "timestamp": "18/12/2024, 12:32:16‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "üëçüèº",
    "answer": "Hi Sireen what time can you come tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "18/12/2024, 12:42:06‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "College counsellor has refused to do her work when Sireen asked for predicted scores",
    "answer": "Why would they do that",
    "timestamp": "19/12/2024, 1:18:26‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "She just came from college",
    "answer": "Ok sure if they cause issues my suggestion is you please visit the school",
    "timestamp": "19/12/2024, 1:23:46‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "She will reach by 3 Sorry for that",
    "answer": "no issues",
    "timestamp": "19/12/2024, 2:09:52‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéSadaf Khan added Anicca Usmani",
    "answer": "Hey Anicca on Monday and Tuesday 11-1 is fine",
    "timestamp": "19/12/2024, 5:40:01‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôll come around 3:30 today",
    "answer": "That‚Äôs fine",
    "timestamp": "20/12/2024, 2:13:47‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Monday and Tuesday I can do 1:15 onwards Wednesday I‚Äôll have to skip Thursday I can do 1:15 onwards Friday I can do 3:30 onwards",
    "answer": "Hira i will confirm exact time with you",
    "timestamp": "21/12/2024, 3:57:15‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I can come btw 2 and 5",
    "answer": "Ok I will sort this out tonight",
    "timestamp": "21/12/2024, 6:41:37‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "sat score 1260",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "22/12/2024, 5:50:38‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "ok",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Anicca Usmani‚Å© tomorrow your meeting with Sireen is from 11-1",
    "timestamp": "22/12/2024, 5:55:01‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok üëç",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Sireen Umer‚Å© post your meeting with Anicca would you need a break before your meeting with Hira",
    "timestamp": "22/12/2024, 6:38:46‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "yes",
    "answer": "So @‚Å®Sireen Umer‚Å© can we do the meeting with Hira at 2:45?",
    "timestamp": "22/12/2024, 6:55:25‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "ok",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Hira Zubair Fellow‚Å© ?",
    "timestamp": "22/12/2024, 7:23:40‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will be there",
    "answer": "For tomorrow @‚Å®Anicca Usmani‚Å© 11-1 Hira 2:45 onwards",
    "timestamp": "22/12/2024, 7:30:31‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Done",
    "answer": "Hi this meeting was at 11!",
    "timestamp": "22/12/2024, 8:07:52‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I told Sireen 11:45 will be there in 10 mins",
    "answer": "Ok sure",
    "timestamp": "23/12/2024, 11:26:41‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "our meeting has finished i‚Äôll be back at 2:45",
    "answer": "Ok sure you wanna step out and come back ?",
    "timestamp": "23/12/2024, 12:45:11‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "yes",
    "answer": "üëç",
    "timestamp": "23/12/2024, 12:45:57‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "And I can do by 3:15 tomorrow?",
    "answer": "Sireen confirm pls",
    "timestamp": "23/12/2024, 5:36:29‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there a break in between? Asking because we don't live nearby",
    "answer": "for tomorrow yes",
    "timestamp": "23/12/2024, 6:28:41‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Need to know confirmed majors for these also, and if these are added to the common app University of Rochester Fordham Bard University of Maryland",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Sireen Umer‚Å© can you check which ones have accounting from above",
    "timestamp": "24/12/2024, 7:01:31‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "For these ones. Have you added them on your common app?",
    "answer": "These are already submitted",
    "timestamp": "24/12/2024, 7:56:51‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "ASA Sireen. What time are you coming tomorrow? Do you have a meeting with anyone? Wanted to schedule mine that‚Äôs why",
    "answer": "Hira pls have yours",
    "timestamp": "25/12/2024, 11:00:29‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay",
    "answer": "Fill them out and I‚Äôll review later today",
    "timestamp": "26/12/2024, 4:33:42‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay",
    "answer": "Hey Sireen",
    "timestamp": "26/12/2024, 5:31:03‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay",
    "answer": "also im replacing George Washington with Bentley",
    "timestamp": "27/12/2024, 4:04:40‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "yes",
    "answer": "cool",
    "timestamp": "27/12/2024, 4:06:00‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "ok I‚Äôll come",
    "answer": "Sireen can you pls submit: 1. Bard 2. Case Western",
    "timestamp": "27/12/2024, 8:06:00‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "done",
    "answer": "Sireen, have you plugged in essays for Rochester and Fordham based on the supplemental sheet sadaf sent?",
    "timestamp": "28/12/2024, 1:54:38‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I have",
    "answer": "Ok both good to submit",
    "timestamp": "28/12/2024, 3:07:04‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "yes",
    "answer": "Ok great",
    "timestamp": "28/12/2024, 6:20:57‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay",
    "answer": "Hey Sireen",
    "timestamp": "30/12/2024, 1:19:31‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "680 math 580 eng",
    "answer": "ok pls add it in the michigan SAT question",
    "timestamp": "30/12/2024, 5:14:04‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "should I start filling out the self reports for the applications submitted",
    "answer": "which ones have asked",
    "timestamp": "30/12/2024, 6:20:28‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "ok",
    "answer": "Sireen Bryn Mawr needs to be done today",
    "timestamp": "31/12/2024, 11:59:31‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Sireen Umer‚Å© @‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© have shared the Bryn Mawr supplement",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Sireen Umer‚Å© please can you add it in the app",
    "timestamp": "2025-01-01T14:41:23",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "should I submit",
    "answer": "Can you share pdf here first",
    "timestamp": "2025-01-01T15:20:08",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "done",
    "answer": "Cool",
    "timestamp": "2025-01-01T17:23:50",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "You can click on request for waiver with o level English",
    "answer": "Also my suggestion is to give IELTS UKVI Academic",
    "timestamp": "2025-02-01T20:22:02",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay [Image]",
    "answer": "This version of ielts",
    "timestamp": "2025-02-01T21:02:22",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "ok i‚Äôll look into it",
    "answer": "Asa Sireen sent Holoyoke and BU",
    "timestamp": "2025-02-01T21:29:08",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "ok",
    "answer": "Sireen I checked Holoyke",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-01T12:39:36",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "ok submitting it",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© her UIUC is pending",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-01T12:58:12",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôve completed the questions",
    "answer": "Pls submit",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-01T13:10:51",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi @‚Å®Hira Zubair Fellow‚Å© we need to do the university of Michigan supplements for Sireen. Please coordinate with her on this",
    "answer": "lets do in office soon so I can also fill the campus related stuff for michigan",
    "timestamp": "2025-07-01T17:14:45",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "uiuc won‚Äôt let me submit",
    "answer": "ok take it out",
    "timestamp": "2025-07-01T17:42:16",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Sireen Umer‚Å© we need to do this. Please add to common app and share the short questions. There are 5 I believe 650 characters each. Please share them today",
    "answer": "also Sireen pls submit Bates",
    "timestamp": "13/01/2025, 1:04:01‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôve shared my Ielts results with 5 universities but it won‚Äôt let me add any more.",
    "answer": "That‚Äôs ok",
    "timestamp": "22/01/2025, 12:18:52‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "ok",
    "answer": "Asa Sireen",
    "timestamp": "22/01/2025, 3:32:12‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Time?",
    "answer": "Around 1:30ish",
    "timestamp": "24/01/2025, 6:28:43‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "i‚Äôll reach around 2",
    "answer": "Ok [Image] [Image]",
    "timestamp": "25/01/2025, 1:34:48‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "ok ‚Äé[28/01/2025, 10:09:16‚ÄØPM] Sireen Umer: Common app pdf.pdf ‚Ä¢ ‚Äé16 pages ‚Äédocument omitted",
    "answer": "looks ok [Image]",
    "timestamp": "28/01/2025, 9:31:51‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I got an offer from qmul",
    "answer": "üëçüëç",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-02T22:45:12",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Nice! Congratulations [Image]",
    "answer": "It‚Äôs ok [Image]",
    "timestamp": "2025-04-02T23:02:05",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéThis message was deleted. [Image]",
    "answer": "Let‚Äôs discuss on call tomorrow first",
    "timestamp": "17/02/2025, 8:16:39‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I got into UMass Amherst",
    "answer": "call m",
    "timestamp": "22/02/2025, 12:43:38‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "accepted- fordham, rochester, case western and clark. bentley rejected",
    "answer": "Ok I",
    "timestamp": "17/03/2025, 7:55:05‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "bu bates bryn mawr lafayette penn state bard umd mount holyoke umich",
    "answer": "lafayette?",
    "timestamp": "17/03/2025, 9:00:39‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "accepted",
    "answer": "Amazing Yaar",
    "timestamp": "19/03/2025, 3:35:20‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "also penn state",
    "answer": "BU?",
    "timestamp": "20/03/2025, 9:27:06‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "for the january semester ‚Äé<This message was edited>",
    "answer": "‚ù§Ô∏è",
    "timestamp": "23/03/2025, 1:11:30‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚Äé‚Äésheza adnan Lyceum changed their phone number to a new number. ‚ÄéTap to message or add the new number.",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Hira Zubair Fellow‚Å© we need her PS for Aud app",
    "timestamp": "18/06/2025, 2:22:40‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "yea okay",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© we need to help her complete the US visa form",
    "timestamp": "16/07/2025, 1:42:57‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéYou removed Anicca Usmani",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Omer Imtiaz‚Å© will try getting the appointment quicker post visa app submission",
    "timestamp": "28/07/2025, 5:59:11‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "will it be eligible for Manchester?",
    "answer": "What was Manchester offer",
    "timestamp": "2025-12-08T13:25:18",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 As 1 B",
    "answer": "I‚Äôm hoping it should convert iA",
    "timestamp": "2025-12-08T13:27:29",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "that‚Äôs durham triple A for manchester",
    "answer": "Ok so let UCAS get updated on the 14th",
    "timestamp": "2025-12-08T14:53:25",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "yea [Image]",
    "answer": "Ok so you wanna keep this or look at another one",
    "timestamp": "2025-12-08T14:55:17",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "i‚Äôm looking into this change",
    "answer": "yes I think we can probably get some good stuff in warwick",
    "timestamp": "14/08/2025, 4:20:21‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôm thinking of accepting manchester‚Äôs offer",
    "answer": "Ok let‚Äôs speak in a bit",
    "timestamp": "15/08/2025, 12:27:12‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sireen Omer",
    "student_phone": "+6152434882",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéMessages and calls are end-to-end encrypted. Only people in this chat can read, listen to, or share them.",
    "answer": "Hey Sophya can you please put your existing Ps here ‚Äé[17/12/2024, 4:48:58‚ÄØPM] sophya mashkoor: Pol Phil PS.docx ‚Äédocument omitted",
    "timestamp": "17/12/2024, 4:39:12‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sophya Mashkoor",
    "student_phone": "+2644548198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "No worries at all, looking forward to it!",
    "answer": "@‚Å®sophya mashkoor‚Å© can you pls put the links of all the programs here",
    "timestamp": "20/12/2024, 12:15:20‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Sophya Mashkoor",
    "student_phone": "+2644548198",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéHamda Khan Dignosco added Fatima Hassan Kgs Parent 2023",
    "answer": "Hamda pls can you send the extra curricular form to Ali",
    "timestamp": "2022-11-01T10:41:39",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "InshaAllah",
    "answer": "Hamda whenever the form is ready pls let me know",
    "timestamp": "14/01/2022, 12:28:01‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Salam Please confirm if we are on for 2:45 pm Tom?",
    "answer": "ASA, please can we shift it to Wednesday same time ?",
    "timestamp": "17/01/2022, 3:54:31‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Let me confirm in a bit...I‚Äôve just messaged his Urdu teacher",
    "answer": "Sure",
    "timestamp": "17/01/2022, 4:05:33‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Wednesday will work for us Thank you Same time? 2:45?",
    "answer": "Great",
    "timestamp": "17/01/2022, 5:04:50‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Salam IA me and Ali will reach today by 2:45 pm",
    "answer": "Sure",
    "timestamp": "19/01/2022, 1:10:30‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I will drop it in physically also by 3 today",
    "answer": "Hey Ali can we meet on Friday",
    "timestamp": "21/01/2022, 10:50:30‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes does 2 pm on friday work for you?",
    "answer": "ill just revert on the time in the morning",
    "timestamp": "24/01/2022, 3:34:46‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I have a tution from 3-4 so that would not be possible",
    "answer": "Ok does Thursday at 3ish work ?",
    "timestamp": "25/01/2022, 9:34:11‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Would thursday at 4:15 work",
    "answer": "yes",
    "timestamp": "25/01/2022, 1:46:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéThis message was deleted.",
    "answer": "Lemme know if same time is fine ?",
    "timestamp": "30/01/2022, 12:53:50‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can we do it a bit later on thursday",
    "answer": "Let me reconfirm else we can do another day",
    "timestamp": "2022-01-02T08:44:50",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you please come in for the meeting on Thursday at 3:00 PM?",
    "answer": "I think he wants it later",
    "timestamp": "2022-01-02T15:27:43",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéThis message was deleted.",
    "answer": "Hey Ali",
    "timestamp": "2022-02-02T16:22:31",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mr. Rizwan Will 3:30 work as that‚Äôs the time he has in between his tuitions.",
    "answer": "Yes that is ok",
    "timestamp": "2022-10-02T16:22:52",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hello Is Ali on for today at 3:30?",
    "answer": "Yes that‚Äôs fine",
    "timestamp": "14/02/2022, 2:38:26‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will there be a meeting today?",
    "answer": "ASA meeting will be in the coming week",
    "timestamp": "24/02/2022, 2:20:07‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "üëç",
    "answer": "Hey Ali let‚Äôs meet on Thursday ?",
    "timestamp": "24/02/2022, 2:59:46‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Perfect what time on thursday?",
    "answer": "3?",
    "timestamp": "2022-01-03T17:20:55",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hey Ali! This is to remind you that your meeting is confirmed for today at 3 PM.",
    "answer": "Hey Ali Wednesday 3pm works ?",
    "timestamp": "2022-03-03T13:38:39",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "My mocks end on thursday so would it be possible to meet then?",
    "answer": "yes that could work too. @923333575290 can you do this so he can meet Reham after?",
    "timestamp": "13/03/2022, 6:11:11‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok will coordinate",
    "answer": "hey sadaf let Ali know if this is moving to next week",
    "timestamp": "14/03/2022, 3:02:40‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes we can meet on Tuesday next week",
    "answer": "Ali meeting will be for Tuesday thenx",
    "timestamp": "16/03/2022, 2:34:54‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "üëç",
    "answer": "Hey Ali lets meet on thursday?",
    "timestamp": "22/03/2022, 12:05:14‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yea that works",
    "answer": "Hey Ali you didn‚Äôt confirm earlier so I scheduled something else",
    "timestamp": "30/03/2022, 10:16:17‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Alright",
    "answer": "Hello Ali does tomorrow work",
    "timestamp": "30/03/2022, 10:20:53‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes that works",
    "answer": "Great",
    "timestamp": "2022-05-04T22:10:54",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéHamda Khan Dignosco left",
    "answer": "hey Ali free to meet on monday?",
    "timestamp": "2022-09-04T12:43:03",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Salam Rizwan Sb Sorry for the late reply but he has cies from Wednesday so Monday may not be possible",
    "answer": "Ok sure we can meet towards the time they finish",
    "timestamp": "21/04/2022, 12:10:26‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sure‚Ä¶will ask Ali to do so Thank you",
    "answer": "Hi Ali",
    "timestamp": "21/04/2022, 12:18:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "How about friday?",
    "answer": "ok sure",
    "timestamp": "25/05/2022, 11:29:37‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes thats perfect",
    "answer": "cool",
    "timestamp": "25/05/2022, 2:03:30‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Salam Rizwan Sb Ali is running a little late‚Ä¶he‚Äôll be with you by 10:30 am",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "27/05/2022, 9:49:13‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéAnab Ahmed left",
    "answer": "Hey Ali let me know when you‚Äôre back in town",
    "timestamp": "15/06/2022, 1:02:54‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "would it be possible to meet anytime next week?",
    "answer": "Hey Ali I‚Äôm outta town",
    "timestamp": "29/06/2022, 2:05:56‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Salam Rizwan Sb. Hope you are doing well. I wanted to meeting you either this week or the coming week. If you could please set up a time for the same. Thank you",
    "answer": "Asa",
    "timestamp": "14/07/2022, 11:19:35‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I would also like to meet you after the 21st",
    "answer": "Yes iA sure",
    "timestamp": "14/07/2022, 12:41:01‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thank you",
    "answer": "Hi Ali lets meet on saturday or monday",
    "timestamp": "14/07/2022, 12:42:39‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "monday would be preferred if thats alright",
    "answer": "Hey Ali didn‚Äôt hear from you so have already other meetings on Monday",
    "timestamp": "22/07/2022, 7:13:24‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Wednesday would be fine Mr. Rizwan for Ali Please let him know the time Thank you",
    "answer": "I‚Äôll confirm time in the morning",
    "timestamp": "22/07/2022, 7:31:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Salam Rizwan Sb. Hope you are doing well. I actually wanted to meet you independently of Ali so if you could please give me a time for tomorrow, I‚Äôd be much obliged.",
    "answer": "ASA, we can meet at 2:30 tomorrow. as off now we have not been able to open our office as Bukhari is not accessible",
    "timestamp": "26/07/2022, 1:22:26‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I see‚Ä¶no issues, I can talk to you on the phone also, so shall I call at 2:30 pm tom?",
    "answer": "you can call at 2:30 today",
    "timestamp": "26/07/2022, 1:25:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay sure [Image]",
    "answer": "Hey Ali did you speak to him",
    "timestamp": "26/07/2022, 1:26:35‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "will call him",
    "answer": "Hey Ali has the internship started",
    "timestamp": "2022-03-08T19:31:43",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes",
    "answer": "hey Ali how is the internship coming along",
    "timestamp": "2022-10-08T12:52:03",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéYou added Saad Ahmed",
    "answer": "Great job Ali",
    "timestamp": "18/08/2022, 11:36:00‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Lets meet on Wednesday",
    "answer": "üëç",
    "timestamp": "27/08/2022, 1:43:09‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "hey can we schedule a meeting for friday",
    "answer": "Hey Ali, can but will be next week",
    "timestamp": "2022-01-09T17:09:43",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "ok perfect",
    "answer": "Hey you didn‚Äôt come and I have to leave now for some work outta office",
    "timestamp": "2022-01-09T17:13:45",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "i apologise school just started this week, orientations are still going on and school is keeping us late these days, could we schedule a session sometime next week",
    "answer": "I will revert",
    "timestamp": "2022-06-09T17:17:20",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéSaad Ahmed left",
    "answer": "Let‚Äôs do Thursday",
    "timestamp": "2022-10-09T03:21:56",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Salam Hope everyone is keeping well. Just wanted to share the awards Ali received at the mini speech day they had at school today for the O Level results.",
    "answer": "Amazing [Image]",
    "timestamp": "23/09/2022, 1:19:04‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "i got 1410 in the SAT",
    "answer": "üëç",
    "timestamp": "14/10/2022, 4:52:35‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "what time would you suggest?",
    "answer": "Let‚Äôs do Monday",
    "timestamp": "19/10/2022, 8:42:46‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "üëç",
    "answer": "lets meet thursday?",
    "timestamp": "19/10/2022, 9:07:27‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Salam Rizwan Sb. Hope you are keeping well. Could I kindly request you to have the meeting tom either at 3:30 pm or any time after that. Thank you",
    "answer": "WAS we can do tomorrow at 3:30",
    "timestamp": "26/10/2022, 5:14:13‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay Thank you",
    "answer": "Let‚Äôs meet next week?",
    "timestamp": "26/10/2022, 5:19:01‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "are you free to meet anytime this week?",
    "answer": "Hey yes let‚Äôs meet tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "21/11/2022, 5:53:17‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923018379777 : yes of course Please let us know the time Thank you",
    "answer": "Let‚Äôs do 2:45",
    "timestamp": "24/11/2022, 7:39:30‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Done IA",
    "answer": ":)",
    "timestamp": "24/11/2022, 7:40:00‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "The link to the page: Let‚Äôs share books",
    "answer": "üëç [Image] [Image] [Image] [Image] [Image] [Image] [Image] ‚Äé[27/04/2023, 5:19:51‚ÄØPM] Fatima Hassan Kgs Parent 2023: ‚Äévideo omitted",
    "timestamp": "25/11/2022, 3:40:00‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923008485884 are you coming in tomorrow? Can you come at 4",
    "answer": "Ali ?",
    "timestamp": "18/05/2023, 5:41:17‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "hey guys did the digital SAT without any practice beforehand got 1460",
    "answer": "Ok cool",
    "timestamp": "14/07/2023, 5:11:47‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "My opinion is to go for crash course only in the end for practise.",
    "answer": "Agreed",
    "timestamp": "14/07/2023, 7:34:52‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923018379777 @923333575290 : can you recommend a place that does do a crash course?",
    "answer": "I know of edge and Anees hussain",
    "timestamp": "14/07/2023, 9:34:12‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Found the books",
    "answer": "@923008485884 what you up to\"?",
    "timestamp": "2023-03-08T15:05:11",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Got all A‚Äôs in my AS result",
    "answer": "MA",
    "timestamp": "2023-10-08T10:27:31",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok 4:15 is fine [Image] [Image]",
    "answer": "Why so late tho",
    "timestamp": "2023-10-08T20:32:25",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "That‚Äôs KGS for you",
    "answer": "lol",
    "timestamp": "15/08/2023, 10:48:16‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "hey have a couple of long important counselling forms from school that need to be filled out before the 25th, would you guys be able to assist me in this?",
    "answer": "yup",
    "timestamp": "15/08/2023, 6:09:47‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Salam Me and my husband would like to meet you and Sadaf. Will Tom 5 pm work for you? Please do inform Thank you",
    "answer": "Let sadaf just revert",
    "timestamp": "23/08/2023, 9:48:38‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sure",
    "answer": "Does anytime today work though ?",
    "timestamp": "23/08/2023, 9:57:08‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Noman is saying after 6 if possible today",
    "answer": "Can we please do like 5:20ish today",
    "timestamp": "23/08/2023, 9:58:47‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "School transcript and caie both",
    "answer": "Have you written the personal statement ?",
    "timestamp": "2023-07-09T18:56:40",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "He is working on it. We have discussed it",
    "answer": "Ok it‚Äôs due tomorrow ?",
    "timestamp": "2023-07-09T19:09:13",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes",
    "answer": "Ali if you have drafted a response pls share here",
    "timestamp": "2023-07-09T19:09:50",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "yea I‚Äôm just working on it once it‚Äôs done I‚Äôll send here",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "2023-07-09T19:26:03",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok also ali you need to send across the second UC essay as well",
    "answer": "also SAT result update?",
    "timestamp": "2023-08-09T15:17:43",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "As discussed we want to draft this separately. Please do so over the weekend [Image]",
    "answer": "cool",
    "timestamp": "2023-08-09T15:53:15",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Couldn‚Äôt break 1500 guys",
    "answer": "It‚Äôs ok let‚Äôs just go with this",
    "timestamp": "2023-08-09T16:01:36",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "guys for the scholarship major I‚Äôm going with life sciences but that‚Äôs the admissions category and there are specific programs within this category whether they be specialists, majors, minors. U get to choose these programs once u get into the uni so I do specify which program I want to go in as well on the scholarship form or do I just go with the greater admission category",
    "answer": "Greater admission category is cool",
    "timestamp": "2023-08-09T18:46:07",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "It asks for division and major so it‚Äôs fine right",
    "answer": "yea so division is dept and major is what you wanna pursue",
    "timestamp": "2023-08-09T18:49:16",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "so division would be life sciences in this case and major I can add the specific program I want to study",
    "answer": "yea [Image] [Image]",
    "timestamp": "2023-08-09T18:53:59",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "The deadline is 11:59 pm tonight",
    "answer": "Why can‚Äôt you ask them to give you till morning",
    "timestamp": "2023-08-09T20:31:10",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also please send the exact question on the form [Image]",
    "answer": "Ali we will send edited version",
    "timestamp": "2023-08-09T20:37:27",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "alright ive added this as my personal statement to the form is there anything else u guys want to see about the form or can i submit it",
    "answer": "Share your common app login details",
    "timestamp": "2023-08-09T22:43:13",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "haven‚Äôt logged in yet",
    "answer": "Have you made the account",
    "timestamp": "14/09/2023, 6:04:24‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "have made the common app account",
    "answer": "Pls share login details",
    "timestamp": "15/09/2023, 8:37:36‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes that will be possible üëç",
    "answer": "Ali",
    "timestamp": "15/09/2023, 5:02:32‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "guys when is the deadline to submit my common app",
    "answer": "Deadline is nov 1",
    "timestamp": "17/10/2023, 8:12:53‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "password is ‚ÄòfRBNYG0TFGF@‚Äò",
    "answer": "I‚Äôm hoping you have brainstormed on the questions we were discussing",
    "timestamp": "17/10/2023, 8:15:46‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will we be filling out the CSS form",
    "answer": "No",
    "timestamp": "18/10/2023, 12:29:04‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "so r we applying for financial aid",
    "answer": "No",
    "timestamp": "18/10/2023, 12:30:01‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "also northwestern doesnt require the common apppersonal essay right",
    "answer": "Ali we discussed this strategy get the other day",
    "timestamp": "18/10/2023, 3:05:26‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "also guys someone who‚Äôs doing NU their father also went to northwestern",
    "answer": "Who",
    "timestamp": "20/10/2023, 9:22:56‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "the guy who i mentioned yesterday zaid Sami",
    "answer": "Hey Ali let‚Äôs do the changes as discussed please [Image]",
    "timestamp": "20/10/2023, 9:37:23‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Dear Customer, Your HBL CreditCard (ending with 3128) has been charged at OUACP for CAD-869.50 on 25/Oct/2023.",
    "answer": "üëç",
    "timestamp": "26/10/2023, 9:09:51‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Payment made to OUACP (for the record)",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "26/10/2023, 9:10:30‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "guys in the video should I just say ‚ÄòThe Polymer and Chemical Head of Engineering‚Äô or should I say ‚ÄòDr Shakeel The Polymer and Chemical Head of Engineering‚Äô",
    "answer": "The latter",
    "timestamp": "28/10/2023, 12:59:55‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Salam all @923018379777 : could you please have a look at this video and let us know if this will work? Thanks",
    "answer": "Asa will review it in a few hours",
    "timestamp": "29/10/2023, 4:07:35‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sure",
    "answer": "So overall video is great, I feel the ending when ali is speaking can improve slightly",
    "timestamp": "29/10/2023, 4:26:55‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yea sure",
    "answer": "Also you‚Äôll need to upload this on Vimeo so a link can be put on the app",
    "timestamp": "29/10/2023, 5:10:17‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "üëç",
    "answer": "I‚Äôm calling",
    "timestamp": "29/10/2023, 5:10:57‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "what time should I come in today?",
    "answer": "@923333575290",
    "timestamp": "30/10/2023, 1:44:22‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "üëç",
    "answer": "My project  has now culminated into an organisation known as ‚ÄòR4Recycling‚Äô. We are currently in the experimental phase with the reactor, testing out different catalysts and different conditions of temperature and pressure to see which give the most efficient yield of ‚ÄòPoly-fuel‚Äô.  We are in the process to raise funds  that can help us scale up this project and possibly  make this Poly-fuel available for a larger audience to use. the reactor will be up and running and we will begin manufacturing more models to help us further accelerate the project, and that gives me a lot of hope for the future.",
    "timestamp": "30/10/2023, 2:45:42‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Rest looks good",
    "answer": "üëç [Image]",
    "timestamp": "30/10/2023, 8:18:26‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "do I need to come in today",
    "answer": "No",
    "timestamp": "2023-03-11T12:34:18",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "guys how do invite my counsellor on my UC application",
    "answer": "So initially you don‚Äôt",
    "timestamp": "2023-06-11T00:09:22",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Guys I don‚Äôt need to invite my counsellor again to my common app right for other universities cus I‚Äôve already invited her for the ED",
    "answer": "No",
    "timestamp": "2023-08-11T13:26:02",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "also r there other websites where I need to invite her besides UC cus deadline for that is today",
    "answer": "But they can add updates themselves",
    "timestamp": "2023-08-11T13:26:49",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok but for US universities",
    "answer": "Which other unis",
    "timestamp": "2023-08-11T13:28:54",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok üëç",
    "answer": "Hey",
    "timestamp": "2023-12-11T20:22:34",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Have finished my activities on the UC application",
    "answer": "Share login",
    "timestamp": "21/11/2023, 10:05:51‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Password is fRBNYG0TFGF@",
    "answer": "Ali what's your SAT score",
    "timestamp": "22/11/2023, 6:54:38‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "A* in math and biology A in physics and chemistry",
    "answer": "I have made all changes in the activities etc . Sadaf you need to review once he puts up the essays and the video links need to be added. @923008485884 in the additional info of the academics I also added your sat score, just double check that it‚Äôs correct",
    "timestamp": "22/11/2023, 10:39:26‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Guys could I come tomorrow at 4 I have an extra physics class immediately after school",
    "answer": "Let sadaf review the app",
    "timestamp": "22/11/2023, 10:23:57‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Guys is ED binding globally",
    "answer": "Only US",
    "timestamp": "23/11/2023, 12:24:42‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "^",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "25/11/2023, 1:36:47‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "perfect üëç",
    "answer": "Ali",
    "timestamp": "25/11/2023, 2:45:55‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "guys I also need assistance in filling out certain Canadian university portals so could I meet with zannirah for that",
    "answer": "Set a zoom time with her as she‚Äôs travelling",
    "timestamp": "28/11/2023, 9:35:58‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Would 4 work",
    "answer": "3:30",
    "timestamp": "28/11/2023, 2:36:52‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "UC submitted",
    "timestamp": "28/11/2023, 2:40:42‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Wasn‚Äôt deadline for BU scholarship today",
    "answer": "yea I have taken feedback, it doesn't really work out now unless school etc are nominating",
    "timestamp": "2023-01-12T15:54:41",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "ok I don‚Äôt think our school is nominating anyone for BU",
    "answer": "yea well submit it anyways",
    "timestamp": "2023-01-12T16:05:15",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "guys do u need me to come in tomorrow to submit the UofT application",
    "answer": "Do it from home",
    "timestamp": "14/12/2023, 7:29:17‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok but they‚Äôre asking for a mid-term transcript and a transcript with predicted results for A Levels which I don‚Äôt have, shld I email the school for these documents",
    "answer": "Why don‚Äôt you have predicted grades ?",
    "timestamp": "14/12/2023, 7:49:33‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "this is the transcript we have but it doesnt mention our predicted grades the school just told us those",
    "answer": "Please ask school",
    "timestamp": "14/12/2023, 8:04:34‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923018379777 : this document does have the predicted grades on the left side and the CIE grades on the right side",
    "answer": "This is good to submit however if the school can write a note on this document stating that his midterm results will come on whichever date they are suppose to it will address the midterm result problem as well",
    "timestamp": "14/12/2023, 8:27:41‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923018379777 please guide",
    "answer": "choose computer and info technology ‚Äé[15/12/2023, 3:05:32‚ÄØPM] Syed Ali Hasan Kgs 2024: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "timestamp": "15/12/2023, 2:58:17‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "shld i give my school teacher's that also wrote my recommendation letter for common app",
    "answer": "@923333575290 ?",
    "timestamp": "15/12/2023, 3:39:15‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "shld i email my school teacher informing her of this or is that not necessary",
    "answer": "I‚Äôm sure you‚Äôll have to",
    "timestamp": "15/12/2023, 3:43:13‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes will do üëç [Image] [Image]",
    "answer": "Ok still not bad",
    "timestamp": "15/12/2023, 3:58:30‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "so I‚Äôm on the waitlist basically?",
    "answer": "discuss with me on monday",
    "timestamp": "16/12/2023, 11:08:53‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi @923018379777 @923333575290 We received the above üëÜ from Northeastern University. Can you please guide as what needs to be done in this regard. Thanks",
    "answer": "He must have received a form which needs to be completed and has to be verified by your bank stating that there‚Äôs atleast one year worth of tution and living expenses",
    "timestamp": "28/12/2023, 11:18:50‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay will check with Ali",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "28/12/2023, 11:32:59‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok ‚Äé[03/01/2024, 12:52:44‚ÄØPM] Syed Ali Hasan Kgs 2024: BROWN APPLICATION.pdf ‚Ä¢ ‚Äé14 pages ‚Äédocument omitted",
    "answer": "share the Brown writing supplemental PDF also",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-01T12:36:42",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "cant review that until common app is submitted",
    "answer": "how is that possible",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-01T12:54:20",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "password is 'fRBNYG0TFGF@'",
    "answer": "the chess essay needs some fixing",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-01T12:55:50",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923008485884 please confirm that you will be doing UK and if so what program",
    "answer": "ye revised essay is good",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-01T18:07:08",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Wait has the format of writing supplement been checked @923018379777",
    "answer": "Share pdf ‚Äé[03/01/2024, 10:04:25‚ÄØPM] Syed Ali Hasan Kgs 2024: BROWN WRITING SUPPLEMENT.pdf ‚Ä¢ ‚Äé3 pages ‚Äédocument omitted",
    "timestamp": "2024-03-01T21:15:28",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923333575290 we will not be doing UK",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "2024-05-01T20:52:57",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Guys my deadline for Claremont McKenna is tomorrow",
    "answer": "whats pending",
    "timestamp": "2024-09-01T10:53:30",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "for the courses and grades section of the common app do i need to fill anything out [Image]",
    "answer": ":/",
    "timestamp": "2024-11-01T00:21:11",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "how should I improve this?",
    "answer": "I explained to you yesterday Alo",
    "timestamp": "2024-11-01T19:26:29",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "?",
    "answer": "Call pls",
    "timestamp": "2024-12-01T13:44:03",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok will plug in ‚Äé[12/01/2024, 2:59:18‚ÄØPM] Syed Ali Hasan Kgs 2024: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "answer": "cool",
    "timestamp": "2024-12-01T14:56:41",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I submit this?",
    "answer": "Yea put it",
    "timestamp": "2024-12-01T20:27:48",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "guys for UBC the majors ive chosen are bachelor of science and bachelor of science in applied biology is that fine",
    "answer": "üëç",
    "timestamp": "13/01/2024, 5:56:50‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can I come in on Monday to submit this application",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "13/01/2024, 8:08:10‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923018379777 please review his UBC app so he can submit",
    "answer": "Share login and link",
    "timestamp": "14/01/2024, 8:24:59‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://signon.educationplannerbc.ca/signin?ReturnUrl=%2Fconnect%2Fauthorize%2Fcallback%3Fclient_id%3Dso%26redirect_uri%3Dhttps%253A%252F%252Fsignon.educationplannerbc.ca%252Foauth%252Fcallback%26response_type%3Dcode%26scope%3Dopenid%2520offline_access%2520epbc_identity%26code_challenge%3Di833Q6T9DPIRCd7VsRLfc9cvw-CsxRUAr9kNms6Za_I%26code_challenge_method%3DS256%26response_mode%3Dform_post%26nonce%3D638408460550748987.ZjAxNDUzYmYtZDEyNi00MmE2LTk2MGUtZjhmNmRjY2JjZDY4MWIzOTk0M2ItNzI0YS00NGEwLWE0MTEtNzg0MzUwNWFkY2Rl%26state%3DCfDJ8PS5O8S0x1xPvzxtr76WyZ3DZ0Dy69Idd0uQ_DtaA8jUe1jrVyipHl0Ri0Jojwqbun62YMA5E29ig32PUOz-_QHxFZ2CNrulzmpAmKoaSmrSIUYLRNrmKX1tVXl4ZjqVW8ufGHUY5USmlgQwIJ7g_E8eSF2UFe9Y3CYIqUWIt711wdd0YFTHd52PLGznRQhuXb5UhprewXVpJrLk7tPa-gl7iG1R1s6RwPXkelGqZPdBckMuPR10RR_QtTgpL2JO1P-O1XURg-mk1wRJdz3N_MlUhpSuGz_LfPCxlLK2-coeFAcpb7yrFZLQZCHdR41Cx7XJKQbcT36Aj8Q1agMWlSQ5G8uK-3V30oRM5nwOnTEon_zNWkt8bFqDMPlSrZbvECIl7l4_7S5TVSbjNzK2TBk%26x-client-SKU%3DID_NETSTANDARD2_0%26x-client-ver%3D6.16.0.0",
    "answer": "Is this O or zero",
    "timestamp": "14/01/2024, 9:21:09‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "USC app",
    "answer": "He can come and submit UBC at office",
    "timestamp": "14/01/2024, 10:19:20‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "what time shld I come in",
    "answer": "I‚Äôm here",
    "timestamp": "15/01/2024, 1:29:59‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ali is in school. He will be back by 2:30.",
    "answer": "ok come after",
    "timestamp": "15/01/2024, 1:49:56‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "guys I got a offer from McMaster",
    "answer": "Mubarak",
    "timestamp": "16/01/2024, 2:49:57‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "have also received an offer from western university now",
    "answer": "solid",
    "timestamp": "17/01/2024, 10:21:13‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "in school rn will share once I get out",
    "answer": "ok waiting",
    "timestamp": "17/01/2024, 10:22:25‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I am out at the moment‚Ä¶I can send you once home",
    "answer": "ok [Image]",
    "timestamp": "17/01/2024, 3:58:08‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "working on it [Image]",
    "answer": "üëçüëç",
    "timestamp": "18/01/2024, 8:47:16‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Have gotten an email for a UPENN interview on Friday. Any tips before I give it?",
    "answer": "Great",
    "timestamp": "23/01/2024, 3:27:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Salam Hope you all are well. @923018379777 @923333575290 : in the Letter of Acceptance from Western University, it states that no matter which uni you are applying for in Canada but you should start your Study Permit process from now. Can you please advise in this regard. Thanks",
    "answer": "It‚Äôs a student visa so he can‚Äôt till he finalises the choice",
    "timestamp": "25/01/2024, 11:08:53‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "guys how shld I prepare for the Penn interview",
    "answer": "Research on interviewer. Tell them why you wanna join Penn Program your interested in Clubs /socities Ask them which program they did. Degree studied. Work opportunities . What socities are good for internationals etc",
    "timestamp": "26/01/2024, 8:39:51‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "cant find much on interviewer it‚Äôs an alumni interview",
    "answer": "Linkden",
    "timestamp": "26/01/2024, 9:51:09‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok also do I need to make a resume to send to the interviewer",
    "answer": "If he hasn‚Äôt asked then I don‚Äôt think so",
    "timestamp": "26/01/2024, 10:21:25‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "also UPENN interview now been rescheduled",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "26/01/2024, 3:57:35‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "guys when do we plan on submitting an update to northwestern. it says this on the applicant portal, 'If you have new information you would like the admission committee to consider, please feel free to submit additional materials via the online Applicant Portal by the end of January. '",
    "answer": "come by 3:30ish tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "31/01/2024, 5:51:53‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "ok, this also requires a 1000 word essay so I‚Äôll send a draft for that which I will need you guys to review",
    "answer": "What does",
    "timestamp": "2024-08-02T21:02:18",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "western scholarship nomination form",
    "answer": "Ok kindly write a proper essay",
    "timestamp": "2024-08-02T21:06:46",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923353797821 would it be possible to meet anytime in the morning tomorrow",
    "answer": "no",
    "timestamp": "2024-11-02T12:35:31",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "got into UoFT",
    "answer": "Amazing",
    "timestamp": "23/02/2024, 10:37:07‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "got into UC Irvine",
    "answer": "Please mention all universities applied to region wise. Mention, accepted, rejected, waitlisted or decision pending: USA UK Canada Europe",
    "timestamp": "2024-11-03T22:55:21",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "USA: -UC Irvine: Acceptance -UC Davis: Acceptance -UC San Diego: Acceptance -UCLA: Waitlist -UC Berkeley: Pending -Northwestern: Waitlist -Northeastern: Waitlist -Swarthmore: Pending -Boston: Pending -Brown: Pending -CMU: Pending -Claremont McKenna: Pending -Colby: Pending -Cornell: Pending -Duke: Pending -UPENN: Pending -GeorgiaTech: Pending -Hamilton: Pending -Middlebury: Pending -Michigan: Pending -USC: Pending -Wesleyan: Pending Canada: -UofT: Acceptance -McGill: Acceptance -Western: Acceptance -McMaster: Acceptance -UBC: Pending -Waterloo: Pending -Ottawa: Pending ‚Äé<This message was edited>",
    "answer": "Middlebury",
    "timestamp": "16/03/2024, 1:07:27‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Waitlist",
    "answer": "Santa Barbara?",
    "timestamp": "16/03/2024, 7:12:11‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "didn‚Äôt apply there",
    "answer": "Has northwestern waitlisted you post the early decision also",
    "timestamp": "20/03/2024, 4:51:05‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Syed Ali Hasan",
    "student_phone": "+8452157259",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Salams, sorry not sure if the thumbs up gave a notification before, but I am ready for the meeting üôÇ ‚Äé<This message was edited>",
    "answer": "Just wait a bit",
    "timestamp": "26/08/2024, 4:33:05‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sure will do",
    "answer": "pls share UCAS login",
    "timestamp": "23/09/2024, 12:15:51‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay",
    "answer": "Hey Zara",
    "timestamp": "27/09/2024, 9:57:04‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "So thought to leave it blank, what should I put there?",
    "answer": "can be any internships etc",
    "timestamp": "27/09/2024, 11:01:36‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "They‚Äôve closed their ug.admissions email and now only use live chat [Image]",
    "answer": "So ask there",
    "timestamp": "2024-07-10T17:31:04",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I have- I like it but still worried about the acceptance rate",
    "answer": "Zara, the econ and politics doesn‚Äôt go with the theme of the essay",
    "timestamp": "2024-07-10T19:54:05",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I do think tho if I‚Äôm applying to 2 courses at LSE maybe keeping that as an option would be good as I wrote this ps mainly tailored towards Econ/IR?",
    "answer": "So that‚Äôs another thing",
    "timestamp": "2024-07-10T20:02:29",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "?",
    "answer": "having another uni would be better . We have again discussed this at length",
    "timestamp": "2024-07-10T20:08:36",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I thought initially doing two courses at LSE was proposed- just curious what changed so I understand better?",
    "answer": "They will assume you‚Äôre not focused",
    "timestamp": "2024-07-10T20:11:09",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "also last question- what abt politics and econ like makes it not fit with personal statement as much- is it that the course is very maths based/technical? ‚Äé<This message was edited>",
    "answer": "https://www.lse.ac.uk/study-at-lse/undergraduate/bsc-politics-and-economics#programme-content",
    "timestamp": "2024-07-10T20:19:31",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Salams, finished all the sections",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Zara Rizvi‚Å© doing a final review, so i see the piano grades in the qualifications",
    "timestamp": "2024-08-10T23:48:28",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there space where you are mentioning piano etc",
    "answer": "It‚Äôs in the qualification section",
    "timestamp": "2024-09-10T12:16:27",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "even the john locke",
    "answer": "i think whatever is in the PS",
    "timestamp": "2024-09-10T14:08:26",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "but let me know when you‚Äôve finished final check cause once i submit to centre and everything is approved not sure if I can change anything",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Zara Rizvi‚Å© good to submit",
    "timestamp": "2024-09-10T14:23:34",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I think my sister did too",
    "answer": "Zara have u submitted",
    "timestamp": "2024-10-10T00:45:31",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "hey @‚Å®Zara Rizvi‚Å© ur feedback on SAQ is ready pls revert back to me with changes latest by tomo!",
    "answer": "sat?",
    "timestamp": "17/10/2024, 8:28:54‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Zara Rizvi‚Å© any update on SAQ",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Zara Rizvi‚Å© ?",
    "timestamp": "19/10/2024, 12:07:08‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Msg me when done with school I‚Äôll call you and explain",
    "answer": "Hey any update from Cambridge",
    "timestamp": "13/11/2024, 3:00:52‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes plz",
    "answer": "We can do abhi in ten 15 min",
    "timestamp": "16/11/2024, 2:46:34‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes she's available in 5m.",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "16/11/2024, 3:33:08‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "salams, did u get the meeting link?",
    "answer": "yup",
    "timestamp": "16/11/2024, 4:26:35‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© salams do you have time to discuss the Main essay?",
    "answer": "also what is our super score for sat",
    "timestamp": "16/11/2024, 4:39:23‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Zara Rizvi‚Å© are you free tomorrow night time",
    "answer": "https://studentaid.gov/fsa-id/create-account/launch",
    "timestamp": "19/11/2024, 12:23:20‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "no idea, but my other friend who applied hasn‚Äôt heard back either",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "20/11/2024, 4:38:11‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Great üëç congratulations!!! Please share details here",
    "answer": "Great :]",
    "timestamp": "20/11/2024, 9:19:45‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "It‚Äôs good with politics and sociology but it‚Äôs very starting analysis worthy",
    "answer": "Zara did you fill in the UC app?",
    "timestamp": "23/11/2024, 10:30:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also @‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å© please coordinate a meeting with Zara‚Äôs parents at your convenience",
    "answer": "we can do that tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "25/11/2024, 4:06:10‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Rizwan k asking how's 12 your time?",
    "answer": "That‚Äôs fine",
    "timestamp": "25/11/2024, 7:21:40‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ill send Kamran's number. Plz cood with him directly Rizwan. Thanks [Image]",
    "answer": "‚ÄéYou deleted this message.",
    "timestamp": "25/11/2024, 11:26:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi Rizwan. Have you had a chance to look at Zaras UC activities? Plz can u give her feedback on it today. A quick call maybe?",
    "answer": "ill review tonight and give her feedback in the morning",
    "timestamp": "28/11/2024, 5:44:06‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is now a good time @‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å©?",
    "answer": "WAS out for prayers",
    "timestamp": "29/11/2024, 1:18:20‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "Join Zoom Meeting https://us04web.zoom.us/j/73618440159?pwd=yb9h23fmmdpLENanGmSYQgm5lbkcY8.1 Meeting ID:  736 1844 0159 Passcode: ShEg99",
    "timestamp": "29/11/2024, 2:00:57‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "as suggestions, just wanted to discuss that with you + the last line change which we said to alter",
    "answer": "The Outstanding Pearson Learner award is for a GCSE candidate who has gained the highest standard mark in the nationally or internationally.",
    "timestamp": "30/11/2024, 1:11:47‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I think i‚Äôll remove this sentence then as there are not many characters left",
    "answer": "we have  48 characters left",
    "timestamp": "30/11/2024, 1:25:24‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can i write it like this?",
    "answer": "Yup",
    "timestamp": "30/11/2024, 1:31:26‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I reformed one of my descriptions: I prepared research over several months on Mao's agricultural policies (Five Year Plans and Great Leap Forward) and their socio-economic impact. Recorded a 10-minute video that was broadcasted online and spoke about the impact of his Five Year Plans and the Great Famine, analyzing quotations from Wild Swains: Jung Halliday as a key source.",
    "answer": "fitting in fine?",
    "timestamp": "30/11/2024, 1:44:23‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "You also then need to review module guides especially Both POL1 and SOC 1",
    "answer": "Hey Zara",
    "timestamp": "2024-04-12T21:26:47",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Speaking to Rehab in a couple hours today",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "2024-07-12T20:33:19",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "She will be done at 1pm her time.",
    "answer": "üëç",
    "timestamp": "2024-08-12T12:42:01",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thanks Rizwan. Zara is looking fwd to itüí™üèª",
    "answer": "Hi Zara, This is our final list for you. Even though we had initially agreed on 5 odd schools, we have gone to take this up to 13. Brown is under process. UCs Pomona Rice Cornell Amherst Brown Wesleyan Williams Colby Middlebury Northeastern UIUC University of Michigan",
    "timestamp": "2024-09-12T09:32:59",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Wondering when that will be + how will be reduce the activities to only 10",
    "answer": "some are honors",
    "timestamp": "18/12/2024, 1:50:19‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Am I allowed to use AI to help with that or no?",
    "answer": "you're pretty good yourself",
    "timestamp": "18/12/2024, 1:55:26‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "yes",
    "answer": "Hey Zara",
    "timestamp": "18/12/2024, 3:43:23‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi Rizwan. She's in the plane at the moment. Will message in a couple of hoursüëçüèª",
    "answer": "sure",
    "timestamp": "19/12/2024, 12:09:05‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi @‚Å®Rizwan Javed‚Å©, will have activity list completed by today should I send screenshots? ‚Äé<This message was edited>",
    "answer": "when you do lemme know",
    "timestamp": "19/12/2024, 6:48:26‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Salam. Rizwan plz take out some time for us. Kamran needs to meet  asapüôè",
    "answer": "I will speak to him on a call at some point today",
    "timestamp": "23/12/2024, 1:58:06‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok bit can we do that now bcz then we will leave the house and there's functions. Kamran wants to send it off now plz",
    "answer": "I‚Äôll be free in 2 hours from now",
    "timestamp": "23/12/2024, 2:20:33‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Salams made tweaks to the supplements, added @‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© @‚Å®Rehab UK‚Å© in the comments",
    "answer": "also @‚Å®Zara Rizvi‚Å©",
    "timestamp": "23/12/2024, 8:39:17‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "was it okay?",
    "answer": "pls reshare common app pass pls",
    "timestamp": "25/12/2024, 8:19:40‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Gratitude@12345",
    "answer": "Zara ive reviewed but lets have a chat on this tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "25/12/2024, 10:04:01‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "okay",
    "answer": "can u also reorder them based on importance",
    "timestamp": "25/12/2024, 10:19:35‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "used the same order as UCs basically some activities were combined but arrangement was same",
    "answer": "in the Art one, overall looks good, but ur position isn't mentioned",
    "timestamp": "25/12/2024, 10:23:28‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "but since its only 10 activities maybe we can change order too based on description",
    "answer": "ok also what is word count for add info",
    "timestamp": "25/12/2024, 10:24:11‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "588 words",
    "answer": "Hey Zara",
    "timestamp": "25/12/2024, 10:28:19‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hello",
    "answer": "Hi Zara we can speak now",
    "timestamp": "26/12/2024, 1:33:52‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "zoom?",
    "answer": "Join Zoom Meeting https://us04web.zoom.us/j/73579367286?pwd=woNfmQgFfGGuSWZnb4O7yIvjnfg3J1.1 Meeting ID:  735 7936 7286 Passcode: K7Mn5V",
    "timestamp": "26/12/2024, 1:53:10‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "ok so submissions will happen by tomorrow?",
    "answer": "Plug everything in the common app",
    "timestamp": "29/12/2024, 8:16:43‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "all the schools are filled out",
    "answer": "Ok I‚Äôll review and give go ahead and you can submit",
    "timestamp": "29/12/2024, 9:00:43‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "We will also do a final review tonightüí™üèª ‚Äé<This message was edited>",
    "answer": "üëç",
    "timestamp": "29/12/2024, 9:09:52‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "Zara fixed?",
    "timestamp": "30/12/2024, 1:12:08‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Salams yes its done",
    "answer": "Will review later today",
    "timestamp": "30/12/2024, 6:27:09‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "any update?",
    "answer": "pls fix punctuation issues in activities.",
    "timestamp": "31/12/2024, 12:58:50‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "from before",
    "answer": "yea but formatting is not ok",
    "timestamp": "31/12/2024, 3:21:54‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Please let me know when I can submit",
    "answer": "Pls do",
    "timestamp": "29/01/2025, 10:09:17‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Salams, got an offer from Kings",
    "answer": "WAS mubarak",
    "timestamp": "13/02/2025, 11:21:55‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "üëç",
    "answer": "wow , such great news",
    "timestamp": "19/02/2025, 9:29:47‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thank you üôè",
    "answer": "Hello",
    "timestamp": "24/03/2025, 7:16:15‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zara Rizvi",
    "student_phone": "+5041290926",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéYou created group ‚ÄúZarain Asim Apps‚Äù",
    "answer": "Hey Zarain we will communicate ok this group",
    "timestamp": "27/10/2023, 12:47:51‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "any preference in which one i should read first?",
    "answer": "Irrational exuberance",
    "timestamp": "27/10/2023, 7:06:28‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "can we have a meeting tmrw with my dad?",
    "answer": "hey we‚Äôre off tomorrow Zarain",
    "timestamp": "28/10/2023, 9:30:08‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "day after tomorrow is alright then?",
    "answer": "Sure",
    "timestamp": "28/10/2023, 9:51:57‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "perfect, is 530 possible?",
    "answer": "Ok [Image]",
    "timestamp": "29/10/2023, 5:49:38‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "have 3 tests day after tmrw i need to study for",
    "answer": "Ok will coordinate a time",
    "timestamp": "2023-05-11T13:28:09",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "no problem",
    "answer": "Cool",
    "timestamp": "2023-06-11T17:08:01",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "yes, what time is good for you?",
    "answer": "4",
    "timestamp": "2023-08-11T13:44:23",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "is 5 fine?",
    "answer": "Hey we can do Friday then",
    "timestamp": "2023-08-11T15:12:17",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "thanks",
    "answer": "3:15 on Friday works ?",
    "timestamp": "2023-08-11T15:12:34",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "could we do 3?",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "2023-08-11T15:20:44",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "made it to the council of finance league",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "14/11/2023, 4:07:13‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "salam",
    "answer": "WAS",
    "timestamp": "16/11/2023, 8:25:36‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "so could we reschedule our meeting?",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "16/11/2023, 8:26:21‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "sure",
    "answer": "4:20 on Monday",
    "timestamp": "16/11/2023, 8:26:35‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "could we do after 5? that‚Äôs the last day of the competition and i‚Äôm not free till 5.",
    "answer": "Ok let‚Äôs finalaose time tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "16/11/2023, 8:27:27‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "sure",
    "answer": "https://youtu.be/M95m2EFb7IQ?si=uW_PvW6d5CLXeK_W",
    "timestamp": "16/11/2023, 8:27:57‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "what times r good for you?",
    "answer": "can do 3:30ish?",
    "timestamp": "20/11/2023, 5:27:15‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "my dads asking if we can do 3 if possible",
    "answer": "Yes is he in town",
    "timestamp": "22/11/2023, 2:35:04‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "yes",
    "answer": "yes",
    "timestamp": "22/11/2023, 2:45:41‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "perfect thanks",
    "answer": "Hey lets meet soon",
    "timestamp": "22/11/2023, 2:49:52‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "yeah sure",
    "answer": "we can target friday",
    "timestamp": "2023-05-12T23:54:38",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "sure",
    "answer": "Hey you wanna meet today",
    "timestamp": "2023-06-12T10:50:23",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "today is really busy",
    "answer": "ok will coordinate",
    "timestamp": "2023-08-12T14:06:30",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "if u want we could do a call",
    "answer": "Oh ok",
    "timestamp": "13/12/2023, 5:01:03‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "i believe 23rd",
    "answer": "Ok maybe we can meet once you‚Äôre back",
    "timestamp": "13/12/2023, 5:01:22‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "perfect",
    "answer": "hey hope all well",
    "timestamp": "13/12/2023, 5:05:00‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "let‚Äôs meet this weekend?",
    "answer": "ok ‚Äé[28/12/2023, 4:33:11‚ÄØPM] Rizwan Javed: Ismail Iqbal Outlook 2024.pdf ‚Ä¢ ‚Äé53 pages ‚Äédocument omitted",
    "timestamp": "26/12/2023, 5:55:34‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "hey can we meet tomorrow?",
    "answer": "Office is shut on Sundays",
    "timestamp": "30/12/2023, 12:22:39‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "hey, when can we meet today?",
    "answer": "2:30",
    "timestamp": "2024-01-01T11:05:27",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "2:30 is difficult‚Ä¶.can we do 530?",
    "answer": "im in office till 4PM today",
    "timestamp": "2024-01-01T14:13:15",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "i‚Äôm free tomorrow if you can do then?",
    "answer": "ok will do tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "2024-01-01T14:13:56",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 pm is fine?",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "2024-01-01T14:14:15",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "when would u like to meet?",
    "answer": "Let‚Äôs do 4 tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "16/01/2024, 8:43:54‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "i‚Äôm trying to convince the heads to release a top 3 rank",
    "answer": "Ok cool",
    "timestamp": "20/01/2024, 7:32:01‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "i have test week until thursday so is friday possible?",
    "answer": "let sadaf revert",
    "timestamp": "19/02/2024, 12:26:36‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "hey can we meet today or tomorrow as the forms for student council are coming out. i wanted to make sure i do it as well as possible",
    "answer": "When are they due for submission",
    "timestamp": "23/02/2024, 12:19:10‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "i think tomorrow would be safer because i‚Äôm not sure the exact time the forms get released",
    "answer": "Ok if tomorrow maybe it could be online? If you get the form before then maybe coming today is better",
    "timestamp": "23/02/2024, 12:45:50‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "5*",
    "answer": "@923333575290 does this work",
    "timestamp": "23/02/2024, 2:17:35‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923087979222 can you come earlier",
    "answer": "i think his tuition finishes at 5",
    "timestamp": "23/02/2024, 2:53:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "hey are we meeting today?",
    "answer": "I believe sadaf will have one with you",
    "timestamp": "24/02/2024, 12:26:15‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "so my council friend thought this point would represent me more accurately",
    "answer": "yes looking good",
    "timestamp": "24/02/2024, 10:05:01‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "so tmrw night",
    "answer": "might make some minor changes.",
    "timestamp": "24/02/2024, 11:14:17‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "sure",
    "answer": "\\cool",
    "timestamp": "24/02/2024, 11:14:29‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hey zarain yes overall it looks good now. Let‚Äôs wait incase rizwan wants to make any minor changes. There are a couple of minor grammatical errors which I‚Äôll fix as well",
    "answer": "I would propose an initiative that would promote further inclusivity within sports and athletics at KGS. I believe that some students do not realise their full potential and may not push themselves accordingly. At the beginning of the academic year, as house captain, I would shortlist and positively encourage students whom I believe underestimate themselves, and will focus on building an environment which will encourage them to train to their optimal potential. I believe , this would make the overall sports environment more inclusive and diverse. (495 characters) An attribute I have is that I am easy to approach; I have interacted with many of my juniors and created healthy relationships with lots of them. Secondly, I am a believer in equal opportunity; students within KGS should have equal access to trainings which is shown by providing my own vehicle to help students whom struggle to reach training and sports trials. Thirdly, I am reliable; this is shown through my consistent participation and effort in trainings, marchpast as well as PE display. (493 characters)",
    "timestamp": "25/02/2024, 11:25:09‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "could you please share some account tutors i could attend?",
    "answer": "PRECISION INSTITUTE. Plot 15-C Lane#2 Shahbaz Comm Area Phase 6 D.H.A 0213-5341301 OR 0213-5840064. It's in the basement of the building which is exactly behind Broadway Pizza shahbaz",
    "timestamp": "26/02/2024, 1:11:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "the writing workshop?",
    "answer": "Yes due to weather etc",
    "timestamp": "2024-01-03T17:57:00",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok üëç",
    "answer": "üå±üå≥üåø https://youtu.be/zGhB0afjAbY?si=6AHg0nG3ewnuOrNa",
    "timestamp": "2024-09-03T14:12:34",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "is 330 possible?",
    "answer": "Let sadaf confirm",
    "timestamp": "20/03/2024, 6:43:41‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes that‚Äôs fine",
    "answer": "Hey good work on prefect :)",
    "timestamp": "20/03/2024, 11:05:23‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "thanks so much",
    "answer": "Hello",
    "timestamp": "2024-08-04T22:46:29",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "sorry again",
    "answer": "pls dont miss these now",
    "timestamp": "22/04/2024, 3:38:49‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "will be 5 minutes late",
    "answer": "pls put pointers on the stuff we discussed in our last meeting",
    "timestamp": "23/04/2024, 2:57:59‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "SAT registration is out, should i book august only or both august and october just in case?",
    "answer": "August for now",
    "timestamp": "2024-07-05T21:13:41",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "is it possible for me to come in tomorrow?",
    "answer": "@923333575290",
    "timestamp": "22/05/2024, 7:44:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéSadaf Khan added Shiraz Ali Larik Canada. Tap to change who can add other members.",
    "answer": "Hey",
    "timestamp": "23/05/2024, 5:58:03‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "python for analytics and a consultancy management course",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "24/05/2024, 4:12:59‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "are we confirmed for 330?",
    "answer": "@14374840028",
    "timestamp": "30/05/2024, 3:13:22‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "if you need to reschedule it‚Äôs possible.",
    "answer": "Zarain he‚Äôs here",
    "timestamp": "30/05/2024, 4:22:01‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "yes i can come online",
    "answer": "Hey @923087979222 what‚Äôs happening",
    "timestamp": "19/06/2024, 4:25:35‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also making posts on the awareness page",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "29/06/2024, 11:21:38‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "i‚Äôll be back on the 24th",
    "answer": "Hey Zarain what are you up to",
    "timestamp": "18/07/2024, 7:39:24‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "bec usually i‚Äôm very good in math",
    "answer": "Do a recheck",
    "timestamp": "13/08/2024, 10:17:19‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "for ED in the US, can you send in retake grades later since the grade comes in january? or can you give an excuse that one of the papers was missing?",
    "answer": "Nopes",
    "timestamp": "13/08/2024, 10:33:19‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "bec i‚Äôm good at math this doesn‚Äôt make sense",
    "answer": "when will recheck result come",
    "timestamp": "13/08/2024, 10:41:09‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "hey so i wanted to drop accounts as a subject and wanted to get the green light from you guys? ‚Äé<This message was edited>",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "14/08/2024, 6:17:33‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Super swamped tomorrow with school stuff",
    "answer": "What are we thinking of ED choice now ?",
    "timestamp": "18/08/2024, 9:47:40‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I can get a recommendation from my Psychology teacher but I also feel that a recommendation from my Accounrs teacher could also look very good as I was struggling a lot in accounts till around February and with his help i was able to study and get a B in the cie",
    "answer": "you can call me and discuss",
    "timestamp": "26/08/2024, 4:39:43‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "sure",
    "answer": "Hey, so my discussion with Zarains dad: wont do ED-1 retake of Math potential ED-2 could be Wesleyan or Tufts but we can decide lets focus on UC apps asap. and lets close on UK Major by next week",
    "timestamp": "26/08/2024, 4:40:01‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok will do Friday then",
    "answer": "Score ?",
    "timestamp": "2024-04-09T22:22:42",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Predicted grades: Economics A* Psychology A* Math B Coding Pass ‚Äé<This message was edited>",
    "answer": "Ok so post math retake they may change ?",
    "timestamp": "13/09/2024, 9:12:36‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "yes confirmed that with my counselor ‚Äé[13/09/2024, 9:31:43‚ÄØAM] Zarain Asim Kgs: Scan 13 Sep 24 9¬∑30¬∑33‚ÄØAM.pdf ‚Ä¢ ‚Äé1 page ‚Äédocument omitted",
    "answer": "ok cool",
    "timestamp": "13/09/2024, 9:31:36‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923087979222 are you free for a meeting tomorrow at 8:30PM?",
    "answer": "@923087979222 ?",
    "timestamp": "13/09/2024, 8:49:54‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923087979222 lets meet today at 8:45PM (Sunday)?",
    "answer": "@923087979222 pls confirm",
    "timestamp": "29/09/2024, 7:52:52‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I have tuition around this time is the issue for my math retake",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "29/09/2024, 4:23:49‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will let you know and reschedule accordingly",
    "answer": "Hey, please be at the office on October 5, 2024. The head of International office from University of Edinburgh will be visiting our office from 1:45 PM till 3:15 PM. We will discuss program choices, location and any specific questions you may have pertaining to the university.",
    "timestamp": "29/09/2024, 6:10:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923087979222 lets meet 8PM tomorrow (Tuesday)",
    "answer": "Reminder for the session tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "2024-01-10T06:04:37",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok sure",
    "answer": "Hi the SOAS head of International office will be visiting our premises on Monday at 4:10PM Please come and attend the session. This will address all questions related to the university and the admissions process.",
    "timestamp": "2024-07-10T12:12:14",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "can we have a meeting soon?",
    "answer": "yes",
    "timestamp": "2024-11-10T19:55:00",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "monday or tuesday?",
    "answer": "Monday just come early to office I‚Äôll meet you",
    "timestamp": "2024-11-10T20:50:31",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "sorry will be 5-10 min late ‚Äé[15/10/2024, 4:02:01‚ÄØPM] Zarain Asim Kgs: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "answer": "https://www.lse.ac.uk/study-at-lse/undergraduate/bsc-economics-and-economic-history#entry-requirements",
    "timestamp": "15/10/2024, 3:28:12‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "i‚Äôve heard a lot of good things about him and people don‚Äôt have good reviews of edge",
    "answer": "I mean you can check",
    "timestamp": "18/10/2024, 10:29:22‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923087979222 are you free for a meeting at 8:30PM (Saturday) ‚Äé<This message was edited>",
    "answer": "@923087979222",
    "timestamp": "19/10/2024, 10:23:47‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "any update?",
    "answer": "@14374840028",
    "timestamp": "26/10/2024, 11:52:57‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Could we have a meeting to discuss this?",
    "answer": "Sure",
    "timestamp": "2024-09-11T19:19:17",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923087979222 let‚Äôs have a meeting tomorrow at 7PM",
    "answer": "Zarain pls do this so I can review too",
    "timestamp": "2024-10-11T07:03:22",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sunday 7PM or Monday 7PM",
    "answer": "I believe it should be today",
    "timestamp": "2024-10-11T11:06:12",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok üëç",
    "answer": "@923087979222 is there interest in UT Austin",
    "timestamp": "2024-10-11T21:21:01",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I can definitely come tomorrow I‚Äôm free most of the day",
    "answer": "Ok tomorrow is fine",
    "timestamp": "2024-11-11T11:31:47",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Please have a look at the UK courses before then so we can help you decide",
    "answer": "LSE - Economics & Economic History and Politics & Economics or Philosophy & Economics, UCL - History, Politics and Economics, Warwick - Economics, Psychology and Philosophy, Durham - Economics & Politics, SOAS in clearing and KCL with Foundation",
    "timestamp": "2024-11-11T11:33:27",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "When are UC deadlines?",
    "answer": "Nov 30",
    "timestamp": "14/11/2024, 8:54:26‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôm stuck in Kashmir for probably the next two days, can we work on UC apps online?",
    "answer": "fill in all the sections including activities",
    "timestamp": "26/11/2024, 1:37:45‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will do today",
    "answer": "yup everything",
    "timestamp": "26/11/2024, 1:39:07‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "He had filled a decent amount of it at the office. @923087979222 please complete",
    "answer": "@923087979222 I‚Äôll review the app tomorrow pls complete all sections",
    "timestamp": "26/11/2024, 2:40:27‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Done most of the activities, only essays r left",
    "answer": "Ok I will review early morning",
    "timestamp": "26/11/2024, 7:23:35‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôm here",
    "answer": "come in",
    "timestamp": "28/11/2024, 4:43:12‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Start working on supplements for: Babson Boston NYU UIUC Wisconsin Madison ‚Äé<This message was edited>",
    "answer": "status on UC?",
    "timestamp": "28/11/2024, 6:19:11‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Have reviewed the entire application with my father. Should I submit now?",
    "answer": "Yes pls",
    "timestamp": "30/11/2024, 5:41:26‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I don‚Äôt think it‚Äôs been made yet",
    "answer": "Pls make",
    "timestamp": "2024-05-12T10:03:05",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay",
    "answer": "How was SAT",
    "timestamp": "2024-05-12T15:59:43",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Math was a bit iffy but solid",
    "answer": "@923087979222 how much of the common app have you filled",
    "timestamp": "2024-08-12T19:56:10",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Could we push this till this weekend",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "2024-09-12T13:41:46",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sending in abit",
    "answer": "Hey Zarain can you come in",
    "timestamp": "15/12/2024, 7:49:10‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tonight would be difficult I can pop in tomorrow if that‚Äôs alright",
    "answer": "Ok what time tomorrow",
    "timestamp": "16/12/2024, 6:53:23‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "By 4pm ‚Äé<This message was edited>",
    "answer": "Yaar that‚Äôs too late",
    "timestamp": "16/12/2024, 7:00:34‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "If that‚Äôs possible",
    "answer": "Yea",
    "timestamp": "16/12/2024, 7:01:17‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Account: s.asim14420@kgs.edu.pk Password: Zarainasim12345!",
    "answer": "we have decided to do ED 2 at Babson",
    "timestamp": "16/12/2024, 7:10:16‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is 6 fine?",
    "answer": "Zarain",
    "timestamp": "17/12/2024, 2:20:22‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay 5 min pls I‚Äôll try move around my schedule",
    "answer": "kindly come in and keep in mind that this will take a few hours",
    "timestamp": "17/12/2024, 2:28:52‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I can be there 415-430",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "17/12/2024, 2:30:23‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "If there‚Äôs anything you need me to work on I can work on it at night",
    "answer": "you know what needs to be done",
    "timestamp": "18/12/2024, 4:31:30‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚Äé‚ÄéShiraz Ali Larik Canada changed their phone number to a new number. ‚ÄéTap to message or add the new number.",
    "answer": "Zarain",
    "timestamp": "20/12/2024, 1:33:39‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôm free",
    "answer": "Why didn‚Äôt you come today",
    "timestamp": "20/12/2024, 11:13:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I wasn‚Äôt called it but I can come tomorrow",
    "answer": "What is new sat score",
    "timestamp": "20/12/2024, 11:14:38‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "1390 on this one",
    "answer": "Should we do Northeastern ED",
    "timestamp": "20/12/2024, 11:14:52‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Let‚Äôs discuss tmrw if ur free",
    "answer": "Just be here by 12:45",
    "timestamp": "20/12/2024, 11:15:11‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "No driver and parents aren‚Äôt home otherwise I‚Äôd come",
    "answer": "Come now",
    "timestamp": "20/12/2024, 11:17:03‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "s.asim14420@kgs.edu.pk Zarainasim12345!",
    "answer": "@923333575290 which of his supplements are done",
    "timestamp": "20/12/2024, 11:26:41‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "We currently have Colgate on the list which we can submit as well if we are keeping it",
    "answer": "We will replace Colgate with Penn State",
    "timestamp": "21/12/2024, 12:00:48‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you need me to come in today?",
    "answer": "Ofcourse Yaar",
    "timestamp": "21/12/2024, 2:00:13‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "‚ÄéYou deleted this message.",
    "timestamp": "21/12/2024, 2:32:51‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôm free anytime after 2PM",
    "answer": "Come at 2",
    "timestamp": "23/12/2024, 10:19:29‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "@923087979222 put list of all submissions",
    "timestamp": "24/12/2024, 3:36:40‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Submitted: Babson Bates Boston University Emory University F&M NYU Northeastern UIUC Wesleyan UVA ‚Äé<This message was edited>",
    "answer": "@923333575290 before Jan 5th the ones pending include: Notre Dame Boston College Vassar",
    "timestamp": "24/12/2024, 3:48:13‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Or do you mean umass Amherst?",
    "answer": "Umass",
    "timestamp": "24/12/2024, 4:42:01‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923018379777 please coordinate to submit vassar and Boston college",
    "answer": "Zarain plug in essays I‚Äôll review shortly",
    "timestamp": "31/12/2024, 10:52:39‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "ok will do",
    "answer": "done?",
    "timestamp": "31/12/2024, 1:01:49‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok wait for @923018379777 to review",
    "answer": "Share pdf here [Image] [Image]",
    "timestamp": "2025-01-01T16:23:42",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923018379777",
    "answer": "Submit pls",
    "timestamp": "2025-03-01T23:47:49",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "A in math retake",
    "answer": "cool",
    "timestamp": "2025-09-01T15:08:27",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923087979222 you need to submit Purdue USC and Madison today. Please share PDFs for review",
    "answer": "@923087979222",
    "timestamp": "15/01/2025, 5:50:04‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "sharing the pdfs soon [Image]",
    "answer": "Submit [Image] [Image]",
    "timestamp": "15/01/2025, 7:38:51‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "purdue and wisconsin good to go? @923333575290 @923018379777",
    "answer": "Yup",
    "timestamp": "15/01/2025, 10:23:27‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@923087979222 lmk as soon as ur done with changes",
    "answer": "@923087979222",
    "timestamp": "15/01/2025, 11:31:15‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "hey so i‚Äôm at the hospital. i‚Äôve gotten my transcript and all the things required for bacconi. once i get home can i finish it and send u the pdf?",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "23/01/2025, 3:30:31‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "school counselor said she could do it from her end",
    "answer": "Pls put the Boconni app",
    "timestamp": "24/01/2025, 4:47:41‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "apart from this i‚Äôm done and will share the pdf",
    "answer": "What Major are we targeting",
    "timestamp": "31/01/2025, 10:26:07‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "which do you think is the better option",
    "answer": "Can do plain econ",
    "timestamp": "31/01/2025, 10:53:22‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "i was thinking that too",
    "answer": "Ok do",
    "timestamp": "31/01/2025, 10:56:04‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "which school?",
    "answer": "Wait lemme login and do this",
    "timestamp": "31/01/2025, 10:58:31‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "logging out",
    "answer": "send me login",
    "timestamp": "31/01/2025, 11:02:29‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "s.asim14420@kgs.edu.pk Zarainasim12345!",
    "answer": "done",
    "timestamp": "31/01/2025, 11:08:30‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "school can‚Äôt change it, they said to email northeastern directly",
    "answer": "So you wanna or keep as is",
    "timestamp": "2025-03-02T16:24:26",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "i‚Äôll change it ‚Äé[11/02/2025, 4:42:55‚ÄØPM] Zarain Asim Kgs: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "answer": "its ok, this is their standard response.",
    "timestamp": "2025-03-02T16:24:58",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "yes i missed the self report unfortunately",
    "answer": "so have they given an extension",
    "timestamp": "2025-03-03T15:30:18",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "what‚Äôs the process for that?",
    "answer": "have they asked u to send the self report",
    "timestamp": "2025-03-03T15:30:45",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "no they haven‚Äôt",
    "answer": "have they declined your app",
    "timestamp": "2025-03-03T15:31:17",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "yes it says my application has been denied",
    "answer": "Yes then can‚Äôt do much",
    "timestamp": "2025-03-03T15:33:53",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "am checking all my portals again as of right now",
    "answer": "Pls see all California ones too",
    "timestamp": "2025-03-03T15:41:59",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yayy! Awesome. Congratulations",
    "answer": "Wow",
    "timestamp": "2025-07-03T23:26:27",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéYou added Hira Zubair Fellow",
    "answer": "@923087979222 if you can come in tomorrow you can do your kings foundation app",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-06T15:56:08",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is day after tomorrow possible?",
    "answer": "Yup",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-06T17:48:29",
    "student_name": "Zarain Asim",
    "student_phone": "+2328208392",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéMessages and calls are end-to-end encrypted. Only people in this chat can read, listen to, or share them.",
    "answer": "Hey Zayan",
    "timestamp": "2023-11-08T15:07:46",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok, See you then",
    "answer": "cool",
    "timestamp": "2023-11-08T15:11:18",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "The course I had started with coursera about anatomy of the body, is no longer available",
    "answer": "Ok we can look at something else",
    "timestamp": "15/08/2023, 9:32:38‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thank you",
    "answer": "How‚Äôs ucat prep coming along",
    "timestamp": "16/08/2023, 12:15:05‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Far*",
    "answer": "Ok great",
    "timestamp": "16/08/2023, 3:09:42‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Also please share your email address so I can share the essays I wanted",
    "answer": "Hey Zayan pls share your email addy",
    "timestamp": "16/08/2023, 3:44:35‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I‚Äôll send essays to read tomorrow",
    "answer": "cool",
    "timestamp": "16/08/2023, 10:56:49‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "Hey Zayan pls can you whatsapp your results",
    "timestamp": "21/08/2023, 6:06:46‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "hows ucat prep",
    "timestamp": "24/08/2023, 12:23:02‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I can talk anytime on Tuesday. I used the book UCAT prep  and medic mind course, but now I am  practicing using medify",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "26/08/2023, 7:42:33‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hello sadaf, would it be possible to do our meeting after the 9th please",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å©",
    "timestamp": "28/08/2023, 5:30:01‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes noted. Really wanted to try have one session on the statement before then. But can do right after the test",
    "answer": "Yea I think if @‚Å®Zayaan Farhan Bahrain‚Å© you can squeeze one session that would be great",
    "timestamp": "30/08/2023, 2:30:10‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I can do tomorrow 4:00 Bahrain time if that is ok?",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© @‚Å®Amna Jamali‚Å© can we do this?",
    "timestamp": "31/08/2023, 7:00:21‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Don‚Äôt think I can do 4 tomorrow. However 6pm your time I can do",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Zayaan Farhan Bahrain‚Å© ?",
    "timestamp": "31/08/2023, 7:35:41‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes. Works for me",
    "answer": "Zayan will revert shortly on the time for today",
    "timestamp": "2023-01-09T16:01:56",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Zayan should we do 6:30 /6:45 your time then?",
    "answer": "Sadaf 6:45 Zayaan‚Äôs time is fine",
    "timestamp": "2023-01-09T16:49:56",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thank you so much. Sure will definitely start work on the draft",
    "answer": "Hey Zayan let‚Äôs speak soon to finalise your program/colleges",
    "timestamp": "2023-08-09T17:07:34",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Let me know when please",
    "answer": "We can do tomorrow ?",
    "timestamp": "2023-10-09T19:23:20",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sorry for the late reply, are you still able to do 5:00 my time today?",
    "answer": "hey will have to be on whatsapp",
    "timestamp": "2023-11-09T17:17:12",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thank you",
    "answer": "Hi guys let‚Äôs agree on a timeline to wrap the PS",
    "timestamp": "2023-11-09T17:48:01",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hey Zayan! When will you be sharing the revised draft of the statement?",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Zayaan Farhan Bahrain‚Å©",
    "timestamp": "13/09/2023, 4:44:37‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I am not too sure but I will work on it over the weekend",
    "answer": "Hey Zayan considering deadline is not too far away, please can we get this sooner",
    "timestamp": "13/09/2023, 8:27:05‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thank you, will research these universities and find the best four",
    "answer": "alsp update on the PS?",
    "timestamp": "17/09/2023, 9:35:51‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚ÄéYou added Sherry Farhan Bahrain",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© @‚Å®Amna Jamali‚Å©  pls share the feedback here",
    "timestamp": "19/09/2023, 8:35:10‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "And text here if u have any questions",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Zayaan Farhan Bahrain‚Å© @‚Å®Sherry Farhan Bahrain‚Å© please see comments sent on email",
    "timestamp": "20/09/2023, 10:33:11‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Great",
    "answer": "Hey Zayan",
    "timestamp": "2023-07-10T00:13:22",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Bahrain time*",
    "answer": "Can we do a little later then ?",
    "timestamp": "2023-10-10T18:38:43",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "Hey Zayan",
    "timestamp": "2023-10-10T19:07:24",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "start*",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Zayaan Farhan Bahrain‚Å©",
    "timestamp": "17/10/2023, 3:51:36‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "On Thursday*",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Zannirah Rehman‚Å©",
    "timestamp": "17/10/2023, 5:00:50‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sorry I am having problems with internet",
    "answer": "Asa Zayan",
    "timestamp": "19/10/2023, 5:45:25‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Not available in Bahrain, my sister is trying to find it in karachi. And then she'll send it. If not I'll have to order from amazon",
    "answer": "maybe he can find an online version",
    "timestamp": "21/10/2023, 2:43:58‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Okay yes. I think Amazon has one",
    "answer": "yes please",
    "timestamp": "21/10/2023, 2:44:50‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "He's starting Insha'Allah from sunday",
    "answer": "ok AH",
    "timestamp": "21/10/2023, 2:46:10‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I'll ask him to send you a link on the company. Would be great if you could give him some questions/ ideas on what info to gather, that would help him. Thanks",
    "answer": "yes i will",
    "timestamp": "21/10/2023, 2:46:55‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thanks",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "21/10/2023, 2:47:21‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "hi zayan, can you please send me your ouac login details.",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Zayaan Farhan Bahrain‚Å©",
    "timestamp": "23/10/2023, 2:44:12‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Username: Zayaan123 Password: 230905Zayaan@1",
    "answer": "Hey Zayan",
    "timestamp": "24/10/2023, 2:18:34‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Logged*",
    "answer": "Zayaan can you tell me your predicted grade subject wise",
    "timestamp": "26/10/2023, 4:50:45‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Maths: A Chemistry: A Biology: A*",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "26/10/2023, 5:42:21‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sure will do it today",
    "answer": "Hey sadaf can you send 2 management PS here",
    "timestamp": "27/10/2023, 12:33:17‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Here are some sample statements for management",
    "answer": "ouac is ready for submission",
    "timestamp": "2023-03-11T15:09:56",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "The call will be around 15-20 mins. Just need to finalise his McGill application. Can we schedule around 5:00 PM?",
    "answer": "zanirah just keep in mind they are two hours behind us",
    "timestamp": "2023-06-11T14:11:11",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Alright, thank you.",
    "answer": "did u gus speak for the mcgill app",
    "timestamp": "2023-06-11T14:14:09",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "It's today at 5.00 pm",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "2023-07-11T14:22:28",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mc Gill app submitted",
    "answer": "ok great",
    "timestamp": "2023-08-11T13:36:16",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Alright noted",
    "answer": "Hey @‚Å®Zannirah Rehman‚Å© status of his UBC account",
    "timestamp": "2023-09-11T12:15:16",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "We're working on it. insha'Allah by Thursday it should be done, if not earlier.",
    "answer": "üëå",
    "timestamp": "14/11/2023, 12:27:46‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I have received a few emails, could you please send me your email so I can forward them to you",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Zannirah Rehman‚Å© pls can you look and see",
    "timestamp": "14/11/2023, 12:39:03‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Not asking for essay just to login into there database",
    "answer": "Ok you can you login and see what they‚Äôre asking for",
    "timestamp": "14/11/2023, 12:40:18‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Zayaan, did you make the account after our meeting that day?",
    "answer": "And if there‚Äôs any confusion then we can assist there too",
    "timestamp": "14/11/2023, 12:40:34‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "https://us05web.zoom.us/j/82868972654?pwd=sq4oUvH6KU4YqCeb7ELSKG3bv0pVU7.1",
    "answer": "Guys status on the essays",
    "timestamp": "14/11/2023, 5:15:47‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I am not going to school on Thursday so I am free to do a meeting",
    "answer": "did this meeting happen",
    "timestamp": "22/11/2023, 8:59:42‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "No",
    "answer": "https://www.lse.ac.uk/study-at-lse/undergraduate/degree-programmes-2024/bsc-management",
    "timestamp": "22/11/2023, 4:52:39‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "7:30 your time",
    "answer": "Hey @‚Å®Zannirah Rehman‚Å© he‚Äôs off school today",
    "timestamp": "22/11/2023, 8:23:47‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Are you joining? @‚Å®Zayaan Farhan Bahrain‚Å©",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Sherry Farhan Bahrain‚Å© @‚Å®Zayaan Farhan Bahrain‚Å©",
    "timestamp": "26/11/2023, 7:08:13‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "As discussed [Image]",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Zannirah Rehman‚Å©",
    "timestamp": "2023-01-12T18:07:21",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Zayaan Farhan Bahrain‚Å© Please send me your portal login details for UofT",
    "answer": "Also Zannirah where are we with UBC essays",
    "timestamp": "2023-01-12T19:30:08",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "sending them in like an hour tops",
    "answer": "Ok",
    "timestamp": "2023-01-12T19:46:26",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "3rd one is the",
    "answer": "?",
    "timestamp": "2023-01-12T19:46:34",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "activities essay",
    "answer": "Ok so has he sent that ‚Äé[01/12/2023, 7:47:52‚ÄØPM] Sherry Farhan Bahrain: UBC essay question.docx ‚Ä¢ ‚Äé1 page ‚Äédocument omitted ‚Äé[01/12/2023, 7:48:42‚ÄØPM] Sherry Farhan Bahrain: UBC essay question 1.docx ‚Ä¢ ‚Äé1 page ‚Äédocument omitted",
    "timestamp": "2023-01-12T19:46:50",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "You qualify for an english language exemption if you have an A or above in O level English. However, if you have IELTS or any other english scores, input those. ‚Äé<This message was edited> [Image]",
    "answer": "Hey @‚Å®Sadaf Khan‚Å© @‚Å®Zannirah Rehman‚Å© we would wanna close this UofT doc by Wednesday pls",
    "timestamp": "2023-01-12T20:02:27",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "@‚Å®Zannirah Rehman‚Å© if you have time tomorrow morning pls let me know and I'll go through Rotman with you. Zayaan can't spare time now as he's studying, and as it has to be submitted tomorrow I need to add the rest of documents needed. I've done some but some I need clarity on. Thanks",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Zannirah Rehman‚Å©",
    "timestamp": "2023-12-12T00:06:31",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hey, if you‚Äôre free now, we can set a meeting",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Zayaan Farhan Bahrain‚Å© @‚Å®Sherry Farhan Bahrain‚Å© can we do this now.",
    "timestamp": "2023-12-12T17:59:13",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok thanks",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Zainab UK‚Å© please ask questions here",
    "timestamp": "2023-12-12T23:05:17",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Username:sidd3554@mylauier.ca Password: 230905Za@1",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Zannirah Rehman‚Å© they‚Äôre not accepting his current English as proof",
    "timestamp": "15/12/2023, 7:33:55‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ok",
    "answer": "did we sort the UofT English issue",
    "timestamp": "16/12/2023, 6:02:06‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Zayaan emailed on the above mentioned email. But they replied saying it's not an active email account. So we resent an email on what they had asked.",
    "answer": "ok ‚Äé[18/12/2023, 10:04:51‚ÄØPM] Zayaan Farhan Bahrain: ‚Äéimage omitted",
    "timestamp": "18/12/2023, 11:55:03‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Please also update us regarding the progress of your UBC application. This includes essays, and any other portal requirements. In case, the application is already submitted, update us regarding the status regardless.",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Sherry Farhan Bahrain‚Å©",
    "timestamp": "21/12/2023, 1:15:12‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi! Have sent across a finalised version of the uk statement over email",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Zannirah Rehman‚Å© pls Can you have a call with. Zayans mom tomorrow and complete the ucas form",
    "timestamp": "22/12/2023, 9:54:47‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "What time are you free today @‚Å®Sherry Farhan Bahrain‚Å©?",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Sherry Farhan Bahrain‚Å©",
    "timestamp": "30/12/2023, 2:59:56‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yes that would be fine. Thankyou",
    "answer": "Hey once done lemme know",
    "timestamp": "30/12/2023, 9:05:12‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ucas login: Email: zs4892@student.st-Chris.net Password: 230905Zayaan@1",
    "answer": "UCAS is ready [Image]",
    "timestamp": "31/12/2023, 4:35:35‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "She means predicted",
    "answer": "By A level maybe she means to highlight that he‚Äôll appear in June 2024",
    "timestamp": "2024-04-01T11:25:20",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "How do I add that?",
    "answer": "Let Zannirah have a look in a bit",
    "timestamp": "2024-04-01T11:25:26",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sure",
    "answer": "have u changed the UCAS password",
    "timestamp": "2024-04-01T11:31:11",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Password is the same",
    "answer": "ok",
    "timestamp": "2024-04-01T15:16:26",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "I've logged out",
    "answer": "ive added A Level Bio and Chem",
    "timestamp": "2024-04-01T15:16:36",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "There's an issue now Rizwan. It's saying we're sorry couldn't save the changes. Although I see the changes. It's not submitting now",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Zannirah Rehman‚Å© can you log and check ? ‚Äé[10/01/2024, 3:50:55‚ÄØPM] Rizwan Javed: SOAS.pdf ‚Ä¢ ‚Äé2 pages ‚Äédocument omitted",
    "timestamp": "2024-04-01T15:50:45",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thank you",
    "answer": "üëçüëç",
    "timestamp": "2024-10-01T23:39:16",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Salam Rizwan. Zayaan has his chemistry paper today. Once he's back he'll send them to you by late afternoon. Hope that's okay?",
    "answer": "No issues",
    "timestamp": "2024-11-01T09:45:26",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "McGill password: 0507zs",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Zannirah Rehman‚Å© they have asked for some stuff",
    "timestamp": "24/01/2024, 2:18:34‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thankyou",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Zannirah Rehman‚Å© can you check quickly",
    "timestamp": "19/02/2024, 8:26:36‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "They‚Äôre asking for the High School Transcript with your current mid year grades on it. ‚Äé<This message was edited>",
    "answer": "@‚Å®Sherry Farhan Bahrain‚Å© can we do this asap pls",
    "timestamp": "20/02/2024, 4:07:14‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "We have a transcipt",
    "answer": "ok but are the mid results on it",
    "timestamp": "20/02/2024, 5:03:05‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Nope",
    "answer": "then we need to show this tos chool",
    "timestamp": "20/02/2024, 5:03:40‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "‚Äé‚ÄéAmna Jamali changed their phone number to a new number. ‚ÄéTap to message or add the new number.",
    "answer": "Asa please can I get a list of all acceptances, rejections and pending ones",
    "timestamp": "2024-08-03T02:10:51",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Acceptance: Durham,SOAS, Wilfred laurel(Waterloo) Pending: everything else Alhamdulliah no rejections",
    "answer": "Hi Zayan",
    "timestamp": "16/03/2024, 2:05:51‚ÄØAM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "But rotman commerce still pending",
    "answer": "MA",
    "timestamp": "29/03/2024, 11:19:30‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Alhamdulliah got an offer from Warwick [Image]",
    "answer": "‚ù§Ô∏è",
    "timestamp": "2024-09-04T19:23:20",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Durham SOAS Warwick",
    "answer": "any other updates?",
    "timestamp": "2024-11-04T20:57:16",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hi Rizwan, UBC has asked for.one last document. zayaan has tried several times to upload the document but we're unable to. Anyone from end can log in to his account and attach the document please. Zayaan his sending UBC log in details here along with the document. Thanks [Image]",
    "answer": "Pls send here",
    "timestamp": "23/04/2024, 9:02:16‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Hey Zayaan, I‚Äôve tried uploading your transcript using multiple devices but the error remains. Its best to use their link to drop a message because it seems to be an IT issue.",
    "answer": "Yes pls do that asap",
    "timestamp": "24/04/2024, 3:18:30‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Thank you [Image]",
    "answer": "asa Zayan what is ur ucas ID",
    "timestamp": "24/04/2024, 11:50:55‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Password: 230905Zayaan@1",
    "answer": "thx",
    "timestamp": "30/04/2024, 3:43:55‚ÄØPM",
    "student_name": "Zayan Farhan",
    "student_phone": "+5963652137",
    "category": "general_inquiry"
  }
]